<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<FlavorTextDefs
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the Flavor Text Editor -->
    <!-- FlavorText_General.xml -->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>GENERAL_CONVERSATION_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Tallas orda cullan bana.
    (You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>1</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_FESTRON</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>true</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMax>-1</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerStronger</RelativeStrength>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>2</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>As you probably suspect, we will soon be laying our eggs inside your flesh.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_NAVIGATORS</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We have heard you refer to the Arnor and Dread Lords as the Precursors. We were the first to discover the subspace streams that connect different parts of the galaxy together.[BR][BR]What is not commonly known is that we didn't invent any sort of technology for this per se. They are not an invention but rather a discovery.[BR][BR]The subspace streams are, in fact, a natural phenomenon of the universe. For all we know, there are streams that reach other galaxies entirely.</Text>
            <Text>There are far stranger oddities in the universe than the subspace streams. For instance, there are dimensional gates that travel between different universes entirely.[BR][BR]We once encountered a species from another universe known as the Arilou who came from a universe with its own storied history.</Text>
            <Text>Long after the Precursors disappeared we were satisfied with simply exploring the universe to find the next great wonder.[BR][BR]Unfortunately, there are far worse things in the universe than the species you refer to as the Dread Lords. [BR][BR]The ancient creators, known as the Mithrilar, had experimented on many types of creations before they made the Precursors and not all of those things are gone and some, I am afraid to say, are now awakened.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MIMOT</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Long ago, on our world, there were five other sentient species. I suppose you could call them 'Sapient' but who am I to play games with semantics. In any case, we were the only ones to survive.

</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_XELOXI</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>For us, self-interest is the highest form of morality. You can know, with absolute certainty, that we will be your most loyal friend if it is in our self-interest for you to survive.[BR][BR]Of course, conversely, if it is in our self-interest for you to die, you can be equally assured that you will die.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ARCEAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>It has been lost to history but it was our civilization that invented the stargates. [BR][BR]Over two hundred thousand years we invested trillions into the construction of a vast network of stargates.[BR][BR]The stargates allowed ships to travel Hyperspace level 2 between any two of them. This cut down the travel time of a ship traveling 10 lightyears down to only a little over 3 years.[BR][BR]Of course, the proliferation of the Hyperdrive technology allowed individual ships to travel much faster making our efforts obsolete. But for tens of thousands of years, this part of the galaxy was ours.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRENGIN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The other civilizations have not come to the realization that the universe is not only finite but only a small fraction will ever be reachable. [BR][BR]Make no mistake, this galaxy is all we will ever reach.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our world was called 'Elemental' by the Precursors during their height. [BR][BR]The first off-world proxy war between the two Precursor factions that we called the Dred'nir and Elas'nir was fought on the surface of our planet long before the other species of the galaxy even evolved into their modern form. Yes, that even includes the humans.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_YOR</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We may not exterminate your kind in the immediate future. But eventually there will be a reckoning.[BR][BR]We have made the calculations. The great void sometimes called Bootes void is simply the result of billions of years of Dyson sphere construction hiding the light of countless galaxies. The civilization at the center of that void has already had their singularity. </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TORIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our civilization was once a peaceful, preindustrial, aquatic paradise. Then the Drengin came.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MANTI</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We were aware of space travel for centuries. How could we help but not know when raiders were perpetually coming down from the heavens and stealing our offspring?[BR][BR]It was fortunate for us when one of their ships failed to escape the surface of our planet and we learned their secrets. </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We do not seek to destroy the Yor simply because they stole our home world. [BR][BR]Contrary to some reports, we did not actually create the Yor. The Precursors ordered us to make them, but the actual spark of life that the Yor have did not come from us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_IRIDIUM</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>In a galaxy with such varied species, it is easy to simply stereotype different civilizations based on their most obvious traits. [BR][BR]We are treated like we are greedy. But this isn't true. Our ideology is opportunity. When we trade, we are creating a better universe for our customers as well as for ourselves.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_BARATAK</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We are not explorers by choice but by necessity.[BR][BR]There is something actively absorbing the life force from all worlds. That is why you find so many dead planets. These worlds weren't always dead. </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_RESISTANCE</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We look forward to rejoining Earth. But while Earth was trapped behind a Precursor shield for years, our fleet was trapped in a pocket universe of the Precursors making.[BR][BR]We saw things in that pocket universe that we cannot unsee. It wasn't just the Orb of Draginol, the so-called Bane weapon, that came out of that pocket universe with us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A well informed galaxy is a peaceful galaxy. If you want to know things about others, seek us out.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRATH</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>While we are certainly physically capable of physically crushing any other species, we do our best to avoid actual direct physical violence.[BR][BR]Our kind can only reproduce on our original home world that is now lost to us. While we are long lived, we are not immortal nor are indestructible.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_KRYNN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>There is a misunderstanding that THE WAY is a religion based on faith. It is not. [BR][BR]We are a collection of species that have had direct, physical contact with a being of such immense glory, whose plan for the universe is so sublime, that we feel obligated to bring others into this holy cause.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>5</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>8</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>2</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SameCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The time is coming where we civilizations with the same philosophy must unite together to destroy those who would stand against us.</Text>
            <Text>Soon, {LEADERNAME:2}, the galaxy will unite one way or the other.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>5</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SameCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We are pleased with the ideological path you have chosen thus far. Benevolence is the path of the righteous.</Text>
            <Text>Resisting the temptation of evil is not always easy. But it will help us all build a better galaxy.</Text>
            <Text>The universe is dark enough without adding to it, {LEADERNAME:2}. We are pleased with the path you have taken so far.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>5</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SameCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Merciless</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You impress us, {LEADERNAME:2}. Your understanding that the weak are fodder for the strong has won you respect with us.</Text>
            <Text>Is it kinder to allow the weak to continue to suffer a state of existence? Or to end their pain by exterminating them? Based on your actions, {LEADERNAME:2}, it would seem you agree with us. The weak must be exterminated.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>5</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <PersonalityType>Aggressive</PersonalityType>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>SiliconBasedAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>What, exactly, are you supposed to be? Some sort of rock-based worm species?</Text>
            <Text>It is hard to believe that a silicon-based life form naturally evolved. Are you sure you are natural?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <PersonalityType>Aggressive</PersonalityType>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>AmphibiousAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The {PLAYERFACTION:2} should have stayed in the sewers of their home world, {LEADERNAME:2}. There is very little water in space.</Text>
            <Text>The vacuum of space is no place for the likes of you, {LEADERNAME:2} . You should return to the oceans of your home world.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CommonEnemy</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Cruel</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The {PLAYERFACTION:2} and {PLAYERFACTION:1} will crush our mutual enemies together! We look forward to torturing them and their pets!</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CommonEnemy</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Diplomatic</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>It is a shame we find ourselves in a time of galactic war. But with you fighting our mutual enemy we believe victory is certain.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>TradeWithOpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Be careful who you trade with, {LEADERNAME:2}. Our people have no tolerance for those who affiliate themselves with evil.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>YouAreWarMonger</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Peaceful</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The advantage you may have gained by declaring war early will cost you far more in good will, {LEADERNAME:2}.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TAUNTING_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>-3</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>OpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your civilization makes me ill. The evil and immorality that you are spreading across the universe makes us dream for your demise.</Text>
            <Text>Your evil civilization will eventually suffer the fate of all civilizations that lack of a moral code.</Text>
            <Text>It saddens us that your civilization continues to exist. We look forward to the day your species goes extinct from the universe.</Text>
            <Text>Your civilization has chosen a poor ethical route. We can only hope that in time, you suffer the fate of all evil empires.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TAUNTING_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>-3</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerWeaker</RelativeStrength>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>OpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You think your power is impressive? Your civilization thrives only because it has always taken the quick and easy path.</Text>
            <Text>Despite your power, we continue to see you as inferiors due to your moral choices.</Text>
            <Text>The corruption within the heart of your civilization has given you a temporary benefit in power. But eventually, your civilization will crumble and we will be there to laugh.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>WarWithAlly</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You are are war with our ally, {LEADERNAME:2}. Find a way to make peace or pay the consequences.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerMuchWeaker</RelativeStrength>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our people admire your vast power, {LEADERNAME:2}.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_YOR_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>SyntheticLife</SpeakerRaceTrait>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>I cannot believe I'm talking to animated meat. How do you function?</Text>
            <Text>I just want to understand. You communicate by pushing air through a piece of meat that is located in a hole that you call your "mouth"?</Text>
            <Text>We continue to be astounded that you creatures exist. You're basically a sack of goo. How are you even created?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Seriously? Are you brazenly going to try to incite our people to rebel right in front of us?</Text>
            <Text>If you don't quit trying to culturally subjugate my people, we will be forced to declare war.</Text>
            <Text>Your communication starbases are spreading your ugly culture too close to our worlds. Remove them.</Text>
            <Text>We do not appreciate your communication starbases so close to our planets.</Text>
            <Text>Your communication starbase is so close to our worlds that we are picking up your obnoxious entertainment.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>40</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>My daughter came by and told me about the amazing ways of your people. I asked her how had she heard about it and that's when I learned that you have a Cultural starbase inside our area of influence! Get rid of it.</Text>
            <Text>You seriously think you can culturally dominate humans? We have chocolate!</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRENGIN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your vile culture offends us. Remove your ridiculous starbases from our sphere of influence immediately.</Text>
            <Text>Your culture is no match for Torian Fire Chili.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our people have resisted Titans, Sorcerer Kings, and Fallen Enchantresses. We will resist your deplorable culture.</Text>
            <Text>Our world is literally magical. Do you really think they will want to join you?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_KRYNN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Stop trying to brainwash our people into following your vile culture immediately.</Text>
            <Text>Our people are deeply spiritual. We will not continue to tolerate your cultural attacks on us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_YOR</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You are wasting your time. Our people cannot be culturally assimilated.</Text>
            <Text>As non-biologics, we have no need for your culture. We are immune to it. Our worlds will never rebel.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We have no interest in your culture. Did you think we wouldn't notice your starbase right next to our planets?</Text>
            <Text>We already had to flee one world, we do not intend to be subjugated to an alien culture. Remove your starbases.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TRADE_OPPOSINGCULTURE_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>TradeWithOpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Be wary who you trade with. If you want to be our friend, do not trade with those who have despicable ideologies.</Text>
            <Text>You should be aware that you are trading with a civilization whose culture represents everything we are against.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_OPENBORDERS_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>OpenBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We are getting a lot of reports from our people regarding the ease of working with your people. 
    
    The open borders treaty that exists between our peoples has greatly improved commerce and relations between our citizens and yours.</Text>
            <Text>The open borders treaty has made navigation in this sector much easier. Thank you.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_ATWAR_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>AtWar</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>StrongerMilitary</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Soon, your worlds will be ours.</Text>
            <Text>If you surrender now, we will show mercy.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>2</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your planets are ripe for conquest. Even now, my military advisors are urging me to take action.</Text>
            <Text>Your military is so weak that it is a miracle you haven't already been conquered.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>70</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>EntrepreneursAbility</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>As much as we love capitalism, we do not appreciate you intentionally trying to incite our people to join you. Remove your starbases, or else.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>TradeRoute</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our mutual trade continues to strengthen our relationship.</Text>
            <Text>We are finding that our trading relationship is building a sense of trust between our people.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>0</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>1</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SharedBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our shared borders are making my advisors irritable. Make sure you stay on your side.</Text>
            <Text>We admit we don't respect your borders. Perhaps it's time for an open borders treaty?</Text>
            <Text>There is tension due to our close borders. An open borders treaty would alleviate this.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>StarbaseInZOCWithoutOpenBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You should be aware that our military is quite annoyed with your starbase. You should negotiate an open borders treaty with us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>ShipInZOCWithoutOpenBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>While we do not plan to attack your ships that trespass, be aware that they cause us some consternation. If you want to travel through our zone of influence, negotiate an open borders treaty.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>MilitaryShipNearMyPlanet</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We have concerns about your armed ships traveling near our worlds without an open borders treaty.</Text>
            <Text>If you want to maintain good relations with us, then don't send armed ships into our space without an open borders treaty.</Text>
            <Text>We do not appreciate having military vessels traveling into our space without a treaty.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerMuchStronger</RelativeStrength>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>ConquestVictoryGoal</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our ultimate goal is to conquer the galaxy. When we ultimately consume you, we want you to know that it wasn't personal.</Text>
            <Text>Our people desire for galactic conquest.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>ColonizedWithinZOC</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You colonized a planet within our zone of influence. We won't necessarily go to war over that, but don't be surprised if the people of that world ultimately decide to join us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>What exactly is your long-term plan? My military advisors tell me that your civilization would be safer under our rule, given your lack of military power.</Text>
            <Text>Have you considered giving your worlds to us? Your people would be much safer under our protection.</Text>
            <Text>Your lack of military power is making you an easy target for would-be conquerors.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Aggressive</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your worlds...so poorly defended. So ripe for conquest.</Text>
            <Text>We appreciate your pacifism. It will make your eventual conquest that much easier.</Text>
            <Text>You have no idea how fortunate you are that we are busy with other things. Your pitiful military and rich worlds are calling to us. Do you understand?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Spiritual</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your people are calling upon us to learn the proper way to live.</Text>
            <Text>There is so much blasphemy on your worlds. It may soon be time to bring a proper moral order to them.</Text>
            <Text>Your people call out for redemption from their sins. We may be the instrument of their salvation.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Cruel</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your worlds are full of beings ripe for the feeding. You are like cattle waiting to be slaughtered.</Text>
            <Text>Your planets are so tempting to us. Our shock troops can be a bit sadistic, but in time, I suspect you will come to appreciate them.</Text>
            <Text>Your planets are ripe for the taking. Traditionally, we flay our victims alive, but if you wish to turn over your worlds over to us voluntarily, we will... well, let's be serious. We'll still flay you alive.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
</FlavorTextDefs>