<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
	
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_Name</Label>
		<String>Intueri Aggregate</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_ShortName</Label>
		<String>Intueri</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_LeaderName</Label>
		<String>Visus</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_Dec</Label>
		<String>The Intueri are a hive mind without any meaningful capability of complex thought. They can comprehend and imitate anything they see but are very slow to develop scientific breakthroughs independently.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_LeaderDec</Label>
		<String>Sees much, understands more.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_Callsign</Label>
		<String>I.A.S.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_StartupTitle</Label>
		<String>Galactic Witnesses</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_StartupDescription</Label>
		<String>The Intueri develop as quickly as those they watch. They can easily comprehend and replicate things they witness; however, their lack of creative thought and ability to problem solve impacts their ability to make their own discoveries.[BR][BR]The collective consciousness of the Intueri had been stagnant for nearly a millennia until they made contact with the Luxar. After first gazing upon their star ships and faster-than-light drives, the Intueri quickly took to the stars. Now they search far and wide for the knowledge of others to expand their own intelligence.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>FACTION_SEEING_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
		<String>The Intueri's have high exploration and sensor range, enabling them to quickly map out the galaxy. To compensate for their low Research rate the Intueri have the Cosmic Eye, a powerful tool that allows them to steal technology and research from other civilizations.</String>
	</StringTable>

</StringTableList>