<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!--Campaign Tutorial Text-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>AllianceAscendant_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Terran Alliance Ascendant</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>AllianceAscendant_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>The year is 2307. It has been decades since the Terran Alliance and their coalition were able to liberate the known universe from the evil Drengin Empire and their thralls.[BR][BR]The galaxy finds itself at peace (other than the continuing proliferation of Hyperdrive, which is allowing some of the aggressive "minor civilizations" to join the galactic stage.)[BR][BR]Today finds DL Bradley in charge of the Leathon system and its neighboring stars. Rumors are that a new civilization, the Xeloxi, is attacking freighters and extorting civilians into paying protection money. If these rumors are true, then something must be done...</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_Overall</Label>
        <String>Bring Stability to the Sector</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_OwnThreeMinorRaces_Name</Label>
        <String>Protect 3 Minor Civilizations</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_OwnThreeMinorRaces_Dec</Label>
        <String>Minor Civilizations have a single homeworld that will provide benefits when within a civilization's Zone of Control. Settle worlds and build starbases to extend your Zone of Control till there are 3 Minor Civilizations under your protection.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_DestroyXeloxi_Name</Label>
        <String>Defeat the Xeloxi</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_DestroyXeloxi_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Xeloxi have been extorting and pillaging these systems long enough. Remove the Xeloxi from the sector by taking all their planets. You can use diplomacy to buy yourself time to build up a strong fleet, but conflict is inevitable.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_EnsureMinorFactionsSurvive_Name</Label>
        <String>Ensure All Minor Civilizatios Survive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_AllianceAscendant_EnsureMinorFactionsSurvive_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Civilizations in this region of space have suffered enough. They've only recently achieved space-faring status and have been subjugated by immoral dealings since then. We must treat and protect them fairly to provide a true sense of security and gain their trust.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <!--Flavor Text for Terran FActions-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_AllianceAscendant_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>It's been decades since the last galactic conflict. The known systems have been more or less at peace. There's been a shift, though; there are reports that a new civilization is conducting less than legitimate business. Rumor is that the Xeloxi, previously unknown, are responsible. The Terran Alliance must intervene, bring stability to the system, and deal with this Xeloxi group.[BR][BR]Minor Civilizations have been hurt the most, so a priority should be bringing them under Alliance influence. Once they're secure and the Xeloxi's stream of ill-gotten resources is cut off, the Xeloxi can be dealt with.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_AllianceAscendant_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>When provided stability and protection, Minor Civilizations serve as a source of resources. Settling near and keeping them under Alliance influence will give a distinct advantage over the unscrupulous Xeloxi.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_AllianceAscendant_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Ascendant Protectors</String>
    </StringTable>

    <!--Star System-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_System_Name</Label>
        <String>Leathon System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_System_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Leathon system has a class 28 planet perfect for a human colony, making it the ideal location to establish a base.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_Star_Name</Label>
        <String>Leathon</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_Homeworld_Name</Label>
        <String>Leathon Prime</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_DeadPlanet1_Name</Label>
        <String>Limerithon</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_DeadPlanet2_Name</Label>
        <String>Coth</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_DeadPlanet3_Name</Label>
        <String>Ennithel</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_HabbitalPlanet1_Name</Label>
        <String>Mallithon</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Terran_AllianceAscendant_HabbitalPlanet2_Name</Label>
        <String>Banthel</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>