<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">

<StringTable>
  <Label>Event_SmugglersTreasure_0x745_Name</Label>
  <String>Smuggler's Hideout Treasure</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
  <Label>Event_SmugglersTreasure_0x745_Desc</Label>
  <String>Our flagship has stumbled upon an abandoned smuggler's hideout, brimming with a treasure trove of riches. The smuggler is nowhere to be seen. We now face a moral dilemma: should we seize this unexpected bounty or respect the unwritten rules of ownership?</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
  <Label>Event_SmugglersTreasure_0x745_Choice_Take_Desc</Label>
  <String>Claim the Treasure</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
  <Label>Event_SmugglersTreasure_0x745_Choice_Take_Details</Label>
  <String>Taking the treasure could significantly boost our resources, providing a much-needed advantage. However, this action might attract unwanted attention and could tarnish our reputation among other factions.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
  <Label>Event_SmugglersTreasure_0x745_Choice_Leave_Desc</Label>
  <String>Leave the Treasure Untouched</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
  <Label>Event_SmugglersTreasure_0x745_Choice_Leave_Details</Label>
  <String>Respecting the principle of ownership, we choose to leave the treasure untouched. This may uphold our moral and ethical standards, but we miss out on a potentially significant opportunity to enhance our resources.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SmuglersRevenge_0xC3B1_Name</Label>
    <String>Smuggler's Revenge</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SmuglersRevenge_0xC3B1_Dec</Label>
    <String>The smuggler, whose treasure we previously encountered, has returned to seek revenge. Enraged by our actions, they have launched a surprise attack against us with a fleet of ships in our territory. We must prepare to face the consequences of our earlier decision.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SmuglersRevenge_Choice_1_0xC3B1_Name</Label>
    <String>Defend Against the Attack</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SmuglersRevenge_Choice_1_0xC3B1_Dec</Label>
    <String>It's time to face the smuggler's wrath. We must deploy our defenses and repel their attack. This encounter serves as a harsh reminder that our actions, even in the depths of space, can have unexpected and dangerous repercussions.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AdvancedShieldTechDiscovery_0xB52_Name</Label>
    <String>New Shield Technology Discovered</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AdvancedShieldTechDiscovery_0xB52_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our flagship has recovered the schematics of a groundbreaking shield technology. This new component, when equipped, promises to add an additional layer of shields to every ship in our fleet, capable of absorbing the first hit from any attack.[BR][BR]Of course, it begs the question, who made this?</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AdvancedShieldTechDiscovery_Choice_Implement_Desc</Label>
    <String>We will keep this ship component in mind for future ship designs.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AdvancedShieldTechDiscovery_Choice_Implement_Details</Label>
    <String>Implementing this technology will provide our fleet with a significant defensive advantage. While it may not withstand sustained assaults, this additional shielding could be the difference in surviving initial enemy strikes, giving us a critical edge in battle.[BR][BR]It will be available in the ship designer.</String>
  </StringTable>
  

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AIFindings_0xA3B2_Name</Label>
    <String>Discovery of AI Planetary Monitor Plans</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AIFindings_0xA3B2_Desc</Label>
    <String>Your flagship has come across ancient plans for a semi-sentient AI designed to monitor and reduce crime on planets.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AIFindings_Choice_Use_Desc</Label>
    <String>Implement the AI Planetary Monitor to reduce crime on a selected planet.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AIFindings_Choice_Use_Details</Label>
    <String>By implementing these AI plans, we can significantly reduce crime rates, leading to a safer and more productive colony.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AIFindings_Choice_Sell_Desc</Label>
    <String>Sell the plans for a substantial amount of credits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AIFindings_Choice_Extract_Desc</Label>
    <String>Extract resources from the discovery instead of using the plans.</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_0x9D5_Name</Label>
    <String>Discovery of Core Tap Plans</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_0x9D5_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our fleet has uncovered abandoned plans and a unique power source for a Core Tap, a device capable of harnessing the energy of a planet's core. This find presents us with several lucrative options.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_Choice_Build_Desc</Label>
    <String>Secure the plans.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_Choice_Build_Details</Label>
    <String>Using the plans and power source, we can build a Core Tap on our core worlds, greatly enhancing our production capabilities. This advanced technology could give us a significant advantage but may also carry unknown risks.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_Choice_Sell_Desc</Label>
    <String>Sell the Plans and Power Source</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_Choice_Sell_Details</Label>
    <String>By selling the plans and power source, we could make a substantial profit immediately. This option provides a financial boost but forfeits the opportunity to potentially revolutionize our energy infrastructure.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_Choice_Extract_Desc</Label>
    <String>Extract Resources from the Power Source</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CoreTapDiscovery_Choice_Extract_Details</Label>
    <String>Extracting the raw resources from the unique power source could yield valuable materials for our current projects, offering an immediate practical benefit but losing the potential of the Core Tap technology.</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Name</Label>
    <String>Ancient Library Satellite Discovered</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our flagship has stumbled upon a derelict satellite, an ancient library filled with unknown knowledge. Its origins and contents are a mystery, and it presents a unique opportunity to uncover lost secrets or technological advancements.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Choice_Study_Desc</Label>
    <String>Conduct a Detailed Study</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Choice_Study_Details</Label>
    <String>By choosing to study the satellite, we can unlock ancient knowledge and giving us an immediate research boost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Choice_Use_Desc</Label>
    <String>Sell the Satellite for Immediate Benefits</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Choice_Use_Details</Label>
    <String>Opting to sell the satellite will bring us much needed hard currency.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Choice_Extract_Desc</Label>
    <String>Extract the resources from the satellite</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientLibrarySatellite_0xB3E_Choice_Extract_Details</Label>
    <String>Extracting the resources from the satellite will give us some Precursor Nanites which may prove useful.</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Name</Label>
    <String>Encounter with the Sleeper Ship</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our flagship has encountered a mysterious sleeper ship drifting through space. [BR][BR]Its chambers are filled with alien passengers in cryogenic slumber, on a course set for the deep core of the galaxy. The origin and purpose of their journey remain unknown.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Choice_1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Allow the Ship to Continue Its Journey</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Choice_1_Details</Label>
    <String>Respecting the sleeper ship's voyage, we choose to let it continue on its path to the galaxy's core. This decision upholds the sanctity of their mission, whatever it may be, but leaves us with unanswered questions about their origins and destination.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Choice_2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Terminate the Passengers and Salvage the Ship</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Choice_2_Details</Label>
    <String>Choosing to terminate the alien passengers for the sake of salvaging any advanced technology on the sleeper ship is a drastic and morally questionable decision. While it may yield technological gains, it comes with the heavy burden of ending countless alien lives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Choice_3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Awaken the Passengers and Initiate Contact</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SleeperShip_0x7A4_Choice_3_Details</Label>
    <String>Waking up the alien passengers to initiate contact could provide valuable insights into their culture and technology. However, this decision carries risks, as their reaction to being awakened prematurely and confronted by an unknown species is unpredictable.  You gain a colony ship</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  

</StringTableList>
