<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_DerelictMiningDrone_Name</Label>
        <String>Derelict Mining Drone</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_DerelictMiningDrone_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our flagship finds a derelict mining drone, drifting aimlessly in space. The drone appears to be from an advanced civilization and is still functional. Your engineers manage to reprogram and repair the drone. Upon confirmation, the drone is added your fleet, providing increased mining capabilities and efficiency for resource gathering.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_DerelictMiningDrone_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Reprogram the drone to enhance general resource gathering capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_DerelictMiningDrone_Equality_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Reprogram the drone to focus on gathering Durantium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_CelestialArtExhibition_Name</Label>
        <String>Celestial Art Exhibition</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_CelestialArtExhibition_Desc</Label>
        <String>Our flagship encounters an awe-inspiring celestial phenomenon that seems to be a form of cosmic art created by an unknown species. The vivid display of colors and patterns has a profound impact on the crew and sparks a wave of creativity throughout the civilization. Upon confirmation, your civilization gains a one-time culture boost, which could help with diplomacy and influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_CelestialArtExhibition_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Embrace the cosmic inspiration giving our worlds additional influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedResearchOutpost_Name</Label>
        <String>Abandoned Research Outpost</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedResearchOutpost_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship has discovered an abandoned research outpost in deep space. The outpost appears to have been deserted for quite some time, but the advanced technology inside is still in working condition.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedResearchOutpost_Investigate_Name</Label>
        <String>Investigate the outpost and retrieve the valuable scientific data.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_ArtifactJoyOrResource_Name</Label>
        <String>Artifact of Joy and Resources</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_ArtifactJoyOrResource_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship discovers an ancient artifact, a mysterious object imbued with immense power. This artifact can either be harnessed to provide a massive energy spike for our Shipyards or used to generate an aura of euphoria on a target planet, uplifting the mood of its inhabitants and providing a temporary boost to productivity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_ArtifactJoyOrResource_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Channel the artifact's energy to temporarily enhance manufacturing on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_ArtifactJoyOrResource_Equality_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Secure the artifact in the vault for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PrecursorArtifactCache_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Artifact Cache</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PrecursorArtifactCache_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship locates a hidden cache of Precursor artifacts, left behind by the ancient civilization. These artifacts are not only valuable but also hold clues to the advanced technologies of the Precursors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PrecursorArtifactCache_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Extract resources from the artifacts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PrecursorArtifactCache_Equality_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Add the artifact into the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_MysteriousEnergySource_Name</Label>
        <String>Mysterious Energy Source</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_MysteriousEnergySource_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship detects an unusual energy signature coming from a nearby asteroid. Upon investigation, the crew finds a stable and potent energy source that can be harnessed to enhanced the manufacturing of our planets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_MysteriousEnergySource_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Utilize the energy source to temporarily increase manufacturing on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostCargoContainer_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo Container</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostCargoContainer_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship comes across a drifting cargo container, seemingly abandoned and adrift in space for years. The container is filled with valuable trade goods and rare resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_LostCargoContainer_Bonus_Stat_0X56CD</Label>
        <String>Lost cargo booty.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostCargoContainer_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Acquire the valuable goods to boost your economy for many months.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientStarMap_Name</Label>
        <String>Ancient Star Map</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientStarMap_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship discovers an ancient star map etched into the surface of a seemingly insignificant moon. The map reveals that there is a very valuable relatively close to our current location.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientStarMap_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Seek out the high quality planet in a nearby star system.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AutomatedRepairStation_Name</Label>
        <String>Automated Repair Station</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AutomatedRepairStation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship encounters an automated repair station left behind by a long-lost civilization. Despite its age, the station is still operational and capable of repairing and upgrading ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AutomatedRepairStation_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Receive free repairs and a one-time upgrade to your starship's weapons, defenses, or engines, improving its combat or exploration capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_EnigmaticMonolith_Name</Label>
        <String>Enigmatic Monolith</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_EnigmaticMonolith_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship discovers an enigmatic monolith floating in space, emitting a mysterious energy that seems to resonate with the crew's thoughts. Studying the monolith provides a temporary boost to the crew's problem-solving abilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_EnigmaticMonolith_Pragmatism_Bonus_Name</Label>
        <String>Gain a one-time burst of knowledge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostExplorersLog_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Explorer's Log</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostExplorersLog_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our flagship finds the remains of a long-lost explorer's vessel, along with a detailed log of their discoveries. This log contains invaluable information on various planets, anomalies, and points of interest throughout the galaxy. Upon confirmation, your civilization finds a previously unknown world available to be settled on.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostExplorersLog_Pragmatism_Name</Label>
        <String>Use the log to chart new paths.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_GhostFleet_Equality_Name</Label>
        <String>Salvage resources from the wreckage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_WreckageOfTheTitan_Name</Label>
        <String>Wreckage of the Titan</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_WreckageOfTheTitan_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship discovers that the artifact contains a key that summons the remains of a massive battlecruiser, the Titan, once the flagship of an ancient and powerful armada.  While too ancient to use directly, our scientists are quick to track down potentially useful knowledge from it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_WreckageOfTheTitan_Pragmatism_Name</Label>
        <String>Discover new technologies from wreckage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_WreckageOfTheTitan_Equality_Name</Label>
        <String>Salvage and recruit a mercenary ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact_Name</Label>
        <String>Mapping Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact_Dec</Label>
        <String>During the thorough analysis of the artifact, your research team has unearthed an astonishing discovery - it is a reservoir of colossal energy. The scientists in your crew are confident that they can channel this raw power to propel our civilization forward. Yet, a dissenting perspective suggests that this energy could be utilized as a cosmic key, opening up uncharted dimensions of the cosmos, and revealing secrets of space hitherto unknown.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact_Choice_1</Label>
        <String>Harvest the artifact's energy and gain a valuable resource.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact_Choice_2_0x43b</Label>
        <String>Store the artifact in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact2_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ancient Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your fleet stumbles upon an ancient artifact floating in the depths of space. Its origin is unknown. It is made of the strange metal our scientists call Durantium. The purpose of this artifact is lost to time but we can still make use of its raw materials.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact2_Choice_1</Label>
        <String>Harvest the artifact's power and gain a valuable resource.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact2_Choice_2</Label>
        <String>Use the artifact's power to create a new world for all to share.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact3_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ancient Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact3_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship arrives at the strange artifact. What it once did can only be known to the ancient Precursors. However, within the depths of it is a container holding valuable Antimatter. Your crew carefully remove the Antimatter and put it into storage for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact3_Choice_1</Label>
        <String>Extract the energy from the artifact and convert it into valuable Antimatter for our use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AncientArtifact3_Choice_2</Label>
        <String>Release the ancient civilization, known as The Ecliptae, from the artifact and allow them to live among the stars once again.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SpaceMonsterCage_Name_0X1F4DE</Label>
        <String>Encounter with the Monstrous Cage</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SpaceMonsterCage_Desc_0X1F4DE</Label>
        <String>Our ship has stumbled upon a peculiar artifact adrift in the cold void of space. It appears to be a cage, but not for any ordinary creature. This containment unit was designed for something... monstrous. We have two clear options: keep the artifact and possibly unleash the beast at a strategic moment, or study the cage's advanced technology, risking the inadvertent release of the captive creature.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SpaceMonsterCage_Keep_Name_0X1F4DE</Label>
        <String>Keep the artifact. This monster might serve a purpose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SpaceMonsterCage_Keep_Desc_0X1F4DE</Label>
        <String>Take the cage into our possession, ready to release the monster when needed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SpaceMonsterCage_Experiment_Name_0X1F4DE</Label>
        <String>Study the cage's technology. We can deal with the monster.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SpaceMonsterCage_Experiment_Desc_0X1F4DE</Label>
        <String>Dissect the artifact for its advanced technology, advancing our own scientific knowledge in the current research topic. This may haunt us later.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorIntegrityDevice_Name_0X1F5C3</Label>
        <String>Unearthed Arnorian Integrity Device</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorIntegrityDevice_Desc_0X1F5C3</Label>
        <String>An intriguing discovery has been made - a device from the long-gone Arnor civilization. Its structure suggests it might be used to enhance the structural integrity of our fleet. Alternatively, its exotic materials could fetch a good price on the interstellar market.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorIntegrityDevice_Bonus_Name_0X1F5C3</Label>
        <String>Preserve and Utilize</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorIntegrityDevice_Bonus_Desc_0X1F5C3</Label>
        <String>Add the artifact to our vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorIntegrityDevice_Disassemble_Name_0X1F5C3</Label>
        <String>Dismantle and Trade</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorIntegrityDevice_Disassemble_Effect_Desc_0X1F5C3</Label>
        <String>Disassemble the artifact and sell the resulting materials on the market for a substantial amount of credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorTerraformer_Name_0X1F4E0</Label>
        <String>Precursor Terraforming Device</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorTerraformer_Desc_0X1F4E0</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has discovered an artifact of the ancient Precursors. It appears to be a device of terraforming capabilities, seemingly able to upgrade a planet's class by an entire level. We could store it for future use or dismantle it to obtain valuable resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorTerraformer_Bonus_Name_0X1F4E0</Label>
        <String>Secure the Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorTerraformer_Bonus_Desc_0X1F4E0</Label>
        <String>Store the artifact in our vault for potential future terraforming purposes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorTerraformer_Disassemble_Name_0X1F4E0</Label>
        <String>Harvest its Resources</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorTerraformer_Disassemble_Effect_Desc_0X1F4E0</Label>
        <String>Dismantle the artifact and sell the extracted resources on the interstellar market.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordWeapon_Name_0X1F5E0</Label>
        <String>The Dread Lord's Harbinger</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordWeapon_Desc_0X1F5E0</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has discovered an artifact, suspected to be of Dread Lord origin. It's a weapon of terrifying power, able to instantly damage an entire enemy fleet. We must decide whether to preserve it for potential usage or dismantle it for valuable resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordWeapon_Bonus_Name_0X1F5E0</Label>
        <String>Secure the weapon artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordWeapon_Bonus_Desc_0X1F5E0</Label>
        <String>Keep the artifact in our vault, harnessing its potential to damage enemy fleets when needed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordWeapon_Disassemble_Name_0X1F5E0</Label>
        <String>Dismantle for resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordWeapon_Disassemble_Effect_Desc_0X1F5E0</Label>
        <String>Disassemble the weapon and sell the obtained resources on the galactic market.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorLifeDevice_Name_0X1F6FB</Label>
        <String>Arnor's Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorLifeDevice_Desc_0X1F6FB</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has stumbled upon an artifact of the ancient Arnor civilization. It is a device with the stunning capability to transform lifeless worlds into habitable ones. Should we preserve it or harvest it for parts?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorLifeDevice_Bonus_Name_0X1F6FB</Label>
        <String>Preserve the past.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorLifeDevice_Bonus_Desc_0X1F6FB</Label>
        <String>Take the artifact. Store it in our vaults. We may find a world worthy of its power.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorLifeDevice_Disassemble_Name_0X1F6FB</Label>
        <String>Profit from the past.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArnorLifeDevice_Disassemble_Effect_Desc_0X1F6FB</Label>
        <String>Break down the artifact and sell its components. Let's profit from this ancient technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_NaniteWarship_Name_0X1F7AC</Label>
        <String>The Nanite Warship Maker</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_NaniteWarship_Desc_0X1F7AC</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has discovered an artifact from an unknown, long-gone civilization. Inside, we found sophisticated Nanites capable of assembling a powerful, automated warship. Do we harness this power, or do we disassemble it for profit?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_NaniteWarship_Bonus_Name_0X1F7AC</Label>
        <String>Command a warship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_NaniteWarship_Bonus_Desc_0X1F7AC</Label>
        <String>Preserve the artifact. The potential of commanding an ancient warship could shift the balance of power in our favor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_NaniteWarship_Disassemble_Name_0X1F7AC</Label>
        <String>Harvest for resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_NaniteWarship_Disassemble_Effect_Desc_0X1F7AC</Label>
        <String>Disassemble the artifact and sell its Nanite components. Such advanced technology could fetch a high price on the interstellar market.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_Name_0x4A2B</Label>
        <String>A lost but now found Survey Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_Dec_0x4A2B</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has stumbled upon a lost cargo container drifting through space. It's marked with several unfamiliar alien symbols and we suspect it might contain some valuable contents. Inside, we find a survey module, one of the rarest items we know of. Survey modules are what make a flagship a "Flagship" in that they contain a vast array of specialized tools and sensors for dealing with the anomalies that litter the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_Choice1_Name_0x4A2B</Label>
        <String>Take the survey module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_Choice1_Dec_0x4A2B</Label>
        <String>This component will be available at our shipyard when we design a new survey ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_Choice2_Name_0x4A2B</Label>
        <String>Mine it for resources, who knows what's inside.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_Choice3_Name_0x4A2B</Label>
        <String>Sell the whole mystery box. Let someone else deal with it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_0x4A2C_Name</Label>
        <String>The Cosmic Needler</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_0x4A2C_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has stumbled across a curious sight. A drifting Precursor cargo container. An intense sense of excitement fills the bridge as we approach. Initial scans indicate the container houses an advanced particle beam that is remarkably small even if not particularly powerful. The component is filled with a high concentration of Promethium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_0x4A2C_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Send the component to our shipyards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_0x4A2C_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>This component will be available for our next flagship design. The engineers are already brimming with ideas.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_0x4A2C_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Extract the Promethium. We could always use more resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FoundCargoContainer_0x4A2C_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the lot on the Galactic Market. In hard credits we trust!</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Name</Label>
        <String>The Enigma of Hyperspace</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our flagship has detected an ancient cargo container, drifting aimlessly in the void. This appears to be a relic from the Precursor Wars! Inside we find a fully intact Arnorian Drive system, a ship component that is remarkably small for its size. It could be attached to a ship to increase its speed. Alternatively, we could harvest a significant quantity of Thulium from it or sell it to the highest bidder. What are your orders?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Send the Precursor drive back home.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>This drive will be available when we design a new ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Harvest it for valuable resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Gain 2 Thulium for use in various advanced technologies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the artifact on the Galactic Market.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RareArtifact_0x9F8D_Choice3_Dec</Label>
        <String>Earn 600 credits from interested buyers across the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Name</Label>
        <String>The Phantom Accelerator</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Dec</Label>
        <String>While cruising through the void, your ship picks up an unexpected signal - a lost cargo container floating aimlessly. Upon closer inspection, it contains a Slipstream Accelerator, an essential component for FTL travel! It's like finding a Ferrari engine at a yard sale.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Awesome. We can use this on one of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Put this in our Artifact Vault to be used on one of our fleets later.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Let's dismantle it for some precious Elerium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Elerium is a rare and valuable resource. It might not be as exciting as a Slipstream Accelerator but Elerium is pretty nice too.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell it for a good sum of credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_AbandonedSlipstreamAccelerator_0x5F2C_Choice3_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's an old saying that one man's space trash is another man's space treasure.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_Name_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo - Survey Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_Dec_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>Your ship has stumbled upon a cargo hold lost in the vastness of space. It contains an advanced Survey Module, possibly from an ancient civilization. This module could be used to give an existing ship the ability to investigate anomalies. Alternatively, it can be broken down into valuable antimatter or sold for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_Store_Name_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>Store the survey module in our vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_Store_Desc_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>We will be able to make an existing ship able to survey anomalies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_BreakDown_Name_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>Break down the survey module for its components.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_Sell_Name_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>Sell the survey module for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SurveyModule_Sell_Desc_0X2D5E</Label>
        <String>Convert the survey module into a substantial amount of credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnergyWeapon_0x5C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Energy Weapon Discovery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnergyWeapon_0x5C2B_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container floating in space. Upon inspection, a mysterious energy weapon is found inside. The weapon appears to be of unknown origin and technology, with the potential to be a powerful asset.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EnergyWeapon_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the energy weapon in the vault for future use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EnergyWeapon_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>You decide to store the energy weapon in your vault for future use. This mysterious device could prove to be a game-changer in your civilization's defense or offense strategies. Or not. In either event you can install it on one of your ships and find out.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnergyWeapon_0x5C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the energy weapon for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostMissileWeapon_0x5C2A_Name</Label>
        <String>Mysterious Missile Cache</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostMissileWeapon_0x5C2A_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container floating in space. Upon inspection, it contains an advanced missile weapon prototype. The device is unlike anything seen before, and its origin remains a mystery. It could be used to add missile weapons to one of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MissileWeapon_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the missile weapon in our vault for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MissileWeapon_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Keep the advanced missile weapon prototype in our vault allowing it to be installed on a ship later.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostMissileWeapon_0x5C2A_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the missile weapon for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostKineticWeapon_0x5C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Kinetic Weapon</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostKineticWeapon_0x5C2B_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a mysterious cargo container floating in space. Upon inspection, it contains an advanced kinetic weapon of unknown origin. It is some sort of self-replicating mass-driver. It could be a valuable addition to your arsenal or sold for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KineticWeapon_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the weapon in our vault for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KineticWeapon_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>You decide to keep the weapon, storing it in your vault for future use. Its advanced technology may help one of your ships survive a battle. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostKineticWeapon_0x5C2B_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the weapon for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_TacticalThrusterUpgrade_0x5E3C_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo: Tactical Thruster Upgrade</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_TacticalThrusterUpgrade_0x5E3C_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a drifting cargo container in deep space. Upon inspection, it contains a highly advanced tactical thruster upgrade device, seemingly lost by another civilization. This thruster could be added to one of our ships making it be able to get into firing range faster, a possibly critical advantage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TacticalThrusterUpgrade_Store_Name_0X3F7A</Label>
        <String>Store the device in the vault for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TacticalThrusterUpgrade_Store_Desc_0X3F7A</Label>
        <String>You decide to secure the newly discovered tactical thruster upgrade device in your vault, for future research and potential implementation into your fleet. This could provide a significant advantage over your adversaries in future conflicts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_TacticalThrusterUpgrade_0x5E3C_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the device for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEngineUpgradeModule_0x5C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Engine Upgrade Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEngineUpgradeModule_0x5C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship's captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container floating in space. Upon investigation, it appears to contain a rare and valuable engine upgrade module that can increase a ship's speed through Hyperspace. The captain awaits your orders on how to proceed with this discovery.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EngineUpgradeModule_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the module in our vault for future use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EngineUpgradeModule_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Bring the engine upgrade module back to our civilization's vault for safekeeping and potential future use. Add to one of your ships to increase its speed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEngineUpgradeModule_0x5C2B_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the module for credits</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPollutionRemoverModule_0x4C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Atmospheric Filter</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPollutionRemoverModule_0x4C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a mysterious cargo container floating in the void. Upon inspection, it contains an advanced Pollution Remover Module of unknown origin. It filters out the pollutants in the atmosphere. The deciphered writing is from the container indicates that it was 'too expensive' and was being returned. This device could be a valuable asset in maintaining planetary ecosystems or sold for a tidy profit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PollutionRemoverModule_Store_Name_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the module in the vault for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PollutionRemoverModule_Store_Desc_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Secure the Pollution Remover Module in your vault, allowing it to be used on one of our various despoiled worlds. You, obviously being the despoiler in this scenario. This device could help give the illusion you care about the ecosystems of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPollutionRemoverModule_0x4C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell out for money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostArmorModule_0x7C3D_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Armor Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostArmorModule_0x7C3D_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container drifting in space. Inside, they found a mysterious and advanced armor module that can be applied to a starship. It seems to be of great value, but its true potential is yet to be unlocked.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArmorModule_Store_Name_0X5A7F</Label>
        <String>Store the Armor Module in our vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArmorModule_Store_Desc_0X5A7F</Label>
        <String>Store the armor module in your vault and keep it for future use. Its potential may prove invaluable in future engagements, providing increased protection to a target ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostArmorModule_0x7C3D_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the Armor Module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPlanetaryBroadcaster_0x4C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Planetary Broadcaster</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPlanetaryBroadcaster_0x4C2B_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container floating in space. Upon further inspection, it appears to contain an ancient, yet functional Planetary Broadcaster device. The device is intended to send out a one-time burst of entertainment related information across a wide area. If it were used on a planet, it would greatly increase the planet's influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PlanetaryBroadcaster_Store_Name_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the Planetary Broadcaster in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PlanetaryBroadcaster_Store_Desc_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Deciding to keep the device, you store the planetary broadcaster in your vault for future use. Apply it to a planet that is struggling against foreign influence for best results.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPlanetaryBroadcaster_0x4C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the Planetary Broadcaster for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPlanetaryCultureModule_0x4C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Planetary Culture Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPlanetaryCultureModule_0x4C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a mysterious cargo container floating in space. Upon opening it, the crew finds an ancient device that upon study appears to have a vast catalog of the cultural significance of every planet in the galaxy. This is a remarkable treasure. Unfortunately, the device is obviously very old and likely only able to be used once. It could be used to increase the cultural value of any planet we choose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PlanetaryCultureModule_Store_Name_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the Planetary Culture Module for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PlanetaryCultureModule_Store_Desc_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Deciding to keep the Planetary Culture Module for your civilization, you store it in your vault. Its potential to shape the cultural identity of entire planets could prove to be a valuable asset in your future endeavors. It will increase the base cultural significance of the planet you choose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPlanetaryCultureModule_0x4C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Dissemble the module and sell the components for money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PlanetaryDefenseModule_0x8F3C_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Planetary Defense Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PlanetaryDefenseModule_0x8F3C_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports discovering a lost cargo container adrift in space. Upon inspection, the container houses an advanced Planetary Defense Module, believed to be from a long-forgotten civilization. This mysterious device could prove invaluable to your empire by increasing a given planet's defense capabilities against invasion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PlanetaryDefenseModule_Store_Name_0X4E7A</Label>
        <String>Store the defense module in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PlanetaryDefenseModule_Store_Desc_0X4E7A</Label>
        <String>Storing this Planetary Defense Module in your vault could provide invaluable protection to your empire's planets in times of conflict. Its advanced technology could potentially prevent a planet from being invaded.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PlanetaryDefenseModule_0x8F3C_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnemyDestablizerModule_0x4C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Enemy Destabilizer Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnemyDestablizerModule_0x4C2B_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container floating in space. This device appears to be able to be quietly slipped into orbit of an enemy planet raising that planet's crime rate. A very devious device indeed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EnemyDestablizerModule_Store_Name_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the Enemy Destabilizer Module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EnemyDestablizerModule_Store_Desc_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Choose to store the Enemy Destabilizer Module in your vault. Crime is bad except when it's happening to people you don't like. This device will increase the crime rate of any planet you choose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnemyDestablizerModule_0x4C2B_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the Enemy Destabilizer Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnemyDefenseSabotageModule_0x4C1B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Enemy Defense Sabotage Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnemyDefenseSabotageModule_0x4C1B_Dec</Label>
        <String>While exploring the far reaches of space, your flagship stumbles upon a mysterious cargo container. Upon opening it, they discover a highly advanced enemy defense sabotage module. This device permanently reduces an enemy planet's ability to defend against invasion by installing trillions of tiny, self-replicating crystalline orbs that damage the planet's air-based defense systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EnemyDefenseSabotageModule_Store_Name_0X2D6F</Label>
        <String>Store the module in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_EnemyDefenseSabotageModule_Store_Desc_0X2D6F</Label>
        <String>Deciding that the module could prove useful in future invasions, you order your crew to store it securely in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostEnemyDefenseSabotageModule_0x4C1B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the module for credits (after taking it apart)</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPropagandizeModule_0x5C2A_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Propagandize Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPropagandizeModule_0x5C2A_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports finding a lost cargo container adrift in space. Upon opening, they discover a sophisticated Propagandize Module capable of swaying enemy citizens' loyalty. The net effect is that it greatly reduces the enemy planet's cultural significance. Will you keep it for future use or sell it for credits?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PropagandizeModule_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the Propagandize Module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PropagandizeModule_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>By keeping the Propagandize Module in your vault, you can use it later to reduce the influence of a target planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostPropagandizeModule_0x5C2A_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Take it apart and sell the pieces for money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PoisonEnemyPlanetModule_0x4C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo: Poisonous Device</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PoisonEnemyPlanetModule_0x4C2B_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your captain reports discovering a lost cargo container in the depths of space. Inside, they found a highly advanced device capable of poisoning an enemy planet's environment. What should be done with this dangerous technology?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PoisonEnemyPlanetModule_Store_Name_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the device in our vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PoisonEnemyPlanetModule_Store_Desc_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>The device is carefully stored in your civilization's vault, where it remains available for potential future use. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PoisonEnemyPlanetModule_0x4C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Take it apart and sell the pieces for money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_PoisonEnemyPlanetModule_0x4C2B_Choice3_Desc</Label>
        <String>Instead of keeping the device, you decide to sell it on the galactic market for a hefty. The buyer remains anonymous, and the device's ultimate destination is unknown. Nonetheless, your civilization's coffers are now filled with valuable currency.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostDepleteResourcesModule_0x5C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Syphoning Resources Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostDepleteResourcesModule_0x5C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>As your flagship approaches an abandoned cargo container, it detects an advanced Deplete Resources Module within. This mysterious device has the power to sap the resources of enemy planets. Will you keep this powerful tool or sell it for credits?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DepleteResourcesModule_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the Deplete Resources Module in the Vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DepleteResourcesModule_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>By storing the Deplete Resources Module in your vault, you gain the ability to use its power in the future. This device can be deployed to drain resources from enemy planets, giving you a strategic advantage in conflicts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostDepleteResourcesModule_0x5C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the Deplete Resources components for money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FriendlyPlanetMineralScanner_0x5C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Mysterious Cargo: Advanced Mineral Scanner</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FriendlyPlanetMineralScanner_0x5C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your captain reports finding a lost cargo container adrift in space. Inside, they discovered an advanced mineral scanner, a device capable of accurately detecting valuable resources on distant planets. It can only be used once but it could still be very valuable. This cutting-edge technology could provide a significant advantage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FriendlyPlanetMineralScanner_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the Mineral Scanner in our vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FriendlyPlanetMineralScanner_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>By storing the advanced mineral scanner in your vault, you can utilize its technology to improve resource detection on our planets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FriendlyPlanetMineralScanner_0x5C2B_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the Mineral Scanner for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FriendlyPlanetTechFinderModule_0x5C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo: Friendly Planet Tech Finder</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FriendlyPlanetTechFinderModule_0x5C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports encountering a lost cargo container floating in space. After careful examination, it appears to be a device made by a long-lost civilization to find Precursor technology on planets. The device is very old and in poor shape, but it could still be valuable even if it can only be used once. Do you wish to store this device in your vault or sell it for credits?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FriendlyPlanetTechFinderModule_Store_Name_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the device in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FriendlyPlanetTechFinderModule_Store_Desc_0X3E6F</Label>
        <String>This device will increase the base Tech rating of a target planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_FriendlyPlanetTechFinderModule_0x5C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the device for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_SummonLeaderModule_0x4C2B_Name</Label>
        <String>Found: Summon Synthetic Leader Device</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_SummonLeaderModule_0x4C2B_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container, floating through the void of space. As your crew investigates, they find a peculiar device inside, emitting a faint yet mesmerizing glow. With a bit of effort, your team realizes that it is an ancient Precursor device for summoning a prototype Yor advisor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SummonLeaderModule_Store_Name_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>Store the device in the vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SummonLeaderModule_Store_Desc_0X2E6F</Label>
        <String>By using this device you will summon an Ancient (but loyal) Yor as a leader you can assign.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_SummonLeaderModule_0x4C2B_Choice3_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the device for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RoboticServantsModule_0x5C2F_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo: Robotic Servants Module</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RoboticServantsModule_0x5C2F_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports the discovery of a lost cargo container floating in space. Upon opening it, they find an advanced Robotic Servants Module - a device capable of significantly improving the efficiency of a planet's workforce. The choice is yours: store it for future use or sell it for credits?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RoboticServantsModule_Store_Name_0X3E7F</Label>
        <String>Store the Robotic Servants Module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RoboticServantsModule_Store_Desc_0X3E7F</Label>
        <String>By storing the Robotic Servants Module in your vault, you can deploy it on one of your planets at a later time, significantly improving workforce efficiency and productivity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RoboticServantsModule_0x5C2F_Choice4_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the Robotic Servants Module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RoboticStarDrone_0x5C3D_Name</Label>
        <String>Encounter with a Robotic Star Drone</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RoboticStarDrone_0x5C3D_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your flagship captain reports discovering a lost cargo container floating in the void. Upon opening, they reveal a mysterious robotic star drone with advanced technological capabilities. When this drone is deployed, it acts as a small but lethal ship in battle. This could prove useful or profitable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RoboticStarDrone_Store_Name_0X3F7C</Label>
        <String>Store the drone in our vault.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RoboticStarDrone_Store_Desc_0X3F7C</Label>
        <String>By storing the drone, you can analyze its advanced technology and integrate it into your fleet, potentially boosting your fleet's capabilities in future engagements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_RoboticStarDrone_0x5C3D_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Sell the drone for credits.</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>