<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_0x522_Name</Label>
        <String>Emerging Rebellion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_0x522_Desc</Label>
        <String>Intelligence reports indicate a growing rebel movement on {PLANETNAME}. There are riots in the streets and massive destruction of property.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Do our best to restore law and order.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>Our security forces will do their best to restore order. But expect high crime for the next several months on {PLANETNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_0x522_Choice_Reassess_Result</Label>
        <String>Rebel movement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Use your central control authority to put down the rebellion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_2_Details</Label>
        <String>Using our reserves of control on {PLANETNAME} we quickly reestablish order.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivWide_Rebellion_0x522_Name</Label>
        <String>Rebellion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivWide_Rebellion_0x522_Desc</Label>
        <String>A wave of rebellion has swept across our civilization. Suppressed voices have now risen in unison, challenging our authority and demanding change. This widespread unrest is the result of our earlier policies and actions. We must decide how to address this crisis.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivWide_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Implement Reforms</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivWide_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>Enacting systemic reforms could pacify the rebellion, showing our willingness to address their concerns. However, it will take several months to calm people down.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivWide_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Use your resources of Control to suppress the Rebellion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivWide_Rebellion_0x522_Choice_2_Details</Label>
        <String>Choosing to suppress the rebellion with force is a decisive action that might quickly quell the unrest. However, this approach could further alienate our citizens and exacerbate tensions, leading to long-term instability and loss of control over our factions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_Name</Label>
        <String>Coup Attempt</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your relentless rule has pushed several of your closest generals to the brink. They have attempted a coup, seeking to overthrow your leadership and install a new regime.  Fortunately, your security was able to thwart the attempt but not before several rebel ships have begun controlling areas of our space.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Crush the Rebellion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_1_Details</Label>
        <String>Deciding to crush the rebellion sends a clear message: you will not tolerate any challenge to your authority. While this may quell the immediate threat, it could instill fear and resentment among your people, potentially leading to more secretive and dangerous forms of resistance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Rebellion_Results</Label>
        <String>Rebellion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_Choice_2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Seek a Peaceful Resolution</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_Choice_2_Details</Label>
        <String>Choosing to negotiate with the rebels is a risky move that could be seen as a sign of weakness. However, it offers a chance to address the underlying issues driving the coup, potentially leading to a more stable and unified rule in the long term, albeit at the cost of some immediate control.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_Choice_3_Desc</Label>
        <String>Murder the families of the leaders</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Attempted_Coup_0xA34_Choice_3_Details</Label>
        <String>There is only one way to prevent this sort of thing from happening in the future.  Round up the Coup leaders families and kill them. Make sure to record it to show the leaders and anyone else what happens to those who disobey.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA42_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic Alien Lazy Genius Fever</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA42_Desc</Label>
        <String>A bizarre fever, contracted from recently discovered exotic alien life that you previously supported monetizing has swept our homeworld. While physically debilitating, causing extreme lethargy, it inexplicably boosts cognitive abilities, turning our people into temporary geniuses. We must decide how to navigate this peculiar epidemic.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA42_Choice_1_Desc</Label>
        <String>We will monitor the situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA42_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>For the next year, people on {PLANETNAME} will be less diligent but far more intelligent..</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA42_Choice_1_Result</Label>
        <String>Lazy Genius Fever.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA43_Name</Label>
        <String>Systemic Processing Overload</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA43_Desc</Label>
        <String>An unexpected systemic anomaly has affected our population.  Something in the exotic fauna we have been distributing is affecting our inorganic systems.[BR][BR] While processing speeds and cognitive functions have significantly increased, mobility systems are severely impaired. This presents a unique challenge: how do we manage this new state of heightened intelligence but limited physical capability?</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Homeworld_Pathogen_0xCA43_Choice_1_Result</Label>
        <String>System overload</String>
    </StringTable>
    

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RogueRobotsCrisis_0xE45_Name</Label>
        <String>Rogue Robot Uprising</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RogueRobotsCrisis_0xE45_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a catastrophic turn of events that should suprrise no one, the robots that we previously used to help bolster our labor shortages have risen up.  Some of them have remained loyal but others have taken to space and surrounded our shipsyards.  They want our blood or whatever is the nearest equivalent.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RogueRobotsCrisis_Choice_Shutdown_Desc</Label>
        <String>Prepare for battle.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RogueRobotsCrisis_Choice_Shutdown_Details</Label>
        <String>They are using Sentinel designs. Look for them near our shipyards.</String>
      </StringTable>

      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingSuccess_0xF12_Name</Label>
        <String>Homeworld Terraforming Triumph</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingSuccess_0xF12_Desc</Label>
        <String>Our cautious and meticulous approach to terraforming has paid off. A new section of our homeworld has been successfully terraformed, expanding our usable land and opening up new possibilities for development and prosperity.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingSuccess_Choice_Celebrate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Great work!</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingSuccess_Choice_Celebrate_Details</Label>
        <String>Our homeworld has gained an extra usable tile.</String>
      </StringTable>

      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialGratitudeTransfer_0x9F1_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Wealth Transfer</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialGratitudeTransfer_0x9F1_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a remarkable display of gratitude, our colonies have banded together to provide a significant one-time wealth transfer to the homeworld. This generous act is in appreciation of the greater autonomy and support they have received from us.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialGratitudeTransfer_Choice_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Graciously Accept the Gesture</String>
      </StringTable>

      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SentientFloraHarmony_0xH5A_Name</Label>
        <String>Harmony with Sentient Flora</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SentientFloraHarmony_0xH5A_Desc</Label>
        <String>Our respectful approach to the sentient plants on {PLANETNAME}. has led to a significant breakthrough in our understanding and cooperation with them.  This has lead to a vast increase in the number of them on the planet who willingly share their wisdom with us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SentientFloraHarmony_Choice_Celebrate_Desc</Label>
        <String>This is a great day.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SentientFloraHarmony_Choice_Celebrate_Details</Label>
        <String>There are now sentient plants available on this world along with more space for you to both live in harmony.</String>
    </StringTable>

      
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MorePowerFleetIncreaseMoves_Name</Label>
        <String>Emergency Speed</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MorePowerFleetIncreaseMoves_Dec</Label>
        <String>Orders fleet to go beyond their maximum rated speed.</String>
    </StringTable>

          
    <StringTable>
        <Label>StarbaseModulesPower_Name</Label>
        <String>Rush Starbase Modules</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>StarbaseModulesPower_Dec</Label>
        <String>Use your vast power to impel private industry to deliver you some new modules for use at Starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>

    </StringTableList>  