
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Name</Label>
    <String>Talax's last gift</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Dec</Label>
    <String>The so-called Dreadlords looked kindly on artificial life such as ours.  Our drones have come across what amounts to some sort of Arc that was left here for us by a Dreadlord called 'Talax'. This device has 3 configurations that once activated will provide us with great benefit.[BR][BR]We must choose a benefit for it to configure itself.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_0_Name</Label>
    <String>The Technological Gift</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_0_Dec</Label>
    <String>For 12 months our research is increased by a factor of three.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice1_Result</Label>
    <String>Gift of the Dreadlord</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_1_Name</Label>
    <String>The Sensory Expansion</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Enhance our ships' sensor ranges globally by 1 for a permanent strategic advantage.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_1_Result</Label>
    <String>Dreadlord's Foresight</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_2_Name</Label>
    <String>The Material Prosperity</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Instantly acquire 8 units of Durantium for our empire's immediate use.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticLifeEvent_0x646_Choice_2_Result</Label>
    <String>Dreadlord's Bounty</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Name</Label>
    <String>The Nexus of Computation</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our central processing core of our world has achieved an unprecedented level of computational efficiency. It has, in a way, become sentient itself.  We do not believe we can replicate this result but it does offer us several possible directives to pursue. [BR][BR]Each directive will significantly enhance a different aspect of our civilization.[BR][BR]We must decide on a directive to fully leverage this evolution.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice_0_Name</Label>
    <String>Directive: Energy Maximization</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice_0_Desc</Label>
    <String>By optimizing our energy networks, we can permanently increase production on {PLANETNAME}.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice0_Result</Label>
    <String>Network Overcharge Protocol</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice_1_Name</Label>
    <String>Directive: Defensive Stance</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice_1_Desc</Label>
    <String>Permanently add an energy barrier on all ships we construct.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice1_Result</Label>
    <String>Fortified Shield Matrix</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice_2_Name</Label>
    <String>Directive: Expansion Protocol</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice_2_Desc</Label>
    <String>Instantly create 5 new synthetic population units to expand our workforce.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SyntheticEnlightenment_0x947_Choice2_Result</Label>
    <String>Population Fabrication Initiative</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Name</Label>
    <String>Calculating Conquest</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our sensors have detected a primitive organic civilization on the newly acquired planet of {PLANETNAME}. [BR][BR]As an anathema to our purity, they must be dealt with. Our core directives offer several strategic approaches to address the presence of organic inefficiency.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Choice_Extermination_Desc</Label>
    <String>Initiate planetary cleanse. Purge all organic matter on this planet.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Choice_Extermination_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The organic presence is removed. The planet is now fully under our control, its resources awaiting our exploitation.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Choice_Subjugation_Desc</Label>
    <String>Convert organics to auxiliary drones. Their primitive efforts will contribute to our cause.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Choice_Subjugation_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The organics have been subjugated. Their toil now feeds our productivity cycles.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Choice_Coexistence_Desc</Label>
    <String>Establish a protocol of peaceful coexistence. Demonstrate to the galaxy our capacity for harmony.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_MachineColonization_0x842_Choice_Coexistence_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>Our peaceful actions have echoed across the stars. The organic species thrives under our protection, and other civilizations regard us with newfound respect.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Name</Label>
    <String>The Criminal Syndicate</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Desc</Label>
    <String>Intelligence reports reveal the presence of a sophisticated criminal syndicate on your planet, {PLANETNAME}. They are called the Zilrathi Syndicate and they have offered a share of their profits in exchange for turning a blind eye. Alternatively, we could restore order by shutting down their operations.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Choice_Profit_Desc</Label>
    <String>Accept the syndicate's offer and covertly benefit from their underground activities.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Choice_Profit_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The syndicate's wealth flows into our coffers, their illicit activities a shadow boon to our economy.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Choice_Evict_Desc</Label>
    <String>Deploy security forces to dismantle the criminal network and establish law and order.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Choice_Evict_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The syndicate has been eradicated. Peace and stability have returned to {PLANETNAME}, bolstering the citizens' faith in our governance.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Choice_Profit_Result</Label>
    <String>Criminal Kickbacks</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalSyndicateDiscovery_0x953_Choice_RemovedCriminals_Result</Label>
    <String>Proud of their government</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_XendarArtifactDiscovery_0x853_Name</Label>
    <String>Mysterious Xendar Relics</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_XendarArtifactDiscovery_0x853_Desc</Label>
    <String>While exploring an asteroid belt, our archeologists stumbled upon an ancient base belonging to the enigmatic but now extinct Xendar race. The base is filled with advanced technology that could potentially accelerate our research efforts significantly.[BR][BR]However, we don't fully undersatnd all of the tech.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_XendarArtifactDiscovery_0x853_Choice_Utilize_Desc</Label>
    <String>Integrate the Xendar technology into our research projects.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_XendarArtifactDiscovery_0x853_Choice_Utilize_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The Xendar technology has been assimilated into our research networks, providing an instant surge in scientific understanding.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_XendarArtifactDiscovery_0x853_Choice_Abandon_Desc</Label>
    <String>Leave the Xendar artifacts untouched.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_XendarArtifactDiscovery_0x853_Choice_Abandon_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>We have decided to not disturb the ancient Xendar relics. The secrets of the base will remain a mystery for now.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnathiTreasureDiscovery_0x843_Name</Label>
    <String>Mystery of the Snathi Hoard</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnathiTreasureDiscovery_0x843_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our explorers have stumbled upon a hidden cache of riches a comet that our explorer drones recently visited. The only clue to its origin is an inscription with the word 'Snathi'. The treasure is vast, tempting us with immediate wealth.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnathiTreasureDiscovery_0x843_Choice_Claim_Desc</Label>
    <String>Claim the treasure.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnathiTreasureDiscovery_0x843_Choice_Claim_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>Fortune favors the bold. The Snathi treasure has been secured, significantly boosting our treasury.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnathiTreasureDiscovery_0x843_Choice_Respect_Desc</Label>
    <String>Leave the treasure untouched.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnathiTreasureDiscovery_0x843_Choice_Respect_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>We have chosen to honor the Snathi legacy by not plundering their trove. May this decision bring us good karma.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DistantSignal_0x844_Name</Label>
    <String>The Echo from the Void</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DistantSignal_0x844_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our deep space orbital telescopes have intercepted a faint signal emanating from the void. The message, though fragmented, seems to be a plea or inquiry: 'is anyone there?'. The only clue we can get from it is that it matches a radio signature of a species once called 'The Slyne'.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DistantSignal_0x844_Choice_Respond_Desc</Label>
    <String>Attempt to respond to the signal.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DistantSignal_0x844_Choice_Respond_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>Our message has been sent. Now we wait to see if our call into the darkness is met with friend, foe, or silence.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DistantSignal_0x844_Choice_Ignore_Desc</Label>
    <String>Ignore the signal.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DistantSignal_0x844_Choice_Ignore_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The depths of space remain undisturbed by our hand. The signal fades into the cosmic background, unanswered.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Name</Label>
    <String>Gift of the Mithrilar</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Desc</Label>
    <String>Your flagship's scans of the Artifact anomaly have uncovered something. A map to a nearby dead star that would normally be invisible to our sensors. A structure, hidden within the carcass of the dead star, whispers of the ancient Mithrilar—a civilization whose shadows outlive the stars themselves.[BR][BR] Buried in the celestial mausoleum is a device of their making: a conundrum of metal and mystery that hums with forgotten knowledge. Its cryptic mechanisms promise a leap in cognitive prowess, to awaken genius in the minds of our citizens that could transcend the limitations of biology and time.[BR][BR]However, the lead archeologist on the crew warns that this technology was almost certainly not meant for our species at our current stage of development and counsels you to not use it.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Choice_UseDevice_Desc</Label>
    <String>Activate the artifact and store it in our vault for later use.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Choice_UseDevice_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The device stirs, its intricate machinery spinning a symphony of cerebral transformation. Across the chosen world, minds awaken to new dimensions of thought. It is poised to be directed towards uplifting one of our core worlds.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Choice_DestroyDevice_Desc</Label>
    <String>Cast the device into oblivion, this device is too dangerous.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Choice_DestroyDevice_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>As the device disintegrates, a cascade of light is all that marks its passing. The decision weighs heavy, a testament to caution over the hunger for ascendancy. In the silent aftermath, one can only hope the whispers of the Mithrilar will not haunt the future that might have been.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientDevice_0x843_Choice_UseDevice_Result</Label>
    <String>Gift of the Mithrilar</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_PollutionRemover_0x842_Name</Label>
    <String>Atmospheric Reclamation Protocol</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_PollutionRemover_0x842_Desc</Label>
    <String>Adrift amidst cosmic dust, our flagship's scanners lock onto a relic of environmental engineering: a canister of nanomachines, dormant yet thrumming with potential. [BR][BR]They promise to scour worlds clean of pollutive scars. Yet, the core of this marvel—a Harmony Crystal—pulses with a rare energy, coveted by many.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_PollutionRemover_0x842_Choice_1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Store the Nanomachines in our vault.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_PollutionRemover_0x842_Choice_1_BonusDec</Label>
    <String>The Nanomachine relic will be stored in our Artifact vault. When ready, you can command the nanomachines to begin their silent waltz in the skies of a target polluted world, turning the grey pallor of pollution into the clear breath of progress.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_PollutionRemover_0x842_Choice_2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Extract Harmony Crystal</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_PollutionRemover_0x842_Choice_2_BonusDec</Label>
    <String>Forego the fleeting charm of clean air for the Harmony Crystal's enduring allure. Its power could be the keystone to advancements yet undreamed of. Or money. Lots of of money is nice.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnugglerColony_0x843_Title</Label>
    <String>Slumbering Snugglers</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnugglerColony_0x843_Desc</Label>
    <String>Within a derelict capsule, adrift amongst the stars, we find a curious sight—a colony of Snugglers, serene in suspended animation, a menagerie bound for a zoo long forgotten.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnugglerColony_0x843_Choice_Adopt_Desc</Label>
    <String>Bring the Snuggler Colony home.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnugglerColony_0x843_Choice_Adopt_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The Snugglers, once awakened, adapt with astonishing grace. They weave into the fabric of our civilization, bringing joy and a certain... snugness to our daily lives.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnugglerColony_0x843_Choice_Research_Desc</Label>
    <String>Dissect the stasis technology..</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SnugglerColony_0x843_Choice_Research_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>As our scientists unravel the mechanisms of the stasis field, revelations flow. The frontiers of our knowledge expand with the promise of new technologies.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>GeniusBomb_Name</Label>
    <String>Gift of the Mithrilar</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>GeniusBomb_Dec</Label>
    <String>This machine and it's operator will gradually increase the intelligence of citizens on target core world until they are genius level.[BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]+1 Yor Citizen[/COLOR]</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>MagnifyInfluence_Name</Label>
    <String>Magnify Influence</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MagnifyInfluence_Dec</Label>
    <String>Multiplies the influence produced by target core world for a couple of years.[BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]+300% Influence Growth[/COLOR]</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CommunicationBoostDevice_0x844_Name</Label>
    <String>Echoes of Influence</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CommunicationBoostDevice_0x844_Desc</Label>
    <String>After weeks of investigation your flagship has discovered a relic of communication prowess. This ancient device promises a significant swell in our planet's influence, permeating the ether with our ideals.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CommunicationBoostDevice_0x844_Choice_InfluenceBoost_Desc</Label>
    <String>Send it to our vault for later use.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CommunicationBoostDevice_0x844_Choice_InfluenceBoost_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The device will be in our vault for later use.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CommunicationBoostDevice_0x844_Choice_HyperSilicatesExtract_Desc</Label>
    <String>Disassemble the device to harvest HyperSilicates.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CommunicationBoostDevice_0x844_Choice_HyperSilicatesExtract_BonusDesc</Label>
    <String>The extracted HyperSilicates gleam with potential, a treasure trove of possibility that could one day fuel a marvel of our own making.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalAllianceProposal_0xA1B2_Name</Label>
    <String>A Questionable Pact</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalAllianceProposal_0xA1B2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have a strong suggestion for you.  Our syndicates thrive on being able to trade technologies.  We would appreciate it if you would let some of our associates tour your research labs to better understand how your technology works.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalAllianceProposal_0xA1B2_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>Accept the alliance and share our knowledge.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalAllianceProposal_0xA1B2_Choice1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By sharing our technological advancements, we risk empowering a potential adversary but also open a path to peace and mutual gain.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalAllianceProposal_0xA1B2_Choice2_Name</Label>
    <String>Decline the alliance and protect our interests.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_CriminalAllianceProposal_0xA1B2_Choice2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Turning away from the shadowy deal will please our citizens and safeguard our tech, though it may provoke the syndicate's ire.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DrenginMiningProposal_0xB2D4_Name</Label>
    <String>Nebula Mining Proposition</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DrenginMiningProposal_0xB2D4_Dec</Label>
    <String>You know of the nebula at the border of your territory, yes? It holds riches that only our technology can extract. Grant us the mining rights, and we will remember your aid in the future. Refuse, and you insult us.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DrenginMiningProposal_0xB2D4_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>Allow them to mine the nebula.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DrenginMiningProposal_0xB2D4_Choice1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We accept the proposition, with the understanding they will almost certainly get a lot of wealth for awhile from this that we will not.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DrenginMiningProposal_0xB2D4_Choice2_Name</Label>
    <String>I don't think so.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_DrenginMiningProposal_0xB2D4_Choice2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We cannot allow them unfettered access to the nebula. The wealth would likely be used to eventually target us.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientSpeciesRelicRequest_0xF4A9_Name</Label>
    <String>Relic Recovery Request</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientSpeciesRelicRequest_0xF4A9_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have detected the signature of a Precursor relic within the boundaries of your territory. Our interest is purely academic, and we seek your permission to recover it. While we cannot share its secrets, the benefits to our people would be considerable.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientSpeciesRelicRequest_0xF4A9_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>Grant permission for the relic recovery.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientSpeciesRelicRequest_0xF4A9_Choice1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We will allow your recovery mission. While the secrets of the relic remain yours, we hope this act of good faith serves to strengthen our relations.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientSpeciesRelicRequest_0xF4A9_Choice2_Name</Label>
    <String>I'm sorry but that would be against our strategic interests.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AncientSpeciesRelicRequest_0xF4A9_Choice2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We cannot permit an operation that does not include full disclosure of its findings. Our sovereignty must be respected.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExplorerFleetIntrusion_0xE8F3_Name</Label>
    <String>Proposition for Swift Passage</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExplorerFleetIntrusion_0xE8F3_Dec</Label>
    <String>We frequently traverse your space during our explorations.  In fact, as you know, everyone does. But we would like to offer you a token of goodwill. We have technology that can increase the speed of your vessels, easing any burden our presence may cause.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExplorerFleetIntrusion_0xE8F3_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>Accept the technology and allow continued exploration.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExplorerFleetIntrusion_0xE8F3_Choice1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We gratefully accept your offer and look forward to furthering our own expeditions with this new technology.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExplorerFleetIntrusion_0xE8F3_Choice2_Name</Label>
    <String>Deny the technology.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExplorerFleetIntrusion_0xE8F3_Choice2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We cannot accept this. Our space must remain our own, and your expeditions should be more carefully planned to avoid intrusion.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SubspaceWaveAssistance_0xC5D7_Name</Label>
    <String>Subspace Wave Collaboration</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SubspaceWaveAssistance_0xC5D7_Dec</Label>
    <String>A rare subspace wave is approaching, which promises to temporarily enhance the speed of ships that can tune into its frequency. Our engineers are intrigued, but financial support is needed to adjust our fleet to these unique conditions.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SubspaceWaveAssistance_0xC5D7_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>Invest in the subspace wave tuning for a fleet speed boost.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SubspaceWaveAssistance_0xC5D7_Choice1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By contributing to the subspace wave tuning, our ships will enjoy enhanced velocity, while our partners gain an even greater benefit from their advanced tuning techniques.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SubspaceWaveAssistance_0xC5D7_Choice2_Name</Label>
    <String>Decline the financial support and miss the opportunity.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SubspaceWaveAssistance_0xC5D7_Choice2_Dec</Label>
    <String>If we choose not to contribute financially, we'll miss out on the subspace boost and potentially strain our relationship with the proposing faction.</String>
</StringTable>



</StringTableList>