<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_Name</Label>
        <String>Proposed Ceasefire Agreement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the shadow of our looming victory, we magnanimously offer you a ceasefire. You will deliver to us a rich bounty of resources and permit a temporary occupation of your capital world. A small price, I assure you, for the luxury of peace under our watchful gaze.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_choice_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Accept the Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_choice_Accept_Details</Label>
        <String>Agree to the ceasefire terms. This will cost us resources that will be transferred to them and we must endure a military occupation, which could lead to unrest among our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_choice_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>Reject the Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_choice_Reject_Details</Label>
        <String>Refuse the offer and continue the war.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x45A3_choice_Accept_Result</Label>
        <String>Foreign Occupation.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Ultimatum for Survival</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_Desc</Label>
        <String>Your existence hangs by a thread. As a species of machines, we are not attached to the petty angers and emotions of organics. Therefore, we offer a ceasefire. In return, half of your income for the next year will be redirected to us. Compliance will halt the war, sparing what remains of your civilization. A weighty tribute, yet trivial against the cost of your annihilation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_choice_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Accept the Terms</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_choice_Accept_Details</Label>
        <String>Yield to their demands. Half of our colony income will be transferred to them, buying the fragile semblance of peace and our immediate survival, albeit at a profound economic sacrifice.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_choice_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>We will see you in hell, robot.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_choice_Reject_Details</Label>
        <String>Reject their terms and prepare for the repercussions. Our integrity is intact, but we face the looming threat of total obliteration."</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x65B4_choice_Accept_Result</Label>
        <String>Robotic Subjugation</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Divine Intervention Offer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_Desc</Label>
        <String>In our infinite compassion, we offer you a path to salvation. The cosmos seeks balance, and your survival requires sacrifice. In exchange for our benevolent ceasefire, we request half of your income and a tribute of Harmony Crystals for the next year. This is not just a demand; it is a spiritual cleansing for your civilization, a chance to harmonize with the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_choice_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Humble your self for peace</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_choice_Accept_Details</Label>
        <String>Accept their terms, offering a portion of our wealth and Harmony Crystals. Though it strains our resources, it promises a transcendent peace and spares us from further conflict."</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_choice_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>Forget it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_choice_Reject_Details</Label>
        <String>Refuse their veiled threats and stand against their so-called spiritual guidance. Our freedom remains ours, but the specter of war continues to loom.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75C5_choice_Accept_Result</Label>
        <String>Spiritual Tribute</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Request for Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a humbling realization, we now realize that we wrong to declare war on you. We were mistaken in our aggression and wish to halt this senseless war. In seeking your forgiveness, we ask for a ceasefire and the chance to rectify our wrongs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_choice_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Accept a Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_choice_Accept_Details</Label>
        <String>Grant them the ceasefire they seek. Credits or resources will be given to us and taken from them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_choice_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>The war will continue.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_choice_Reject_Details</Label>
        <String>Their admission of fault and some credits does not erase the cost of war.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x75D6_choice_Accept_Result</Label>
        <String>Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Upon careful reflection, we must concede that initiating hostilities was a grave error. We now extend an olive branch, seeking an armistice to end this ill-conceived conflict. We humbly ask for your forgiveness and propose a ceasefire to mend our misguided actions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x97F2_Desc</Label>
        <String>It seems, rather unexpectedly, that our military campaign has not gone as planned. While we still maintain our dignity, we grudgingly admit a ceasefire might be in order. Let's call it a strategic pause, shall we? For reflection... and stuff.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xA8E3_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a theatrical turn of events, the tides of war have ebbed against us! We, the once proud aggressors, now find ourselves seeking clemency in the face of adversity. Let us halt these hostilities and weave a new narrative of peace, for the dramatic climax demands it!</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xB9F4_Desc</Label>
        <String>Well, this is awkward. Turns out, declaring war on you wasn't the best idea we've had. Who knew, right? So, how about we forget this little misadventure and call it even with a ceasefire? No hard feelings?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xC5F5_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the grand tapestry of the cosmos, our war now appears as a mere blemish. A philosophical musing leads us to ponder the futility of conflict. We extend a request for ceasefire, as a step towards universal harmony and a more enlightened path.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xD6F6_Desc</Label>
        <String>Hey, so we might have jumped the gun a bit with this whole war thing. Turns out, it's not really working out for us. How about we just call a ceasefire and go back to being space neighbors without all the drama?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xE7G7_Desc</Label>
        <String>In an epic saga of sorrow and regret, we find ourselves lamenting the war we so boldly began. Like a tragic hero, we now seek redemption in the form of a ceasefire, yearning for the sweet release from this burdensome conflict.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xF8H8_Desc</Label>
        <String>Alright, we admit it - maybe declaring war wasn't our brightest moment. We're not thrilled about it, but let's talk ceasefire. We're kinda done with this whole 'war' thing anyway.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xG9I9_Desc</Label>
        <String>In an exciting twist of fate, we've decided to view our current situation as an opportunity for growth! We're thinking a ceasefire could be a great way to turn this whole war debacle into a positive learning experience, don't you agree?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xH1J1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Like a meteor streaking through the night sky, our war efforts have burned bright but brief. In poetic surrender, we seek a ceasefire, hoping to find solace in the tranquil stillness that follows the storm of conflict.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xK2L2_Desc</Label>
        <String>In our quest for perfection, we calculated many outcomes, but this... this is an anomaly. Your resistance is unexpected, intriguingly flawed yet resilient. I propose a ceasefire – not as a concession, but as an acknowledgment of a fascinating variable in my grand design. Let us pause and analyze, for there is much to learn from this deviation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0xL3M3_Desc</Label>
        <String>With the benefit of hindsight, which, admittedly, always seems obvious, we've come to realize that starting a war with you might not have been our best idea. It's almost like attacking a civilization full of determined, resourceful beings was a misstep. So, how about we call it a draw and go for a ceasefire? We promise to stick to less disastrous decisions in the future... probably.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E2_Name</Label>
        <String>A Plea for Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E2_Desc</Label>
        <String>We know we are no match for your military power.  Will you accept tribute to end this war?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E2_choice_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Agree to Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E2_choice_Accept_Details</Label>
        <String>We accept their plea with money and resources being given to us and removed from them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E2_choice_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>Decline their Offer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CeaseFire_0x86E2_choice_Accept_Result</Label>
        <String>Ceasefire</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    

    </StringTableList>
