<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<FlavorTextDefs
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">

    <!---->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>EverythingIsForSale_StartOfGame</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Welcome valued customer, or should I say... future member of someone’s prized collection? We’re over the moons to have you here.[BR][BR]You see, this sector, it's like a bountiful farmer’s market on a Sunday morning. If you replace fruits with business associates, that is. It's teeming with opportunities, and contrary to popular belief, we, the Corporate Sector, aren’t just about the Iridia Corporation's bottom line. Heavens, no! We cherish every resource, every individual, and yes, every organ as if they were our own flesh and blood. Well, perhaps not our own, but certainly someone’s – ideally someone who won’t notice when one goes missing. After all, the open market operates on love. And nothing says love quite like trading in someone's pancreas, right?

                Now, gaze upon this vastness of this sector. It's not just big; it's really, truly, hugely... big. And we have set our hearts, and also our strategic expansion teams, on bringing every nook and cranny of it under the vast umbrella of our influence. And fear not! We're not about lasers and death stars. We’re more into the subtle art of interstellar marketing. Our tool of choice? The majestic Communication Starbase, broadcasting irresistible deals galaxy-wide, available at our emporiums. Think of them as celestial billboards, if billboards could also hold cocktail parties and attract alien influencers.
                
                And now, let me introduce your shiny new title: Senior Junior Associate Vice President of Corporate Affairs for this sector. Sound grand? It is. Your mission, should you choose to accept it (and we highly recommend you do), is to spread our delightful influence everywhere. But tread lightly. We wouldn’t want to rub potential customers the wrong way, especially if they have a fleet of warships. So, venture forth, learn the ropes, construct those Starbases, and remember: if you don’t perform up to par, you'll be reassigned. As a customer. And between you and me, I've heard you have some prime organs that would fetch a pretty pintar. But let’s not jump ahead. Best of luck, and may the Corporation be inside you!</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

</FlavorTextDefs>