<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<FlavorTextDefs
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_GenericConfirm</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Understood</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <!---->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_ColonizedCoreworld</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>You've settled your first planet large enough to establish a new core world![BR][BR]Many planets aren't rich enough in resources to justify large colonies. Planets too small to support a shipyard are well-suited for supporting larger colonies. These smaller colonies don't require any additional leadership or management. [BR][BR]Due to their rarity, taking advantage of any planet resource-rich enough to justify larger colonies is advisable. To do so, a [HS=HS_Leaders]Leader[/HS] must be assigned as a [HS=HS_Governor]Governor[/HS] to the planet. Once a [HS=HS_Governor]Governor[/HS] is appointed, a shipyard can be built over the planet, and the planet can be developed to better utilize the resources.[BR][BR][HS=HS_Leaders]Leaders[/HS] can be recruited from the [ICON=Menu_Leader_Icon] Leaders screen under the Recruitment tab. Recruited [HS=HS_Leaders]Leaders[/HS] can then be assigned to manage planets under the Governors tab.[BR][BR]New Objective: Appoint a Governor</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_ColonizeTargetPlanets</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Terran Alliance alliance was charged with colonizing planets to secure humanity's foothold in space. None can contest the Alliance's competency with all the planets successfully colonized. Take a moment to revel in this accomplishment.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Colonize 8 Planets</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_ColonzieTargetWorldsNoCoreworld</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Terran Alliance alliance was charged with colonizing planets to secure humanity's foothold in space. None can contest the Alliance's competency with all the planets successfully colonized. Take a moment to revel in this accomplishment.[BR][BR]There is work yet to do. None of the colonized planets have a high enough class to justify expansion. Continue searching for a Planet with a Planet Class 10 or higher to colonize so that we can establish a new Core World.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Colonize 8 Planets[BR]New Objective: Colonize a Core World</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_InstalledGovernor</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>You've successfully assigned a governor! Their presence turns the Colony into a Core World where a Shipyard can be built and the planet developed.[BR][BR]There is some bad news. Reports have confirmed the presence of Pirates in the sector. While they're allowed a foothold in space and a place to construct ships, they are a threat. We'll need to destroy their shipyard to secure our colonies' safety.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Appoint a Governor[BR]New Objective: Destroy a Pirate Shipyard</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_InformPlayerUnlockedLeaderScreen</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>No one can manage the entire Terran Alliance alone, no matter how competent. With the appropriate infrastructure, [HS=HS_Leaders]Leaders[/HS] can now be recruited. Every applicant has strengths and weaknesses, making them more or less suitable for any role.[BR][BR][HS=HS_Leaders]Leaders[/HS] can serve as Governors and manage a Core World, become Diplomats, and they can serve as Ministers. Ministers focus on benefiting the entire civilization. Each ministry office has an area of focus and gives a benefit based on a Leader's specific skill.[BR][BR]Recruit new [HS=HS_Leaders]Leaders[/HS] from the [ICON=Menu_Leader_Icon] Leaders screen under the Recruitment tab. [HS=HS_Leaders]Leaders[/HS] can then be assigned to new roles under the Ministers tab.[BR][BR]New Objective: Appoint 3 Ministers</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_CabinetFilled</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>You've successfully appointed several leaders into roles as Ministers. Their support will go a long way to assisting in exploring the galaxy, settling new planets, and the expansion of the Terran Alliance's Influence. As you recruit new Leaders or their skills change, you can always change what role a leader has from the [ICON=Menu_Leader_Icon] Leaders screen.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Appoint 3 Ministers</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_PiratesSpotted</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>A Pirate Shipyard has been located in this sector.[BR][BR]Some time ago, the plans for the Hyperdrive Propulsion system were leaked to less scrupulous groups. A group of pirates has managed to use this technology to take to space on their own. Even if they lack our resources, they should not be underestimated.[BR][BR]While they are allowed a foothold in space and a place to construct ships, they are a danger. Their presence threatens each and every colony. To secure the safety of the Terran Alliance, we'll need to destroy their Shipyard.[BR][BR]Assemble a fleet of armed ships to assault and take down the Pirate Shipyard.[BR][BR]New Objective:  Destroy a Pirate Shipyard</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_PirateShipyardDestroyed</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Pirate's base of operations in this sector has been destroyed. There may be a few stragglers, but their presence in this sector will wane without the ability to create more ships.[BR][BR]Great work. The Terran Alliance is closer to establishing a solid foothold in this sector.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Destroy a Pirate Shipyard</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Tutorial_NeedsUnlockLeaderScreen</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>As the Terran Alliance's influence expands, we'll need competent leaders. Leaders can help manage Core Worlds, fill Ministry positions that benefit the entire Alliance, and more. The Alliance needs to ensure the infrastructure is in place to recruit leaders. This can be done by completing the Colonial Leadership Project at the homeworld.[BR][BR]New Objective: Complete the Colonial Leadership Project</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
</FlavorTextDefs>