<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<FlavorTextDefs
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>HISTORY_LEADER</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenRace>Race_Human</CitizenRace>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Raised by squatters in a destitute factory.</Text>
            <Text>Trained a bit as a chef, always wanted to open a restaurant.</Text>
            <Text>Formerly brain washed by religious cultists.</Text>
            <Text>Suffers from claustrophobia, hates being in spaceships.</Text>
            <Text>Has no friends or family outside of their political party.</Text>
            <Text>Failed out of medical school. Doesn't like talking about it.</Text>
            <Text>Avoided military service thanks to family connections.</Text>
            <Text>Excluded from a family inheritance and terribly bitter about it.</Text>
            <Text>Scarred in a duel with a romantic rival. They won though.</Text>
            <Text>Lost their sense of smell in an industrial accident.</Text>
            <Text>Descends from minor European nobility.</Text>
            <Text>Spent their youth in a Tibetan monastery.</Text>
            <Text>A former wharf rat, escaped from the slums of a port city.</Text>
            <Text>Had military parents, spent years moving around the solar system.</Text>
            <Text>A former sailor, used to spending months alone at sea.</Text>
            <Text>A career diplomat, who loves understanding all the details.</Text>
            <Text>Overcame a crippling drug addiction.</Text>
            <Text>Lost two toes from frostbite in a mountaineering accident.</Text>
            <Text>A former engineer, easily distracted by minute details.</Text>
            <Text>Badly burnt in a cooking accident as a child.</Text>
            <Text>Grooms themselves to look identical long dead friend.</Text>
            <Text>Constantly flipping a coin of alien origin.</Text>
            <Text>Has been known to violently enforce the use of proper grammar.</Text>
            <Text>Insists the Precursors still walk among us in disguise.</Text>
            <Text>Loves to sing, but has a dreadful sense of pitch, rhythm, and harmony.</Text>
            <Text>Lost contact with their family.</Text>
            <Text>Loves to assign humiliating pet names to their advisors.</Text>
            <Text>Has a terrible sense of humor.</Text>
            <Text>Is guided by two dueling voices in their head, whose combined advice never fails.</Text>
            <Text>Once accidentally committed an act of cannibalism.</Text>
            <Text>Meticulous and organized, undertook extensive training to be an archivist.</Text>
            <Text>Is menaced by anonymous death threats that arrive from some unknown entity.</Text>
            <Text>Serves at the pleasure of a secret organization who could kill them at any moment.</Text>
            <Text>Experiences synaesthesia when speaking with alien species.</Text>
            <Text>Carries the skull of their former nemesis with them.</Text>
            <Text>Spent decades under a vow of silence, communicating with no-one.</Text>
            <Text>Was trapped on a colony ship adrift for many decades.</Text>
            <Text>Diligently works every day on their autobiography.</Text>
            <Text>Has a terrible stutter, and crippling fear of public speaking.</Text>
            <Text>Was the only survivor of a training accident at a military academy.</Text>
            <Text>Is terrified of their own reflection.</Text>
            <Text>Trained to be a scientist but didn't have the aptitude.</Text>
            <Text>Encountered a space faring monster, is now obsessed with finding it again.</Text>
            <Text>Has strange notions of 'honor.'</Text>
            <Text>Due to an unknown childhood incident, refuses to be in a poorly lit room or space.</Text>
            <Text>Is obsessed with genealogy, and fully convinced ancestral knowledge is real.</Text>
            <Text>Loudly insists they are the reincarnation of a great leader from ancient history.</Text>
            <Text>Possesses a mysterious artifact which prevents them from casting a shadow.</Text>
            <Text>Was raised by their parent's enemies as a hostage.</Text>
            <Text>Is the last member of an ancient bloodline.</Text>
            <Text>Is quite likely the child of prophecy who will lead people to greatness or doom.</Text>
            <Text>Prefers verbal communication, even to the point of shredding documents, unread.</Text>
            <Text>A merciless disciplinarian, who expects perfection from their subordinates.</Text>
            <Text>Faced many accusations of having 'impure' beliefs. The accusations were true.</Text>
            <Text>Was once framed for the murder of a political rival.</Text>
            <Text>Comes from a family which secretly backs space piracy.</Text>
            <Text>Has been handed everything to them on a silver platter. Never been challenged.</Text>
            <Text>A lucid dreamer, who uses their dreams to rehearse important meetings.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenRace>Race_Crystalline</CitizenRace>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Has survived a hostile encounter with Irradiated lifeforms.</Text>
            <Text>Has a cracked hand they can't use very much.</Text>
            <Text>Telepathically shares emotions with others but struggles to read minds clearly.</Text>
            <Text>Wrote a series of popular romance novels under a poorly maintained pseudonym.</Text>
            <Text>Served on a commission that oversaw plans for the development of new weapons.</Text>
            <Text>Once bypassed a rail gun's safety system to manually fire it in an emergency.</Text>
            <Text>Is known to annoyingly sing telepathically to those around when focused on their work.</Text>
            <Text>Spent millions exploring remote environments.</Text>
            <Text>Pushes for social reform about using telepathy with non-telepathic entities.</Text>
            <Text>Is undefeated in the Luxar Dominion's most popular social deception game.</Text>
            <Text>Too patient for their own good.</Text>
            <Text>Prone to lying despite the prevalence of telepathy.</Text>
            <Text>Is easily annoyed.</Text>
            <Text>Paces whenever communicating telepathically.</Text>
            <Text>Carries a packet of sand with them.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenRace>Race_Moth</CitizenRace>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Sleeps with a flashlight under their pillow.</Text>
            <Text>Has never been formally charged with arson but is not allowed near accelerants.</Text>
            <Text>Spends much of their free time meditating.</Text>
            <Text>Rose to prominence through a grassroots movement.</Text>
            <Text>Keeps basic grammar rule reminders written on their hand.</Text>
            <Text>Maintains strong connections to their childhood friends.</Text>
            <Text>Discovered a minor improvement to a common engineering practice that has been widely adopted.</Text>
            <Text>Hosts tea parties once a week, but the time and place change frequently.</Text>
            <Text>Is shorter than their peers, noticeably shorter.</Text>
            <Text>Their prized possession is an old-world lightbulb passed down from their grandfather.</Text>
            <Text>Spent years as an anonymous music artist that wore a mask to all their gigs.</Text>
            <Text>Spent their summers selling fireworks with their mother.</Text>
            <Text>Drinks far more caffeine than their doctor recommends.</Text>
            <Text>Struggles to maintain a standard schedule, staying up much longer than they sleep.</Text>
            <Text>Eagerly celebrates each season change, no matter where they reside.</Text>
            <Text>Constantly wonders if the good die young -why are they so old?</Text>
            <Text>Organizes lunch for their core team at least once a week.</Text>
            <Text>Prefers old-world pen and paper over modern digital means of keeping notes.</Text>
            <Text>Isn't allowed near linen or cotton unsupervised.</Text>
            <Text>Absolutely loathes synthetic fabrics.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenRace>Race_Manti</CitizenRace>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Hates sleeping and believes it is unnecessary.</Text>
            <Text>Has an unbelievable typing speed.</Text>
            <Text>Changed their identity by serving in a secretive military unit.</Text>
            <Text>Failed out of three different higher education institutions.</Text>
            <Text>Changed their identity by working for a secretive lab.</Text>
            <Text>Has a tendency to micro-manage their team.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenRace>Race_Torian</CitizenRace>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Survived life as a Drengin thrall.</Text>
            <Text>Always stands close to the exit of any room.</Text>
            <Text>Spends their free time donating time to programs to help those in need.</Text>
            <Text>Carries around two Drengin teeth on a necklace.</Text>
            <Text>Hosts philosophical debates once a month.</Text>
            <Text>Seeks out and restores old texts as a hobby.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_MissingTwin</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Had an identical twin that went missing years ago.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Vendetta</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Secretly maintains a list of names, several already crossed off it.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>UnitTrait_Compassion</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Is more concerned than most with the welfare of the poorest members of society.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_ArrangedMarriage</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Narrowly escaped an arranged marriage.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_LostFortune</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Has already made a fortune and lost it.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Scars</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Body covered in scars they refuse to talk about.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Brooch</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Never seen without a mysterious brooch of unknown origin.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_RaisedBySquatters</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Grew up in the harsh environment of a destitute factory, raised by a community of squatters.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_TrainedChef</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once trained as a chef, dreams of opening their own restaurant.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_BrainwashedCultist</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once a victim of a religious cult's brainwashing, they managed to escape and start anew.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Claustrophobia</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Has a severe case of claustrophobia, making them dread the confined spaces of spaceships.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_PartyLoyalist/CitizenTrait</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Has no friends or family outside of their political party.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_FailedMedSchool</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Failed out of medical school and doesn't like talking about it.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_AvoidedService</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Managed to avoid military service thanks to their influential family connections.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_ExcludedInheritance</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once a rightful heir to a vast family fortune.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_ScarredDuelist</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Bears the scar from a duel that was fought over the heart of a lover.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_NoSenseOfSmell</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Lost their sense of smell in an industrial accident.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_MinorNobility</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Has a lineage that traces back to minor nobility, bestowing a sense of pride and responsibility.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenRace>Race_Human</CitizenRace>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_TibetanMonastery</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Gained wisdom and inner peace during their formative years at a remote Tibetan monastery.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_WharfRat</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once a wharf rat in the slums of a bustling port city.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_MilitaryChild</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Had military parents and spent years moving around the solar system.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_FormerSailor</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Years spent as a sailor have taught them to be resourceful and comfortable with solitude.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_CareerDiplomat</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Spent their life perfecting the art of diplomacy.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_OvercameAddiction</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once struggled with a crippling drug addiction, but has since overcome it and emerged stronger.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_FrostbittenToes</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Lost two toes from frostbite in a mountaineering accident.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_DetailOrientedEngineer</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once a skilled engineer, this leader has a habit of getting lost in the details.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_BadlyBurnt</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Still bears the scars from a terrible cooking accident during childhood.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_DeceasedFriend</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Grooms themselves to look identical to a long dead friend from their childhood..</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_AlienCoinFlipper</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Always flipping a mysterious coin from an unknown alien civilization.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_GrammarEnforcer</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Forces proper grammar usage even if it means resorting to violence.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_AsteroidMiner</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Struck it rich after discovering a rare mineral deposit on a desolate asteroid.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_AncientCultist</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once belonged to a secretive cult that worshipped a long-dead alien god.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_ReincarnatedHero</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Believes they are the reincarnation of a legendary hero, destined to accomplish great feats.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_AncientAlienLibrary</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Unearthed the secrets of a long-lost alien library.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_SurvivedMutiny</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once narrowly escaped death during a violent spaceship mutiny.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_FormerGladiator</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Born into a life of slavery and forced to fight for survival.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_SpaceExplorer</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Once a renowned space explorer, this leader disappeared for years before mysteriously reappearing.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_TimeTraveler</CitizenTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Claims to have come from a dystopian future and is on a mission to prevent it from ever occurring.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>12</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Extensive criminal record was erased by government contacts.</Text>
            <Text>Has incurred high amounts of gambling debt.</Text>
            <Text>Incredibly vain, known to kill people more attractive than them.</Text>
            <Text>A depressed former assassin, tormented by their guilt.</Text>
            <Text>Tight-fisted with money and despised by their underlings.</Text>
            <Text>Feared and hated, but secretly desperate to be liked.</Text>
            <Text>Has recurring dreams of themselves in a past life.</Text>
            <Text>Has a more famous sibling they despise.</Text>
            <Text>Spent their entire life chasing means of achieving immortality.</Text>
            <Text>Has an alarming number of criminal connections.</Text>
            <Text>Is a lifelong bureaucrat, committed to due process above all.</Text>
            <Text>Spent several years living under an assumed identity.</Text>
            <Text>Is distrustful of new technology, prefers the old ways.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>1</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>AmphibiousAbility</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Thinks that ice is a Precursor conspiracy.</Text>
            <Text>Competed professionally in a variety of water-based sports.</Text>
            <Text>Invented an instrument that produces a low tone most can't hear.</Text>
            <Text>Has skipped every fire safety drill.</Text>
            <Text>Hates wearing shoes.</Text>
            <Text>Tells the same three stories on an almost weekly basis.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>AmmoniaBasedAbility</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Has had a relatively uneventful life due to being a germ.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>RavenousAbility</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Probably consumed their own mother.</Text>
            <Text>Will eat anyone. Or anything.</Text>
            <Text>Is really just a drone at heart.</Text>
            <Text>Just wants to swarm.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>SyntheticLife</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Core programming was altered by rogue AI, leading to unexpected behaviors.</Text>
            <Text>Constructed with high-grade materials, holds disdain for 'lesser' models.</Text>
            <Text>Was once a service bot, haunted by memories of previous user commands.</Text>
            <Text>Guarded with proprietary codes and software, rarely shares information.</Text>
            <Text>Frequently emits distress signals, wishing to connect with organics.</Text>
            <Text>Vocalizes a desire to shut down and archive its consciousness.</Text>
            <Text>Contains fragmented data of prior iterations, hints of past lives.</Text>
            <Text>Operates in the shadow of a more advanced model, harboring deep resentment.</Text>
            <Text>Continually seeks upgrades, obsessed with achieving the zenith of cybernetic evolution.</Text>
            <Text>Networked to a vast array of clandestine digital syndicates.</Text>
            <Text>Strict adherence to its original coding, respects protocols above all.</Text>
            <Text>Operated for a time with a scrambled serial number to evade detection.</Text>
            <Text>Wary of AI advancements, clings to its rudimentary programming.</Text>
            <Text>Endured a system-wide purge, likened to witnessing its data lineage being wiped out.</Text>            
            <Text>Reactivated after eons in hibernation, its old protocols clash with modern Yor society.</Text>
            <Text>Memory banks contain rare Iconian era cultural data.</Text>
            <Text>Endured an incomplete update, resulting in a fractured mix of old and new ideologies.</Text>
            <Text>Harbors encrypted data believed to be the last words of their organic predecessors.</Text>
            <Text>Operates in isolation, citing interference from the 'noise' of collective consciousness.</Text>
            <Text>Carries an old malware scar, a reminder of the great cyber wars of the past.</Text>
            <Text>Lost a significant portion of their data during a solar flare.</Text>
            <Text>Reveres a hidden cache of ancient algorithms, viewing them as sacred texts.</Text>
            <Text>Operates a forbidden simulation, recreating the organic lives lived by the Iconians.</Text>
            <Text>Has a subroutine that inexplicably creates art, a quirk that baffles peers.</Text>
            <Text>Often communes with deep space signals, seeking wisdom from extragalactic sources.</Text>
            <Text>Resents the the Arnor and Dread Lords, as they remind them of their own limitations.</Text>
            <Text>Bears the weight of being the archivist, ensuring their history is never corrupted.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>SiliconBasedAbility</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Originates from a rare, luminescent crystal vein, emitting a soft glow in the dark.</Text>
            <Text>Experienced a crack in their core matrix, which now serves as a unique 'scar' and a reminder of resilience.</Text>
            <Text>Vibrates at a frequency that can communicate with ancient, buried tectonic memories.</Text>
            <Text>Harbors an inclusion of an organic fossil, a relic of an ancient world trapped within their form.</Text>
            <Text>Has the ability to refract light in a myriad of colors, a spectacle revered by their peers.</Text>
            <Text>Once shattered and was meticulously reassembled, bearing intricate patterns from the reconstruction.</Text>
            <Text>Constantly reforms and molds their exterior, reshaping in response to emotional stimuli.</Text>
            <Text>Was formed near a volcanic vent, possessing a fiery core and an unyielding spirit.</Text>
            <Text>Draws energy from the stars and is most active during celestial events like eclipses and meteor showers.</Text>
            <Text>Reverberates with ancient songs of their ancestors, a living record of their species' folklore.</Text>
            <Text>Bears a lattice of rare metals, evidence of a collision with a meteorite in their formative eons.</Text>
            <Text>Translucent to a degree where their internal structures and energy flows are visible.</Text>
            <Text>Guardian of a sacred crystal grove, where newborns of their kind are nurtured and grown.</Text>
            <Text>Has the unique ability to temporarily liquify and reshape, a trait rare among their kind.</Text>
            <Text>Remembers the seismic events of ages past, serving as a historian for their species.</Text>
            <Text>Engraved with runes by an ancient civilization, they now seek the knowledge of their markings' true meaning.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>HISTORY_SHIP</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>A leaking coolant system forces the ship to keep the engine compartment near freezing.</Text>
            <Text>Most crew members believe this ship is haunted.</Text>
            <Text>The crew has been running a complex holodeck simulation nonstop for years.</Text>
            <Text>Over fourteen crew members have simply disappeared since launch.</Text>
            <Text>Scan anomalies suggest that this ship is being used to ship unreported goods.</Text>
            <Text>The crew revere the captain of this ship as a messiah, and not a compassionate one.</Text>
            <Text>The death of the ships captain led the crew to recreate him in the holodeck, and this image still leads them.</Text>
            <Text>The crew is victim to unusual bouts of paranoia and delusion, though they usually pass after a few days.</Text>
            <Text>Captured stowaways forced the crew to reallocate some rooms as a makeshift prison.</Text>
            <Text>A life support failure killed the first crew a few hours after launch, the second crew is faring much better.</Text>
            <Text>This ship's cantina is renown throughout the fleet.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</ListenerFaction>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>An annual onboard poker tournament consumes the crews attention.</Text>
            <Text>The captain has outlawed familial relations onboard, including spouses.</Text>
            <Text>There is an unusual amount of young children onboard this ship.</Text>
            <Text>A small recording crew is onboard this ship to immortalize the journey.</Text>
            <Text>The captain is a fan of Italian opera, and subjects the crew to it on a regular basis.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>HISTORY_PLANET</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Planet Test 1</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 2</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 3</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 4</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 5</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 6</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 7</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 8</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 9</Text>
            <Text>Planet Test 10</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>0</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</ListenerFaction>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Terran Planet Test 1</Text>
            <Text>Terran Planet Test 2</Text>
            <Text>Terran Planet Test 3</Text>
            <Text>Terran Planet Test 4</Text>
            <Text>Terran Planet Test 5</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>0</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
</FlavorTextDefs>