<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Entry_DrenginEmpire</Label>
        <String>Drengin Empire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Entry_DrenginEmpire_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Drengin Empire embodies the quintessence of cosmic ambition. Towering at over 9 feet and brandishing an impressive set of razor-sharp teeth, their reputation in the galaxy is one of both awe and fear. The year 2226 marked a poignant chapter in their history, witnessing a civil confrontation with the Korath. And in this intricate dance of power, the Drengin, surprisingly, were the more measured participants.[BR][BR]The Drengin's creed is simple: the galaxy and all its non-Drengin inhabitants exist for their dominion. Their history with the Arceans is a testament to this belief. The joint invention of the stargates was a landmark of cooperation, swiftly followed by the Drengin's attempted betrayal. The ensuing debacle cemented a rivalry that remains fervent, even as stars burn out.[BR][BR]It would be an error to assume the Drengin's aggressiveness overshadows their intellect. Their technological marvels tread into areas many would deem ethically nebulous. Their persistence in galactic conquest is evident from their historical annals. When humanity was embroiled in terrestrial power struggles, the Drengin were engineering audacious mechanisms, like the ominous 'death furnaces', and undertaking expansive campaigns like the Torian enslavement.[BR][BR]Ironically, what held the Drengin back from universal domination was the vastness of space itself. Their venture to Toria, while grand, underscored the inefficiencies of their space travel. Humanity's invention of the hyperdrive, however, leveled the cosmic playing field. The initial human overtures, grounded in idealistic hopes of a united cosmos, were met with Drengin pragmatism in 2176. The ensuing silence from that human delegation speaks volumes, reminding us all that cosmic diplomacy, with the Drengin, comes with its own set of... challenges.</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>