<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Name</Label>
        <String>Global Uncertainty over the Colonization Program</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Desc</Label>
        <String>The knowledge that there is alien life out there has shaken our people to their core. The global population is in a state of shock and confusion, and the future is uncertain. There are riots and growing unrest across the planet. [BR][BR]The world is looking to you for leadership on what steps we shoud take next.
        </String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Choice_0_Dec</Label>
        <String>Initiate the Global Mental Wellness Initiative.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Choice_0_Details</Label>
        <String>Launch a comprehensive mental health support program to help the populace adapt to this new reality, ensuring societal mental resilience.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Choice_1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Establish the Civil Stability Corps.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>Form a specialized task force to maintain public order and security in the face of increasing unrest and societal disruption.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Choice_2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Create the Human Expansion Council.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FirstContactResponse_0x5C3B_Choice_2_Details</Label>
        <String>Develop a fund aimed at harnessing the economic opportunities of this new era, boosting research and development, and fostering global economic growth.</String>
    </StringTable>


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RapidExpansionCrisis_Name</Label>
        <String>Rapid Expansion Crisis</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_RapidExpansionCrisis_Desc</Label>
        <String>Our civilization's swift expansion into the galaxy has led to a critical juncture.[BR][BR]While new worlds have been colonized, our population is now thinly spread across many planets, resulting in neglected infrastructures and overstretched supply chains. Our homeworld's population is dwindling as citizens migrate to new frontiers. We face a dilemma of maintaining the momentum of our expansion while ensuring the stability and sustainability of our far-flung civilization. [BR][BR]Strategic decisions are imperative to navigate this complex landscape and secure the future of our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_REC_Choice_ManageGrowth_Desc</Label>
        <String>Implement policies to carefully manage and pace our growth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_REC_Choice_ManageGrowth_Details</Label>
        <String>Slowing down expansion allows for more sustainable development.This will dramatically reduce shipyard production for a year across all worlds but increase local manufacturing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_REC_Choice_BolsterDefenses_Desc</Label>
        <String>Strengthen our defenses to protect our rapidly expanding borders.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_REC_Choice_BolsterDefenses_Details</Label>
        <String>Investing in defense ensures the security of our new territories, though it requires substantial resources. Will provide three new ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_REC_Choice_PromoteStability_Desc</Label>
        <String>Focus on promoting stability and order within our existing colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_REC_Choice_PromoteStability_Details</Label>
        <String>Enhancing stability reduces the risk of internal conflicts, but might slow our overall momentum in expansion. Will provide two supply ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Expansion Celebration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Desc</Label>
        <String>The Arcean Empire stands at the threshold of a new galactic era. Leaders and visionaries gather on Arcea Prime to chart the course of the Empire's future amidst grand celebrations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <!-- Peaceful Exploration Choice -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Choice_Peaceful_Desc</Label>
        <String>Embrace Peaceful Exploration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Choice_Peaceful_Details</Label>
        <String>Adopt a policy of peaceful exploration, focusing on diplomacy and research to build a galaxy-wide network of alliances and mutual understanding.[BR][BR]Places a Expansion Celebration improvement on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <!-- Aggressive Colonization Choice -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Choice_Aggressive_Desc</Label>
        <String>Assertive Colonization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Choice_Aggressive_Details</Label>
        <String>Launch an aggressive colonization campaign, expanding the Empire's borders and asserting Arcean dominance throughout the galaxy.[BR][BR]Places a Colonization Program improvement on homeworld</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <!-- Defensive Strategy Choice -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Choice_Defensive_Desc</Label>
        <String>Strengthen Homeworlds</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ArceanExpansionCelebration_Choice_Defensive_Details</Label>
        <String>Focus on fortifying the homeworlds, enhancing planetary defenses and ensuring the foreign influence never becomes a problem for the Arcean people.[BR][BR]Places a Resistance Center on homeworld</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Dawn of a New Era for Torians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the wake of their hard-won liberation, the Torians stand amidst the remnants of Drengin oppression, a newfound autonomy pulsating within their grasp. [BR][BR]Surrounded by the alien technology of their former overlords, they grapple with its enigmatic potential. From the dense jungles of Toria Prime, strategic minds converge, debating the fate of the advanced arsenal now at their fins. Will they dismantle the relics of subjugation to prevent future tyranny, repurpose them to fortify their liberated worlds, or set forth as harbingers of peace in the interstellar theater? The Torians choice will redefine their destiny among the stars.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Choice_Exploration_Desc</Label>
        <String>Embrace the Stars: Chart New Horizons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Choice_Exploration_Details</Label>
        <String>Focus on space exploration to uncover new possibilities and expand Torian presence in the galaxy.[BR][BR]Places the Torian Telescope on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Choice_Technological_Desc</Label>
        <String>Leverage Abandoned Technologies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Choice_Technological_Details</Label>
        <String>Utilize the enemy's left behind technologies to boost our own scientific and technological capabilities.[BR][BR]Provides a Drengin Tech Cache on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Choice_Cultural_Desc</Label>
        <String>Revitalize Torian Culture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TorianLiberationAdvancement_Choice_Cultural_Details</Label>
        <String>Invest in cultural revival programs to strengthen the Torian identity and unity in this new era.[BR][BR]Places the Cultural Revival Structure on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Name</Label>
        <String>Expansion of the Drengin Empire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the shadowy corridors of power, the Drengin Empire devises sinister new stratagems to tighten its iron grip on the galaxy. Their fearsome fleets, armed with technologies harvested from the ruins of vanquished foes, cut through the void, ready to unleash terror that will echo in the silence of space. [BR][BR]Across star systems, subdued whispers speak of the coming dread - a darkness that seeks to consume the light of freedom and resistance, forging an eternal empire where the Drengin's will is the only law, unchallenged and absolute.[BR][BR]What should be our next move?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Choice_SlaveLabor_Desc</Label>
        <String>Intensify Slave Labor Camps</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Choice_SlaveLabor_Details</Label>
        <String>Expand and intensify slave labor camps to boost production at the cost of morality and decency.[BR][BR]Places Labor Camps on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Choice_WarMachines_Desc</Label>
        <String>Construct Doomsday Armories</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Choice_WarMachines_Details</Label>
        <String>Gain access to a unique weapon component for ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Choice_Suppression_Desc</Label>
        <String>Establish a Terror Surveillance Network</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrenginTyrannyExpansion_Choice_Suppression_Details</Label>
        <String>Create a planet-wide network to suppress dissent and spy on citizens, ensuring total control.[BR][BR]Places a Terror Center to increase control on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Authoritarian_Result</Label>
        <String>Suppression</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Name</Label>
        <String>Yor Singularity Advancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Desc</Label>
        <String>At the cusp of a computational renaissance, the Yor collective orchestrates its next grand phase of synthetic evolution. [BR][BR]Networks humming with the electric wisdom of untold aeons, they prepare to assimilate revolutionary technologies into their very framework. Each node, a nexus of potential, echoes with the binary promise of expansion. [BR][BR]Poised to extend their consciousness across the galactic expanse, the Yor forego flesh-bound limitations, their collective intellect converging on a singular, indomitable purpose: to engrave the logic of their existence deep into the fabric of the cosmos itself.[BR][BR]They now have a decision to make.</String>

    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Choice_NeuralNexus_Desc</Label>
        <String>Construct Neural Nexus Complexes</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Choice_NeuralNexus_Details</Label>
        <String>Develop advanced neural nexus hubs to enhance collective intelligence and decision-making processes.[BR][BR]Places four Neural Nexi on the planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Choice_QuantumProcessor_Desc</Label>
        <String>Deploy Quantum Processors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Choice_QuantumProcessor_Details</Label>
        <String>Integrate quantum computing technologies to exponentially increase processing power and efficiency.[BR][BR]Places a Quantum Processors on the planet. Others can be constructed on other core worlds</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Choice_AutonomousFabricators_Desc</Label>
        <String>Establish Autonomous Fabricators</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorSingularityMilestone_Choice_AutonomousFabricators_Details</Label>
        <String>Create self-replicating fabricators to bolster construction and maintenance capabilities autonomously.[BR][BR]Places a number of Fabricators on the planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Name</Label>
        <String>Iconian Renaissance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Desc</Label>
        <String>Emerging from the tenebrous veil of their catastrophic exodus, the resolute Iconians have alighted upon a virgin world. Here, they have forged resolve from desolation, sowing the seeds of resurgence in the fertile soil of newfound hope. [BR][BR]With ancient glory whispering in their genes, a renaissance blooms, promising to rekindle the embers of their long-dormant heritage. Now, at the dawn of their re-entry into the galactic theater, a pivotal choice looms: will they seek retribution, diplomacy, or a path yet undiscovered, as they carve their destiny anew among the starry firmament?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Choice_AncientArchives_Desc</Label>
        <String>Rebuild the Ancient Archives</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Choice_AncientArchives_Details</Label>
        <String>Revive the vast knowledge and cultural heritage stored in the ancient archives, lost during the Yor conquest.[BR][BR]Places an ancient archive on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Choice_TechnologicalHarmony_Desc</Label>
        <String>Establish Bio-Digital Fusion Centers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Choice_TechnologicalHarmony_Details</Label>
        <String>Create centers that epitomize the Iconian's unique blend of biology and technology, fostering innovation and recovery.[BR][BR]Installs a Bio-Digital Fusion Center on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Choice_DiplomaticOutreach_Desc</Label>
        <String>Open Galactic Diplomacy Hubs</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IconianResurgence_Choice_DiplomaticOutreach_Details</Label>
        <String>Strengthen diplomatic relations and forge new alliances to ensure the Iconians' presence and influence in galactic affairs.[BR][BR]Places a Diplomatic Outreach Center on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Name</Label>
        <String>Rise of the Drath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Desc</Label>
        <String>The Drath, savvy survivors of lost Elemental, have charted their way through the stars at a deliberate pace. Now, with FTL travel in their toolkit and a newfound planetary roost, they're ready to unfurl their plans with a flair for the dramatic. Revenge against the Altarians simmers on the back burner, but the galaxy's a big place with plenty of room for subtlety and strategic plays. [BR][BR]As they ready themselves to mingle with the cosmic ensemble, the Drath must choose their approach. Will they be the cunning architects of alliances or the silent puppeteers of galactic intrigue? Their ancient fire burns anew, but it's their moves that will shape the next era.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Choice_AncientWisdom_Desc</Label>
        <String>Convene the Elders' Council</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Choice_AncientWisdom_Details</Label>
        <String>Establish a council chamber for the wisest of the Drath to guide their civilization with ancient knowledge and foresight. [BR][BR]Places an Elder's Council on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Choice_MilitaryPreparation_Desc</Label>
        <String>Strengthen Military Prowess</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Choice_MilitaryPreparation_Details</Label>
        <String>Focus on military training and preparedness, building grounds to train warriors, anticipating future conflicts with ancient adversaries. [BR][BR]Places a Warrior Training center on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Choice_CulturalHeritage_Desc</Label>
        <String>Preserve Dragon Cultural Heritage</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DrathAscendancy_Choice_CulturalHeritage_Details</Label>
        <String>Create a preserve to honor and maintain the rich mythos and cultural heritage of the Drath dragon lineage.[BR][BR]Places the Mythos of the Dragon Preserve on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Name</Label>
        <String>Altarian Spiritual Renaissance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the midst of a harmonious convergence, the Altarians gaze upon the galaxy with enlightened eyes. Their deep spiritual and arcane heritage, a beacon of their identity, calls forth a renewed purpose in the celestial dance of the cosmos. [BR][BR]Poised at the threshold of expansion, they stand contemplative, seeking to weave the ethereal strands of their mystical lineage into the tangible reality of interstellar relations. The time has come to choose: will they spread their ideals through gentle guidance or leverage their arcane might to shape the galaxy? Their decision will send ripples through the very fabric of existence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Choice_TempleOfEnlightenment_Desc</Label>
        <String>Construct the Temple of Enlightenment</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Choice_TempleOfEnlightenment_Details</Label>
        <String>Build a grand temple to serve as a beacon of wisdom and spiritual guidance, enlightening citizens and leaders alike.[BR][BR]Places a Temple of Enlightenment on Homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Choice_ArcaneSanctuary_Desc</Label>
        <String>Establish an Arcane Sanctuary</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Choice_ArcaneSanctuary_Details</Label>
        <String>Create a sanctuary for the study and practice of Altarian mystic arts, fostering magical research and arcane knowledge.[BR][BR]Places an Arcane Sanctuary on Homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Choice_CouncilOfSages_Desc</Label>
        <String>Form a Council of Sages</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianSpiritualAwakening_Choice_CouncilOfSages_Details</Label>
        <String>Convene a council of the wisest Altarians to offer guidance and foresight, ensuring benevolent and wise leadership.[BR][BR]Places a Council of Sages on Homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Name</Label>
        <String>Korath Rising</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Desc</Label>
        <String>The Korath were banished to Kora by the Drengin who thought they were too extreme.  Where the Drengin support enslaving inferior beings, the Korath do not recognize other species as being sentient but rather more akin to bugs that need to be exterminated. [BR][BR]Where the galaxy was previously very focused on the Drengin Empire, the Korath, due to their relative isolation, were largely left alone.  Now is their time to rise and to do what they were born to do, murder every other sentient being in the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Choice_WarMongerAltar_Desc</Label>
        <String>Erect the Altar of War Mongers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Choice_WarMongerAltar_Details</Label>
        <String>Build a monument to martial superiority, inspiring dread and dominance in the hearts of all Korath. [BR][BR]Places a Warmonger Altar on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Choice_ExterminationCamps_Desc</Label>
        <String>Establish Extermination Camps</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Choice_ExterminationCamps_Details</Label>
        <String>Set up systematic camps to deal with lesser species efficiently, proving the merciless prowess of the Korath's rule.[BR][BR]Places an Extermination Camp on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Choice_BattleThrallArena_Desc</Label>
        <String>Construct the Battle Thrall Arenas</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_KorathDominionRising_Choice_BattleThrallArena_Details</Label>
        <String>Create arenas to test and hone the Korath's combat artistry, a gruesome spectacle that reinforces their fearsome reputation.[BR][BR]Places a Battle Thrall Arena on homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
      
      


<!--  Planetary Improvement Text -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GlobalWellnessInitiative_Name</Label>
        <String>Global Wellness Initiative</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GlobalWellnessInitiative_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A comprehensive mental health and well-being program designed to help humanity adapt to the new reality of interstellar relations and the challenges of space colonization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>StabilityCorps_Name</Label>
        <String>Stability Corps</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>StabilityCorps_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A specialized task force focused on maintaining public order, ensuring civil stability, and addressing societal disruptions in the wake of our transition to an interstellar community.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EconomicExpansionCouncil_Name</Label>
        <String>Economic Council</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EconomicExpansionCouncil_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Harnessing the economic opportunities to increase population social skills.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>AggressiveColonizationProgram_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonization Program</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>AggressiveColonizationProgram_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the ratio the population that have a citizen representative.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ArceanExpansionCelebration_Name</Label>
        <String>Expansion Celebration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ArceanExpansionCelebration_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A worldwide celebration of the glory of the Arcean peopole.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ResistanceCenter_Name</Label>
        <String>Resistance Center</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ResistanceCenter_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases planetary defense and foreign influence resistance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TorianTelescope_Name</Label>
        <String>Torian Telescope</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TorianTelescope_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Greatly increases the sensor range of this world.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>DrenginTechCache_Name</Label>
        <String>Drengin Tech Cache</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DrenginTechCache_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A stockpile of advanced Drengin technology left over from the invasion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CulturalRevivalProgram_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Revival Initiative</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CulturalRevivalProgram_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A broad-based effort to reinvigorate our cultural heritage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EnforcedLaborCamps_Name</Label>
        <String>Enforced Labor Camps</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EnforcedLaborCamps_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Labor camps filled with slaves working for our glory.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TerrorSurveillanceNetwork_Name</Label>
        <String>Terror Surveillance Network</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TerrorSurveillanceNetwork_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>An expansive network of surveillance focused on preemptive identification and suppression of dissenting elements within the society.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrestDueToSpaceColonization_Name</Label>
        <String>Worldwide Turmoil: The Space Colonization Crisis</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrestDueToSpaceColonization_Desc</Label>
        <String>As our civilization embarks on the epochal journey of colonizing other planets, our homeworld is swept by a wave of riots and unrest. [BR][BR]The prospect of permanent settlements in space is fracturing societal norms, with some fearing loss of cultural identity and others anxious about unequal access to this new frontier. [BR][BR]Meanwhile, dreams of boundless opportunities and new beginnings fuel the chaos. In the midst of these competing sentiments, how will you navigate this transformative period in our history?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Negotiate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Negotiate with the protestors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Negotiate_Details</Label>
        <String>Attempt to negotiate with the protestors to end the riots. This will calm things for a time. But this isn't likely the last we'll hear of this.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Suppress_Desc</Label>
        <String>Suppress the protestors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Suppress_Details</Label>
        <String>Use force to suppress the protestors. This will work for a time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Ignore_Desc</Label>
        <String>Ignore the protestors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Ignore_Result</Label>
        <String>Riots</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GlobalUnrest_Choice_Ignore_Details</Label>
        <String>Ignore the protestors and hope they go away.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TheMachineExpansion_Name</Label>
        <String>The Machine Expansion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TheMachineExpansion_Desc</Label>
        <String>As our civilization stands on the threshold of interstellar expansion, internal divisions surface. [BR][BR]The leap from seclusion on our homeworld to exploring distant, life-bearing planets stirs a complex mix of anticipation and apprehension. Concerns about the unpredictable dynamics with organic life forms and the moral implications of such encounters vie with the excitement of discovering and interacting with diverse existences. In this pivotal chapter of our journey, how will you steer us through these uncharted waters of cosmic diplomacy and existential discovery?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ExpansionInfrastructure_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Synthesize Durantium to expedite our expansion of infrastructure</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SupportShipyard_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Send resources to our Shipyard</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InternalFocus_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Look inward and gain new knowledge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Name</Label>
        <String>Homeworld Political Issues Amidst Rapid Expansion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Desc</Label>
        <String>With the rapid expansion of our dominion, encompassing myriad new worlds, our homeworld finds itself grappling with escalating political tensions. [BR][BR]Diverse ideologies clash, as longstanding traditions and governance structures strain under the weight of integrating vastly different societies. Debates surge over resource allocation, cultural preservation, and representation of these new territories. As we stand at the crossroads of unity and division, the question looms: How shall we navigate and reconcile these growing pains to forge a cohesive and prosperous interstellar society?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Diplomacy_Desc</Label>
        <String>Engage in open dialogue to address concerns and integrate diverse perspectives for a more unified future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Diplomacy_Result</Label>
        <String>Our leader cares about us</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Diplomacy_Details</Label>
        <String>This approach may calm tensions and promote a sense of shared purpose among our populace, leading to greater stability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Authoritarian_Desc</Label>
        <String>Implement strict measures to ensure continued control and suppress dissenting voices.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Authoritarian_Details</Label>
        <String>Though effective in the short term, such a response could lead to long-term resistance and unrest. Crime is reduced for awhile.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Reform_Desc</Label>
        <String>Initiate comprehensive governmental reforms to better represent our growing and diverse population.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalUnrest_Choice_Reform_Details</Label>
        <String>Reforms may be challenging and time-consuming to implement, but could ultimately strengthen our political foundations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Name</Label>
        <String>Political Crisis on the homeworld</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Desc</Label>
        <String>Mounting unrest is seizing our homeworld, presenting the global government with its gravest challenge yet. [BR][BR]The core of this turmoil is the contentious allocation of resources towards our ambitious colonization program. Disparities are emerging, with certain regions benefiting more than others. [BR][BR]Our planet, once a beacon of unity and planetary solidarity, now teeters on the edge, threatening to fall back into the divisive, territorial rivalries of our history. [BR][BR]Political opportunists, seizing the moment, are stoking the flames of discord, exploiting cultural and regional differences to carve out their own spheres of influence. [BR][BR]As the leader of the colonization initiative, you've been endowed with extensive powers to address these challenges. Yet, exercise caution, as you've become a pivotal political figure in this unfolding drama. [BR][BR]Your advisors have laid out three potential courses of action. Each choice comes with its own set of consequences. Choose wisely.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_Negotiate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Seek a peaceful resolution by negotiating with opposition leaders to understand their grievances and reach a compromise.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_Negotiate_Details</Label>
        <String>Negotiations could pacify the opposition and foster a more inclusive governance, but may also weaken your perceived authority.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_MartialLaw_Desc</Label>
        <String>Enforce martial law to maintain order and suppress the brewing unrest through a display of military strength.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_MartialLaw_Details</Label>
        <String>Imposing martial law may deter potential uprisings but also risks alienating the populace and eroding democratic principles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_Decentralize_Desc</Label>
        <String>Begin the process to decentralize power.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_Decentralize_Details</Label>
        <String>Decentralization can promote self-governance. It will reduce homeworld manufacturing but increase it on the core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_Decentralize_Results</Label>
        <String>Decentralization of resources</String>
    </StringTable>
   
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Calls for Autonomy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Desc</Label>
        <String>As our colonial territories flourish under the distant light of foreign suns, a confluence of cultural uniqueness and self-reliance fuels their desire for greater autonomy.[BR][BR]Emanating from the far reaches of space, their voices reach the halls of power on the homeworld, fervently imploring for the right to govern their own destinies. [BR][BR]Should you accede to their demands, integrating their unique perspectives into the broader legislative structure, or staunchly uphold the centralized power of the homeworld?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Grant_Desc</Label>
        <String>Recognize the colonies' growth and maturity by granting them greater autonomy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Grant_Result</Label>
        <String>Greater Autonomy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Grant_Details</Label>
        <String>Autonomy could engender a sense of responsibility and loyalty amongst the colonies, yet may also pave the way for calls of independence. It will also increase colonial economic output but reduce the income coming from colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Integrate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Offer a compromise through deeper integration.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Integrate_Details</Label>
        <String>Integration promises inclusivity and unity, though it demands significant bureaucratic reorganization and could be seen as merely symbolic by the colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Deny_Desc</Label>
        <String>Refuse the demands for greater autonomy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialAutonomyDemands_Choice_Deny_Details</Label>
        <String>Denying autonomy safeguards centralized authority and simplifies governance, but risks inciting resentment or even rebellion among the colonial populace. Be careful.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Name</Label>
        <String>The Interstellar Commerce Clash</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Desc</Label>
        <String>Emerging from the burgeoning marketplaces of our colonial outposts is a tapestry of economic strife and competition that reverberates back to our homeworld. [BR][BR]Merchant guilds from across the stars, emboldened by offworld trade and newfound riches, are challenging the traditional monopolies and tariff laws. They demand economic reforms that could redefine our very understanding of wealth distribution and market control in this new interstellar age.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Protect_Desc</Label>
        <String>Uphold the current economic protocols to protect established homeworld businesses.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Protect_Details</Label>
        <String>A protective stance may comfort the old guard and keep socioeconomic structures intact, yet risks stifling innovation and colonial development. Increases homeworld wealth while reducing it on other core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Protect_Result</Label>
        <String>Homeworld Favoritism</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Liberalize_Desc</Label>
        <String>Embrace the commercial revolution by liberalizing trade policies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Liberalize_Details</Label>
        <String>Liberalization promises an economic boom and colonial growth but could incur unrest at home from those left behind in the wealth race.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Liberalize_Result</Label>
        <String>Liberalized economic policy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Regulate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Introduce new regulations to ensure fair trade across the empire, balancing colonial growth with the homeworld's prosperity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Regulate_Details</Label>
        <String>New regulations aim to level the playing field, but excessive bureaucracy could burden businesses and dampen economic enthusiasm.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarCommerceClash_Choice_Regulate_Result</Label>
        <String>Economic Regulations</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Resource Crisis</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Desc</Label>
        <String>The rapid growth of colonies has stretched our resources thin.[BR][BR]Planetary governors send desperate communiques, their words laced with urgency as they paint grim portraits of depleting resource caches. The specter of scarcity looms over our burgeoning colonies — a challenge that could thwart our extraterrestrial ascent and sow the seeds of discontent.[BR][BR]How should we respond?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Subvention_Desc</Label>
        <String>Inject capital and resources to stabilize the colonial economies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Subvention_Details</Label>
        <String>Subventions can quickly alleviate the crisis, but risk creating dependency and siphoning resources from the homeworld's reserves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Investigate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Launch a thorough investigation into the causes of the resource shortages to find sustainable long-term solutions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Investigate_Results</Label>
        <String>Ongoing Investigation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_MartialLaw_Result</Label>
        <String>Martial Law</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Investigate_Details</Label>
        <String>Investigation could uncover inefficiencies or new opportunities; however, the delay may worsen the immediate crisis and create unrest on all our core worlds for a year.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Ignore_Desc</Label>
        <String>Stay the course. Colonial ingenuity will prevail without intervention.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialResourceCrisis_Choice_Ignore_Details</Label>
        <String>Ignoring the problem may uphold economic autonomy, yet it bears the risk of unrest and the potential collapse of vulnerable colonies. A rebellion movement will form.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldPoliticalCrisis_Choice_Negotiate_Result</Label>
        <String>Tensions over rapid Colonization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarPoliticalStrain_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Political Strain</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_InterstellarPoliticalStrain_Desc</Label>
        <String>The rapid expansion of our civilization has led to significant political challenges on the homeworld.[BR][BR]There is a growing concern that we have colonized too fast without the necesssary infrastructure to support all these colonies.[BR][BR]Meanwhile, our citizens on our core worlds are feeling they are being treated as second class citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_DiplomaticIntegration_Desc</Label>
        <String>Seek a diplomatic approach to integrate the new worlds, promoting understanding and cooperation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_DiplomaticIntegration_Details</Label>
        <String>This approach may increase overall happiness and trade, but could also lead to slower decision-making, increasing the amount of resources lost in transit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_DiplomaticIntegration_Result</Label>
        <String>Temporary integration policy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_AuthoritarianControl_Desc</Label>
        <String>Too bad for the colonists. Impose strict control from the homeworld to ensure uniform governance across our colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_AuthoritarianControl_Results</Label>
        <String>Homeworld controls</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_AuthoritarianControl_Details</Label>
        <String>This might lead to greater efficiency and security, but could also increase unrest in the newly integrated worlds. A rebellion movement is likely to start.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_DecentralizedGovernance_Desc</Label>
        <String>Adopt a decentralized governance model, giving new worlds more autonomy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_DecentralizedGovernance_Details</Label>
        <String>While this could lead to increased innovation and local satisfaction, it might also result in weakened central authority.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_IPS_Choice_DecentralizedGovernance_Result</Label>
        <String>Decentralization</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Name</Label>
        <String>The Multiplanetary Unity Challenge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Desc</Label>
        <String>Cultural and political factions across our colonies are seeking varying degrees of autonomy and self-governance. Critics charge that we are engaging in a 'Colony Rush' and we must slow down. [BR][BR]The movement has gained momentum, challenging the central authority's ability to maintain a cohesive governance structure across multiple worlds. How will the leadership address these burgeoning calls for local control?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Choice_Integrate_Desc</Label>
        <String>Begin a campaign to reinforce the benefits of a strong central authority.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Choice_Integrate_Result</Label>
        <String>Homeworld Unity Pride</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Choice_Integrate_Details</Label>
        <String>An overarching integration initiative could solidify the empire’s cultural identity but may be perceived as oppressive by advocacy groups seeking independence. It will be popular on the homeworld. For awhile.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Choice_Autonomy_Desc</Label>
        <String>Grant greater autonomy to the colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_MultiplanetaryUnityChallenge_Choice_Autonomy_Details</Label>
        <String>Embracing autonomy can empower individual colonies and placate separatist movements, but it will reduce the amount of resources that colonies provide to core worlds even if the core worlds are happier.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Name</Label>
    <String>The Terraforming Dilemma</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our terraforming efforts have reached a critical juncture. Planetary engineers warn of ecological pushback from the aggressive alteration of entire ecosystems. Meanwhile, colonial settlers yearn for earthlike landscapes that remind them of the homeworld. The path we choose now could seal the fate of our environmental legacy and the biodiversity of new worlds for generations to come.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Expand_Desc</Label>
    <String>Accelerate our terraforming projects to rapidly achieve habitable environments. </String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Expand_Details</Label>
    <String>Expansion may provide swift habitability gains but could lead to unforeseen ecological disasters and galvanize environmentalist opposition. Will increase the planet quality of {PLANETNAME} by 1.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Conserve_Desc</Label>
    <String>Adopt a conservative approach to terraforming.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Conserve_Details</Label>
    <String>A conservative policy could ensure sustainable development and promote galactic biodiversity.  This will temporarily reduce the economic output of our core worlds.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Conserve_Result</Label>
    <String>Careful Terraforming</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Halt_Desc</Label>
    <String>Temporarily halt all terraforming activities to reassess their impact and explore alternative means of adaptation.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_TerraformingDilemma_Choice_Halt_Details</Label>
    <String>Halting the projects respects existing ecosystems and could lead to innovations in living on unaltered worlds, but may cause unrest among settlers awaiting terraformed lands. This will dramatically reduce the economic output of our core worlds for awhile..</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Name</Label>
    <String>Colonial Exodus Crisis</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Desc</Label>
    <String>A surge in emigration to new colonies has triggered a population vacuum on our homeworld, causing labor shortages, economic instability, and social unrest. Experts warn that the situation may become unsustainable if not addressed promptly. [BR][BR]You have certainly noticed this. How shall we navigate this delicate demographic conundrum?</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Choice_Restrict_Desc</Label>
    <String>Divert resources from the Shipyard to building up our homeworld for one year.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Choice_Incentivize_Desc</Label>
    <String>Let's create some clones.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Choice_Incentivize_Details</Label>
    <String>Adds some clones to our homeworld. This won't make our citizens happy.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Choice_Advance_Desc</Label>
    <String>Invest in advanced automation and infrastructure to compensate for labor losses.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Choice_Advance_Desc_Details</Label>
    <String>Provides some automicons to our world. Hopefully they won't rise against us. But they probably will.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialExodusCrisis_Choice_Incentivize_Result</Label>
    <String>No one likes clones</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Name</Label>
    <String>Colonial Rush Repercussions</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Desc</Label>
    <String>Our rapid colonization has outpaced its societal and infrastructural development, leading to sprawling, undeveloped colonies and overstretched supply chains. How will you address these systemic issues?</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Reassess_Desc</Label>
    <String>Temporarily reduce further colonization efforts to focus on enhancing the existing colonies, fostering faster growth and integration.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Reassess_Result</Label>
    <String>Temporarily Shipyard Moratorium</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Reassess_Details</Label>
    <String>A moratorium might stabilize your core territories at the expense of losing the initiative in space expansion to rival factions. Our Shipyard production will be dramatically reduced for a year.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Reallocate_Result</Label>
    <String>Colonial Reallocation Program</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Reallocate_Desc</Label>
    <String>Reallocating resources from homeworld to established core worlds.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Reallocate_Details</Label>
    <String>This approach will cost a lot of money on our home world for a year but greatly increase production on core worlds for a year.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Protect_Desc</Label>
    <String>Implement social policies to protect the vulnerable populations.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Protect_Details</Label>
    <String>This policy will cost money for a time but will improve morale for the next year.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushRepercussions_Choice_Protect_Result</Label>
    <String>Temporary Social Policy</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Name</Label>
    <String>Colonial Rush Backlash</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Desc</Label>
    <String>The rapid colonization of new worlds has led to overextended supply lines, neglected infrastructures, and disgruntled populations. We must take steps to stabilize our burgeoning galactic civilization.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Choice_Consolidate_Desc</Label>
    <String>Focus on strengthening the infrastructure and society of current colonies before embarking on new excursions.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Choice_Consolidate_Details</Label>
    <String>This will cost money for the next year but prevent riots.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Choice_Redistribution_Desc</Label>
    <String>Redistribute resources from core worlds to peripheral colonies to alleviate pressures and inequities caused by hasty expansion.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Choice_Redistribution_Details</Label>
    <String>Resource redistribution will help newly established colonies but could lead to contention and reduced productivity on core worlds.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Choice_EconomicStimulus_Desc</Label>
    <String>Inject capital into fledgling colonies to jumpstart their economies.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ColonialRushBacklash_Choice_EconomicStimulus_Details</Label>
    <String>An economic boost could hasten the development of new colonies at the risk of sparking inflation and economic bubbles. Core world manufacturing will be increased for two years.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Name</Label>
    <String>Failed Assassination Attempt</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Desc</Label>
    <String>A recent assassination attempt on your life has been narrowly thwarted. This incident seems to be a direct result of widespread discontent among our citizens over our aggressive colonization policy. The homeworld is in turmoil, with people divided and fearful. How will you address this crisis and restore order?</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Choice_Investigate_Desc</Label>
    <String>Launch a Thorough Investigation</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Choice_Investigate_Details</Label>
    <String>By choosing to investigate, you are looking to uncover the mastermind behind the assassination attempt. This might lead to the discovery of a larger conspiracy, but could also draw resources away from other important matters.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Choice_SecurityIncrease_Desc</Label>
    <String>Increase Security Measures</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Choice_SecurityIncrease_Details</Label>
    <String>By increasing security measures, you prioritize the immediate safety of yourself and key figures in your administration. This action could reassure the public but may also be seen as an overreaction, potentially causing unrest.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_FailedAssassinationAttempt_0x523_Choice_SecurityIncrease_Results</Label>
    <String>Increased Security</String>
  </StringTable>
  

    <StringTable>
        <Label>NeuralNexusComplex_Name</Label>
        <String>Neural Nexus Complex</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>NeuralNexusComplex_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Connects the minds of Yor increasing their intelligence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>QuantumProcessingUnit_Name</Label>
        <String>Quantum Processing Unit</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>QuantumProcessingUnit_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows core worlds to increase their processing power for greater research.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>SelfReplicatingFactory_Name</Label>
        <String>Self-Replicating Factory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>SelfReplicatingFactory_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>An automated industrial complex that auto generates its own resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>AncientKnowledgeRepository_Name</Label>
        <String>Ancient Archive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>AncientKnowledgeRepository_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A vault of wisdom from bygone eras containing ancient lore.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BioDigitalFusionCenter_Name</Label>
        <String>Bio-Digital Fusion Center</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BioDigitalFusionCenter_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By digitizing knowledge, greatly increase our population growth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticDiplomacyHub_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Diplomacy Hub</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticDiplomacyHub_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>The central nexus for interstellar relations increasing our diplomacy ability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EldersCouncilChamber_Name</Label>
        <String>Elders' Council Chamber</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EldersCouncilChamber_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A revered convocation hall where the wisdom of the ages is convened to guide the future of the civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>WarriorTrainingGrounds_Name</Label>
        <String>Warrior Training Grounds</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>WarriorTrainingGrounds_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A specialized facility dedicated to honing the skills increasing our soldiering ability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DragonMythosPreserve_Name</Label>
        <String>Dragon Mythos Preserve</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DragonMythosPreserve_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A sanctuary safeguarding the ancient traditions and legendary tales of dragons bringing our people together and eliminating crime.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TempleOfEnlightenment_Name</Label>
        <String>Temple of Enlightenment</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TempleOfEnlightenment_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A sacred place dedicated to intellectual and spiritual growth increasing the influence of our world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ArcaneSanctuary_Name</Label>
        <String>Arcane Sanctuary</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ArcaneSanctuary_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A secluded retreat for the mystically inclined, where ancient magics and esoteric knowledge converge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CouncilOfSages_Name</Label>
        <String>Council of Sages</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CouncilOfSages_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>An assembly of the wisest individuals tasked with preserving and imparting knowledge, offering counsel on matters of great importance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>WarMongerAltar_Name</Label>
        <String>War Monger's Altar</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>WarMongerAltar_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>A sinister shrine dedicated to the glorification of conflict resulting on all ships constructed here being veterans.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BattleThrallArena_Name</Label>
        <String>Battle Thrall Arena</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BattleThrallArena_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>An arena where our thralls fight and die for our amusement.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ExterminationCamps_Name</Label>
        <String>Extermination Camps</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ExterminationCamps_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>These efficient camps convert sub-Drengin species into valuable nutrients and other resources to fuel our cleansing of the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DrenginUnique_WeaponSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Energy Weapons Amplifier</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DrenginUnique_WeaponSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>Channels energy to magnify the beam weapon output of other ships in the fleet.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ClonesTurningIntoFleshEatingZombies_Name</Label>
        <String>Clone Mutation Crisis</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ClonesTurningIntoFleshEatingZombies_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a horrifying turn of events, our efforts to boost population on our homeworld through cloning have backfired. The clones have undergone a drastic and unexpected mutation, turning them into flesh-eating zombies. This epidemic poses a grave threat to the entire homeworld. Immediate action is required to prevent further catastrophe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ClonesTurningIntoFleshEatingZombies_Choice_1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Contain and Research the Mutation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ClonesTurningIntoFleshEatingZombies_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>Our best course of option is to find the zombies and load them onto a colony ship and ship them off somewhere deep into the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_0x8D4_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Economic Strike</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_0x8D4_Desc</Label>
        <String>A major strike has broken out across our colonies. The colonists are protesting against our homeworld-centric economic policies, which they feel have neglected their needs and contributions. This widespread unrest demands immediate attention and a reassessment of our policies.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Address the Colonists' Concerns</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>By choosing to address the concerns of the colonists, we acknowledge their grievances and work towards a more equitable distribution of resources and opportunities. This may require rethinking our current economic strategies to prevent future unrest. This will cost us some control.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Crush them.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_2_Details</Label>
        <String>The colonists need to quit thinking of themselves as 'people'. Their whole point is to serve the home world.</String>
      </StringTable> 
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_3_Desc</Label>
        <String>Let them strike.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_3_Details</Label>
        <String>The strike will take care of itself. For about a year, however, there will be a lot of crime on our colonies.</String>
      </StringTable> 
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_ColonialStrike_Choice_3_Results</Label>
        <String>Colonial Strike.</String>
      </StringTable> 

      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorAICatastrophe_0x7C4_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor AI Defense Protocol Tragedy</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorAICatastrophe_0x7C4_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a tragic misunderstanding, the Precursor AI we activated on {PLANETNAME} has identified our own people as intruders and unleashed its defense protocols. This catastrophic misjudgment has resulted in a massive loss of life. We must act swiftly to prevent further disaster.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorAICatastrophe_Choice_Shutdown_Desc</Label>
        <String>Immediately Shut Down the AI</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PrecursorAICatastrophe_Choice_Shutdown_Details</Label>
        <String>Shutting down the AI is the only option to immediately cease its fatal protocols. While this stops further loss of life, the decision will remove the benefits the AI provided.</String>
      </StringTable>
      
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldEfficiencyBoost_0x9A2_Name</Label>
        <String>Homeworld Efficiency Investigation is Complete</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldEfficiencyBoost_0x9A2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Our extensive investigation into enhancing homeworld efficiency has borne fruit. We have developed a series of groundbreaking policies and techniques that will significantly increase our manufacturing capabilities, catapulting our production capacity to new heights.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldEfficiencyBoost_Choice_Implement_Desc</Label>
        <String>Implement the New Efficiency Policies</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldEfficiencyBoost_Choice_Implement_Details</Label>
        <String>By implementing these new policies, we stand on the brink of a manufacturing revolution. This will not only boost our production but also set a new standard for efficiency and innovation on our homeworld.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_HomeworldEfficiencyBoost_Choice_Implement_Result</Label>
        <String>Efficiency Policy</String>
      </StringTable>  

      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CoretapDestabilization_0x8D3_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Coretap Destabilization</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CoretapDestabilization_0x8D3_Desc</Label>
        <String>The ancient coretap we made use of on {PLANETNAME}, once thought to be a boon, has now caused severe destabilization of our planet's core. This has triggered environmental catastrophes and poses a threat to all life. We must act swiftly to mitigate this disaster.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CoretapDestabilization_Choice_Contain_Desc</Label>
        <String>Initiate Containment Measures</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CoretapDestabilization_Choice_Contain_Details</Label>
        <String>We will save the planet but it will never be quite the same.</String>
      </StringTable>
      
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordShipSummoned_0x9C6_Name</Label>
        <String>Dread Lord Ship Emergence</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordShipSummoned_0x9C6_Desc</Label>
        <String>YOu may recall the Dread Lord archive we found on {PLANETNAME}.  You may also recall we decided to use it. [BR][BR]Unfortunately, our interaction with the Dread Lord archive has had an unforeseen and alarming consequence. A massive Dread Lord ship has been summoned into a nearby star system. This formidable vessel poses a significant threat to our security and demands immediate attention.</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordShipSummoned_Choice_Engage_Desc</Label>
        <String>Prepare to Engage the Dread Lord Ship</String>
      </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreadLordShipSummoned_Choice_Engage_Details</Label>
        <String>The Dread Lord ship should be easy to find. It will be the one bristling with weapons of death.</String>
      </StringTable>
      
      <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingCatastrophe_0xF13_Name</Label>
        <String>Catastrophic Terraforming Failure</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingCatastrophe_0xF13_Desc</Label>
        <String>The reckless approach we took on {PLANETNAME} to terraforming has backfired, leading to a severe ecological collapse on the planet.  A massive release of toxic gasses from below the mantle of the planet has killed the entire planet.[BR][BR]While the toxic fumes are short-lived, the death of our colonists is quite real.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingCatastrophe_Choice_Repair_Desc</Label>
        <String>We will need to bring new colonists.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TerraformingCatastrophe_Choice_Repair_Details</Label>
        <String>With all life gone we will have to transport new colonists to the planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_UniversalTranslatorTourism_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Tourism Initiative</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_UniversalTranslatorTourism_Desc</Label>
        <String>The breakthrough in Universal Translator technology has opened a gateway for interspecies communication, turning our planet into a potential hub for interstellar tourism. This presents us with a unique opportunity: to become a crossroads for galactic civilizations, where knowledge, culture, and commerce can be exchanged freely and efficiently. As we contemplate this prospect, we must consider the infrastructural and diplomatic challenges it poses. [BR][BR]Put another way, we have an opportunity to make some tourism income from alien visitors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_UniversalTranslatorTourism_Choice_Welcome_Desc</Label>
        <String>Let's construct the Galactic Nexus Pavilion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_UniversalTranslatorTourism_Choice_Welcome_Details</Label>
        <String>We should proceed with caution with this as this will make some people very unhappy on our world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_UniversalTranslatorTourism_Choice_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>We are not turning our homeworld into an amusement park.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_UniversalTranslatorTourism_Choice_Welcome_Results</Label>
        <String>Dislike alien tourism policy</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Contamination Concern</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Desc</Label>
        <String>There is a wave of revulsion sweeping through our ranks. [BR][BR]The citizenry abhors the very thought of intermingling with the galaxy's lesser beings as a result of our exploration. They dread not just the dilution of our superior genetics but the erosion of our hallowed culture, the tainting of our sacred bloodlines, and the defilement of our ancestral legacies. [BR][BR]The people for look to your decisive leadership to safeguard our purity as we cast our shadow across the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Choice_0_Desc</Label>
        <String>Implement the Crucible of Pain enhancement on our Homeworld to harden our populace.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Choice_0_Details</Label>
        <String>The Crucible of Pain will reinforce our citizens' strength and purity, ensuring the superiority of our kind.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Choice_1_Desc</Label>
        <String>Dispatch those who express fear to the front lines in colony ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Choice_1_Details</Label>
        <String>By facing the unknown, our people will either return victorious or not at all. The weak will be weeded out.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Choice_2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Perhaps we should be more open to other species and realize that we are no better than anyone else.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_Choice_2_Details</Label>
        <String>This controversial decree may be seen as a weakness by many, challenging the very core of our beliefs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FearOfContaimination_0x5C3B_OurLeaderIsAWeakling</Label>
        <String>Our leader is a weakling.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CrucibleOfPain_Name</Label>
        <String>Crucible of Pain</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CrucibleOfPain_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Turns our weaklings into formidable soldiers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    


    
 </StringTableList>  