<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C35_GourmetGala_Name</Label>
        <String>The Gourmet Gala</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C35_GourmetGala_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your trusted leaders, once aspired to be a chef and harbored dreams of opening their own restaurant.[BR][BR]      News of this culinary inclination has reached the ears of the Torian Confederation. Their delegates have proposed a Galactic Gourmet Gala, a grand banquet featuring cuisines from all corners of the galaxy. They have requested that {LEADERNAME} personally prepare a signature dish representing our civilization for this prestigious event.[BR][BR]Our advisors are concerned, pointing out that while the Gala could boost our diplomatic relations, a poorly received dish might lead to humiliation and decrease our standing with other races.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C35_GourmetGala_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Agree to the Gala.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C35_GourmetGala_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You agree to participate in the Gala. {LEADERNAME} is thrilled at the opportunity to showcase their culinary skills. The potential gain in diplomatic favor and influence is substantial, but there is a risk of diplomatic embarrassment if the dish is not well received.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C35_GourmetGala_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Decline the Gala.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C35_GourmetGala_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is disappointed, but understands the decision. By avoiding the risk of a culinary disaster, you ensure that your standing with other civilizations remains unchanged. However, this decision may have missed a significant opportunity to strengthen diplomatic bonds and expand our influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Name</Label>
        <String>The Factory Child</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Result</Label>
        <String>The Factory Child</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Desc</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME}, one of your most trusted advisors, was raised by squatters in a destitute factory in the outer rim of your civilization's territory. Recently, a message arrived from the factory, claiming that it is now facing a crisis. A ruthless corporate entity wants to take over the land to build a high-tech facility, displacing the squatters who have called it home for generations.[BR][BR]{GOVERNORNAME} has appealed to you for help, asking if the government can intervene to negotiate a resolution between the squatters and the corporation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Defend the factory.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to defend the factory and its inhabitants, sending government negotiators to work out a deal with the corporation. This act of compassion earns you the loyalty and gratitude of the squatters, resulting in a small but dedicated group of new citizens who will work tirelessly for your cause. [BR][BR]However, the corporation is not pleased resulting in a temporary reduction in manufacturing output on your homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the corporate takeover.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_FactoryChild_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Deciding that progress is more important than sentimentality, you allow the corporation to proceed with their plans.[BR][BR]The high-tech facility will bring jobs and technological advancements to your civilization, boosting your economy.[BR][BR]However, this decision greatly disappoints {GOVERNORNAME}, who loses faith in your leadership and may harbor resentment in the future.[BR][BR]The displaced squatters struggle to find new homes and lives, causing a temporary but significant increase in unrest and crime in your territories.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_CulinaryDream_Name</Label>
        <String>Culinary Dream</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_CulinaryDream_Dec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME}, one of your most trusted advisors, has confided in you their lifelong dream of opening a restaurant. They were once trained as a chef and have always felt a strong connection to the culinary arts. They've recently discovered an opportunity to open a restaurant on a bustling trade planet, where exotic ingredients and diverse clientele abound. {GOVERNORNAME} seeks your advice and support in pursuing this dream.[BR][BR]Our advisors warn that the time and resources {GOVERNORNAME} would need to invest in the restaurant could impact their focus on their current responsibilities to our civilization. However, they also note that this venture could boost morale and cultural exchange.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_CulinaryDream_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support their dream.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_CulinaryDream_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support {GOVERNORNAME}'s dream. They invest time and resources into the restaurant, which becomes a popular cultural hub provides a temporary boost of approval on your worlds.[BR][BR]However, their divided attention results in a temporary decrease in their productivity and effectiveness in their current role resulting in decreased diligence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_CulinaryDream_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage focus on duties.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_CulinaryDream_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You encourage {GOVERNORNAME} to remain focused on their current responsibilities to our civilization.[BR][BR]They reluctantly agree, but their unfulfilled dream may cause some minor discontentment and lower their overall satisfaction in their role. This could potentially affect their loyalty in the future but increases their diligence significantly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_CultRevelation_Name</Label>
        <String>Cult Revelation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_CultRevelation_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who has been a trusted member of your government, once fell victim to a brainwashing cult. They had managed to break free from the cult's control, but now, disturbing news has reached us: the cult is not only still active but has been expanding its influence throughout the galaxy. They have been infiltrating other governing bodies and using mind-controlled pawns to manipulate political decisions.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} is deeply troubled by this revelation and wishes to help bring down the cult that almost destroyed their life. But this action would require resources and risk exposing the dark past of {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_CultRevelation_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the cult's downfall.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_CultRevelation_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to support {LEADERNAME} in their quest to bring down the cult. This will require allocating resources and personnel to investigate and dismantle the cult's operations. [BR][BR]While this will strengthen your civilization's resistance to foreign influence in the long run, it will also strain your budget and expose {LEADERNAME}'s past, potentially affecting their reputation and effectiveness in their current position.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_CultRevelation_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Focus on our civilization's interests.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_CultRevelation_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>You decide that the well-being of your civilization comes first and choose not to support {LEADERNAME}'s personal crusade against the cult. [BR][BR]While this may save resources, there is a possibility that the cult's influence may continue to spread unchecked, posing a potential threat to your civilization and others in the future. [BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} will also be disheartened by your decision, possibly affecting their loyalty and dedication to their duties.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <!-- <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Claustrophobia_Name</Label>
        <String>Claustrophobic Crisis</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Claustrophobia_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a key figure in your government, is known to suffer from severe claustrophobia. This fear of confined spaces has made their service on spacecraft nearly unbearable.[BR]Recently, {LEADERNAME} has expressed their concern about an upcoming diplomatic mission which requires them to travel on a spaceship for an extended period. They have requested alternative arrangements, but our advisors warn that it may be seen as a sign of weakness or insult to the other party.[BR]The choice lies with you: accommodate {LEADERNAME}'s request or insist on their participation in the mission.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Claustrophobia_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Accommodate their request.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Claustrophobia_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to accommodate {LEADERNAME}'s request, showing empathy and concern for their well-being. This boosts morale among your people but may be interpreted as a sign of weakness by foreign governments, potentially damaging diplomatic relations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Claustrophobia_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Insist on their participation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Claustrophobia_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You insist that {LEADERNAME} participate in the diplomatic mission, prioritizing the importance of maintaining a strong image. This decision may strain your relationship with {LEADERNAME} but it sends a clear message of strength to other civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable> -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Inheritance_Name</Label>
        <String>The Disinherited</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Inheritance_Desc</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME} has always been consumed by resentment over being excluded from their family's inheritance. Recently, a new opportunity has arisen to claim a portion of that fortune. A mysterious individual with access to confidential family documents has contacted {GOVERNORNAME}, offering to help them prove their rightful claim to the inheritance in exchange for certain political favors.[BR][BR]Our advisors warn that this individual may have ulterior motives and that the information could be fabricated. They suggest that {GOVERNORNAME} should either pursue the inheritance with caution or let go of the bitterness and move on.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Inheritance_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Pursue the inheritance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Inheritance_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You decide to allow {GOVERNORNAME} to pursue the fortune, susceptible to a inheritance tax of course.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Inheritance_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Let go of the bitterness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Inheritance_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME} heeds your advice and decides to let go of the bitterness, focusing on their responsibilities within your government. As a result, they gain the Focused trait, improving their overall effectiveness. However, there will always be a lingering resentment, and {GOVERNORNAME} may be more susceptible to future temptations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8B7C_DuelScar_Name</Label>
        <String>The Duel's Aftermath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8B7C_DuelScar_Dec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME}, a distinguished figure in your government, had once won a duel against a romantic rival, leaving them with a prominent scar as a reminder.[BR][BR]Recently, the defeated rival has re-emerged, now a prominent figure in a competing empire, and has challenged {GOVERNORNAME} to a rematch. While the duel would be an excellent opportunity for {GOVERNORNAME} to showcase their prowess and strengthen their reputation, it could also lead to a diplomatic incident with the rival's empire.[BR][BR]Our advisors are torn; some believe the duel could boost morale, while others fear the potential consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8B7C_DuelScar_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Allow the rematch.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8B7C_DuelScar_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You allow the rematch to take place. If {GOVERNORNAME} wins, their reputation will be strengthened, boosting morale and loyalty within your ranks. However, the defeated rival's empire may take offense, potentially straining diplomatic relations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8B7C_DuelScar_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Forbid the duel.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8B7C_DuelScar_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME} begrudgingly accepts your decision, but their pride is wounded, causing a temporary drop in their effectiveness. On the other hand, you avoid a diplomatic incident with the rival's empire, which could have led to more significant troubles down the line.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BA3_NobleLineage_Name</Label>
        <String>The Noble Lineage</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BA3_NobleLineage_Dec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME} is a descendant of minor nobility, and has recently been approached by a distant relative who claims to have unearthed a long-lost family treasure. They propose an expedition to recover the artifact, which could hold significant cultural and historical value. However, the journey will be dangerous and resource-intensive, and detractors argue that our focus should be on our current struggles, not the past.[BR][BR]Will you support {GOVERNORNAME}'s quest to recover their family's ancient treasure, or deny them the resources and focus on more immediate concerns?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BA3_NobleLineage_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the expedition.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BA3_NobleLineage_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support the expedition. The journey is treacherous, but if successful, the treasure could provide invaluable insight into the history and culture of {GOVERNORNAME}'s ancestors. This may lead to increased influence and prestige for your civilization. However, the resources diverted to the expedition may hinder your ability to respond to more immediate threats.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BA3_NobleLineage_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Deny the expedition.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BA3_NobleLineage_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By denying the expedition, you conserve valuable resources for your civilization's more pressing needs. However, {GOVERNORNAME} is disappointed and may harbor resentment, potentially affecting their loyalty and performance in the future. Additionally, the opportunity to uncover a significant historical artifact is lost, and with it, the chance to elevate your civilization's cultural standing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Diplomat_Name</Label>
        <String>The Diplomat's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Diplomat_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your esteemed career diplomat, has come across a highly sensitive and classified file that could potentially cause a diplomatic crisis among several species in the galaxy. The information in the file could be used to gain a significant advantage in negotiations, but it could also lead to unrest and mistrust if discovered.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} is torn between using this knowledge for your civilization's benefit and staying true to their principles of diplomacy and integrity. They have come to you for guidance on how to handle this delicate situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Diplomat_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Use the information.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Diplomat_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to use the classified information to your advantage in negotiations. While this choice leads to favorable trade deals and treaties, it puts a strain on {LEADERNAME}'s conscience and may have unforeseen consequences if the truth is revealed. Your civilization gains a temporary diplomatic advantage, but at the risk of long-term trust and stability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Diplomat_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Preserve diplomatic integrity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Diplomat_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is relieved by your decision to uphold their principles of diplomacy and integrity. While the opportunity to gain an advantage in negotiations is lost, your civilization's reputation for fair and honest dealings is strengthened. This choice may not yield immediate benefits, but it solidifies your civilization's long-term standing among the galactic community, fostering trust and cooperation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x1CD9_Recovery_Name</Label>
        <String>Overcoming the Past</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x1CD9_Recovery_Desc</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME}, one of your most trusted leaders, was once plagued by a crippling drug addiction. Through sheer determination, they managed to overcome the addiction and now stand as a beacon of hope and resilience for many.[BR][BR]Recently, a new drug has emerged that is dangerously similar to the one {GOVERNORNAME} was once addicted to. As it spreads throughout the galaxy, we must decide how to address this threat and prevent it from causing more harm.[BR][BR]{GOVERNORNAME} has requested to be involved in the decision-making process, but some advisors worry that their past may cloud their judgment.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x1CD9_Recovery_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Involve {GOVERNORNAME} in the decision.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x1CD9_Recovery_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You trust {GOVERNORNAME}'s judgment and involve them in the decision-making process. Their personal experience becomes invaluable in formulating an effective strategy to combat the drug, but there is a slight risk that they may relapse under the pressure.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x1CD9_Recovery_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep {GOVERNORNAME} out of the decision.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x1CD9_Recovery_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to keep {GOVERNORNAME} out of the decision-making process to protect them from any potential triggers. This results in a more conservative approach to combating the drug, but it may take longer to see results and {GOVERNORNAME} may feel excluded and undervalued.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AFE_Engineer_Name</Label>
        <String>Engineering Enigma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AFE_Engineer_Dec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME}, a former engineer known for being easily distracted by minute details, has stumbled upon a technological marvel in the form of an ancient alien artifact. The artifact is believed to hold tremendous power and potential, but its secrets are locked away by a complex series of intricate puzzles and mechanisms.[BR][BR]{GOVERNORNAME} is eager to study the artifact and unlock its mysteries, but doing so will divert their focus from their current duties. Our advisors caution that other factions may also be interested in the artifact, and its true purpose could be dangerous.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AFE_Engineer_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Allow them to study the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AFE_Engineer_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You grant {GOVERNORNAME} permission to study the artifact. This decision will lead to a temporary reduction in their productivity and efficiency in their current role. However, if they successfully unlock the artifact's secrets, it could provide a significant technological advantage to your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AFE_Engineer_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep them focused on their duties.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AFE_Engineer_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME} remains focused on their duties, maintaining their current productivity and efficiency levels. However, the artifact remains a mystery, and there is a chance that another faction will discover and unlock its secrets, potentially gaining an advantage over your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C51_CoinFlip_Name</Label>
        <String>The Alien Coin</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C51_CoinFlip_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most trusted advisors, has always had a unique habit of constantly flipping an alien coin during decision-making processes. Recently, the coin has attracted the attention of a powerful interstellar collector, who claims that the coin is a rare artifact from a long-lost civilization and demands its return.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} is reluctant to part with the coin, as they believe it brings them luck and helps them make better decisions. The collector, however, is offering a substantial reward for the coin's return and has hinted at potential consequences if their demand is not met.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C51_CoinFlip_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Return the coin to the collector.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C51_CoinFlip_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to return the coin to the collector. While this decision grants your civilization a significant reward, {LEADERNAME}'s decision-making abilities suffer without their lucky coin, resulting in a temporary decrease in their effectiveness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C51_CoinFlip_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep the coin with {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C51_CoinFlip_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is grateful for your support and retains the lucky coin, maintaining their decision-making prowess. However, the collector is not pleased and may cause diplomatic complications in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GrammarEnforcer_Name</Label>
        <String>The Grammar Enforcer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GrammarEnforcer_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has a notorious reputation for violently enforcing the use of proper grammar. Recently, a video of {LEADERNAME} brutally correcting a subordinate's language mistake has gone viral, sparking heated debates across the galaxy.[BR][BR]This incident has led to a dilemma: Should we condemn {LEADERNAME}'s actions and risk losing their valuable expertise, or defend their extreme methods and face potential backlash from the public and other civilizations?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GrammarEnforcer_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Condemn the actions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GrammarEnforcer_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to condemn {LEADERNAME}'s actions. The public is pleased, leading to a temporary boost in approval ratings. However, {LEADERNAME} feels betrayed and their productivity and loyalty are significantly reduced for a period.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GrammarEnforcer_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Defend the methods.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GrammarEnforcer_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to defend {LEADERNAME}'s methods. Their productivity and loyalty are strengthened, but the public is outraged, leading to a temporary decrease in approval ratings. Additionally, other civilizations may view your support of such extreme actions as a sign of aggression.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Precursors_Name</Label>
        <String>The Precursor Enigma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Precursors_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your trusted advisors, believes that the Precursors still walk among us in disguise. They have gathered evidence suggesting that some individuals within our civilization may actually be these ancient beings. This revelation has the potential to cause panic and unrest among the population.[BR][BR]Our intelligence agency has analyzed the information and proposed two courses of action: we can either expose the alleged Precursors publicly or keep the information secret to avoid causing fear and chaos.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Precursors_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Expose the Precursors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Precursors_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to expose the alleged Precursors. While this decision may lead to short-term unrest and fear among the population, it could also result in long-term benefits as we learn from these ancient beings and gain access to their advanced knowledge. However, the Precursors may not react kindly to being exposed and could retaliate in unforeseen ways.[BR]+250 Research</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Precursors_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep the information secret.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Precursors_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to keep the information about the alleged Precursors secret. This decision maintains stability and prevents panic among the population. However, we may miss out on the opportunity to learn from these ancient beings and their advanced knowledge, and it's possible that the Precursors could be working against us, undetected.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Musical_Name</Label>
        <String>The Dreadful Melody</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Musical_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most beloved leaders, has a passion for singing, despite their dreadful sense of pitch, rhythm, and harmony. As a result, their performances are nothing short of disastrous.[BR][BR]Recently, {LEADERNAME} has been invited to participate in a charity singing event organized by various species in the galaxy. While their participation could raise a significant amount of funds for the cause, it could also cause widespread embarrassment and even diplomatic tensions.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest that we either support {LEADERNAME}'s performance or find a way to prevent them from participating in the event.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Musical_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage the performance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Musical_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to encourage {LEADERNAME}'s performance. While the charity event raises a considerable amount of funds, the disastrous performance causes a temporary decrease in diplomatic relations with other species and a decline in morale throughout your civilization. However, {LEADERNAME} gains the Loyal trait for your unwavering support.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Musical_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Prevent the performance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Musical_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You manage to prevent {LEADERNAME}'s performance by arranging for a holographic stand-in to perform in their place. The event goes smoothly, and your civilization's reputation remains intact. However, {LEADERNAME} is disappointed by your lack of faith in their abilities and loses the Loyal trait. The stand-in performance does raise funds for the charity, but not as much as {LEADERNAME}'s performance would have.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RelativisticReunion_Name</Label>
        <String>Relativistic Reunion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RelativisticReunion_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves your government, has a tragic past. On a long journey at relativistic speeds, they lost contact with their family due to the time dilation effects. [BR][BR]Recently, a message capsule from {LEADERNAME}'s family has been discovered, drifting in the void of space. It contains a heartfelt plea for a reunion, sent decades ago. The capsule also contains valuable information about a hidden resource cache.[BR][BR]Our advisors are conflicted: Should we prioritize the emotional reunion or focus on the potential resources that could benefit our civilization?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RelativisticReunion_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Arrange the reunion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RelativisticReunion_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to prioritize {LEADERNAME}'s emotional well-being and arrange the reunion. {LEADERNAME} is grateful, and their loyalty to your government strengthens. However, the resources from the cache remain undiscovered, potentially falling into the hands of rival civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RelativisticReunion_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Retrieve the resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RelativisticReunion_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to focus on the hidden resource cache, benefiting your civilization's growth and technological advancement. However, {LEADERNAME} is deeply hurt by this decision, and their loyalty to your government wavers. The reunion never takes place, leaving a rift in {LEADERNAME}'s heart.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PetNames_Name</Label>
        <String>The Naming Game</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PetNames_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a leader in your government, has a peculiar habit of assigning embarrassing pet names to their advisors. While some take it in stride, others are growing increasingly disgruntled. [BR]A group of advisors has approached you, asking for your intervention. They feel that the demeaning nicknames have gone too far and are affecting their professional reputation. [BR]Our analysts predict that addressing the issue could improve morale, but also potentially cause tension between you and {LEADERNAME}. On the other hand, doing nothing might lead to decreasing productivity among the unhappy advisors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PetNames_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Ask {LEADERNAME} to stop.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PetNames_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You approach {LEADERNAME} and diplomatically request that they stop assigning embarrassing pet names to their advisors. While they might feel slightly offended, the advisors' morale and productivity improve. However, your relationship with {LEADERNAME} could be strained in the long run, potentially affecting their loyalty to you.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PetNames_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Do nothing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PetNames_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to do nothing, allowing {LEADERNAME} to continue their naming game. While your relationship with {LEADERNAME} remains strong, the advisors' morale declines over time, leading to decreased productivity and potential internal conflicts. This could have negative consequences for your government's efficiency and stability in the long run.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C47_DuelingVoices_Name</Label>
        <String>The Dueling Voices</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C47_DuelingVoices_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a trusted advisor in your government, has always been known for their unique ability to make the right decisions, guided by two dueling voices in their head. [BR][BR]Recently, the voices have started to diverge more than ever before, causing {LEADERNAME} to doubt their own judgment. They have reached out to us, seeking guidance on how to handle this internal conflict.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest two possible approaches: Encourage {LEADERNAME} to rely on their instincts and continue listening to both voices, or recommend that they seek professional help to quiet the voices and develop alternative decision-making strategies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C47_DuelingVoices_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Trust their instincts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C47_DuelingVoices_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to trust {LEADERNAME}'s instincts and encourage them to continue relying on the dueling voices. Although this may lead to occasional indecisiveness, their track record of success remains a valuable asset to your government. The potential to unlock new strategic insights also increases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C47_DuelingVoices_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Seek professional help.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C47_DuelingVoices_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>You suggest {LEADERNAME} seeks professional help to quiet the voices and develop alternative decision-making strategies. While this may result in some temporary instability as they adjust to their new methods, it could potentially lead to more consistent and rational decision-making in the long term. However, the loss of the dueling voices might also result in less creative solutions to challenges faced by your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C21_DeathThreats_Name</Label>
        <String>The Menacing Threats</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C21_DeathThreats_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been receiving anonymous death threats on a daily basis, and the situation is growing unbearable. The origin of these threats remains unknown, leaving {LEADERNAME} in a constant state of unrest.[BR][BR]Our intelligence services have identified two potential courses of action: trace the source of these threats and confront the perpetrator, or increase {LEADERNAME}'s security detail to ensure their safety. Both options have their own risks and rewards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C21_DeathThreats_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Trace the source.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C21_DeathThreats_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You order our intelligence services to trace the source of the death threats. If successful, the perpetrator will be dealt with and {LEADERNAME} will be safe. However, this option requires resources and time, potentially diverting attention from other crucial matters.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C21_DeathThreats_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Increase security detail.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C21_DeathThreats_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to enhance {LEADERNAME}'s security detail, making it almost impossible for any harm to come to them. While this ensures their immediate safety, the unknown threat remains at large, possibly seeking new targets within your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Secret_Organization_Name</Label>
        <String>The Secret Watchers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Secret_Organization_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is a loyal and effective member of your government. However, it has recently come to your attention that they are also serving a secret organization that could eliminate them at any moment if they were to disobey or fail in their objectives. [BR][BR]The organization, known as "The Watchers," is shrouded in mystery, but they seem to have their own hidden agenda. They have recently contacted you, threatening to expose {LEADERNAME}'s connection to them unless you comply with their demands.[BR][BR]Your advisors are split on how to handle this situation. Some wish to negotiate with The Watchers, while others believe that confrontation is the best course of action to secure {LEADERNAME}'s safety and the integrity of your government.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Secret_Organization_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Negotiate with The Watchers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Secret_Organization_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to negotiate with The Watchers. As a result, you gain their favor and possible future assistance. However, your civilization's morale is affected negatively due to the perceived weakness and vulnerability to external forces.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Secret_Organization_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Confront The Watchers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Secret_Organization_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to confront The Watchers, sending a clear message that you will not be manipulated. While this move boosts your civilization's morale, it also puts {LEADERNAME}'s life in danger and potentially instigates a long-lasting conflict with the secretive organization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Synaesthesia_Name</Label>
        <String>The Synaesthetic Encounter</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Synaesthesia_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always experienced synaesthesia, a rare phenomenon causing the blending of senses, when communicating with alien species. Recently, while attending an interstellar summit, {LEADERNAME} encounters a previously unknown species, triggering an overwhelming wave of synaesthesia.[BR][BR]The experience reveals hidden patterns and connections within the aliens' language, opening up new diplomatic opportunities. However, {LEADERNAME} is left disoriented and exhausted, potentially affecting their performance in future negotiations.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest two ways to proceed: either encourage {LEADERNAME} to embrace this unique ability for the benefit of our civilization or arrange for a temporary leave of absence to recover and avoid potential diplomatic incidents.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Synaesthesia_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Embrace the ability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Synaesthesia_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to encourage {LEADERNAME} to embrace their synaesthesia. This leads to new diplomatic opportunities and a bonus to our relations with the alien species. However, {LEADERNAME} may become fatigued and less effective in future negotiations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Synaesthesia_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Grant leave of absence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Synaesthesia_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is granted a temporary leave of absence to recover from the overwhelming synaesthetic experience. This ensures that they remain sharp and effective in future negotiations but risks missing out on potential diplomatic opportunities with the new alien species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Skull_Name</Label>
        <String>The Nemesis' Skull</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Skull_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most trusted advisors, has a peculiar habit of carrying around the skull of their former nemesis as a reminder of their past victory.[BR][BR]Recently, the nemesis' family has contacted your civilization, demanding the return of the skull to them for a proper burial. They claim that it is an affront to their culture and a desecration of their ancestor's memory. They are threatening to turn other civilizations against you if their demands are not met.[BR][BR]Your advisors are split on the matter. Some believe that returning the skull would show respect for other cultures and promote diplomatic relations. Others argue that it would be a sign of weakness and would embolden your enemies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Skull_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Return the skull.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Skull_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to return the skull, showing respect for the nemesis' family and their culture. This will improve diplomatic relations with certain civilizations, but {LEADERNAME} will lose their unique memento, potentially affecting their resolve in future conflicts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Skull_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Refuse to return the skull.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Skull_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} continues to carry the skull, which boosts their resolve in conflicts. However, this decision angers the nemesis' family and their allies, resulting in strained diplomatic relations and potential repercussions from other civilizations in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_SilentPast_Name</Label>
        <String>The Silent Past</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_SilentPast_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has maintained a vow of silence for decades, communicating with no one, even during their rise to power within your civilization. Their mysterious past has piqued the interest of a prominent media outlet, and they have sent a journalist to investigate {LEADERNAME}'s reasons for maintaining this vow.[BR][BR]The journalist is persistent and could uncover sensitive information regarding {LEADERNAME}'s past. Our advisors recommend either cooperating with the journalist or attempting to suppress the story.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_SilentPast_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Cooperate with the journalist.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_SilentPast_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to cooperate with the journalist. {LEADERNAME}'s story of introspection and personal growth becomes a sensation, boosting your civilization's cultural influence and approval for several months. However, this newfound attention may attract unwanted interest from other civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_SilentPast_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Suppress the story.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_SilentPast_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to suppress the story. {LEADERNAME}'s past remains a mystery, but your government's actions to suppress the media will be seen as a breach of freedom of speech, resulting in a temporary decrease in approval. Additionally, there is a chance that the journalist may leak the story in the future, causing further damage to your reputation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Adrift_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Colony Ship</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Adrift_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves your government, was once trapped on a colony ship that drifted in space for many decades. The ship has been recently discovered, still adrift, with its occupants in cryogenic stasis. The ship's AI system failed, leaving the crew and colonists in their frozen state.[BR][BR]Our experts have informed us that, with some effort, we can safely revive the passengers and integrate them into our civilization, or we could salvage the ship's valuable resources to strengthen our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Adrift_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Revive the passengers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Adrift_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to revive the passengers, welcoming them into your civilization. This boosts your population, but requires significant resources and time to help them acclimate to their new lives in the 23rd century.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Adrift_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Salvage the ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Adrift_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to salvage the ship, gaining valuable resources and technology to upgrade your fleets. However, this decision weighs heavily on {LEADERNAME}, who mourns the loss of their fellow colonists.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C3D_Autobiography_Name</Label>
        <String>The Unfinished Autobiography</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C3D_Autobiography_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is known for their diligence in working on their autobiography every day, providing an in-depth look into their life and experiences. [BR][BR]Recently, a rival faction has managed to obtain an unpublished draft of the autobiography and threatens to leak sensitive information that could potentially harm our civilization's reputation.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest we either negotiate with the rival faction to prevent the leak or discredit the draft as a work of fiction.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C3D_Autobiography_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Negotiate with the rival faction.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C3D_Autobiography_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to negotiate with the rival faction. This prevents the leak of sensitive information, but at the cost of resources and a temporary decrease in diplomatic relations with the rival faction.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C3D_Autobiography_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Discredit the draft as fiction.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C3D_Autobiography_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} publicly dismisses the draft as a work of fiction, protecting your civilization's reputation. However, this choice may result in a loss of trust and credibility for {LEADERNAME} and the potential for future complications.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_UnfulfilledDream_Name</Label>
        <String>Unfulfilled Dream</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_UnfulfilledDream_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been a loyal servant to your government, but deep down, they have always harbored a secret bitterness about their missed opportunity to become a scientist. [BR][BR]Recently, they have been presented with a unique chance to work with a renowned team of scientists on a cutting-edge research project. {LEADERNAME} is now torn between their duty to your government and the opportunity to fulfill their lifelong dream.[BR][BR]They have come to you for guidance. Will you let them pursue their scientific aspirations, or insist they remain fully committed to their current position?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_UnfulfilledDream_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Let them join the project.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_UnfulfilledDream_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to allow {LEADERNAME} to temporarily join the scientific project. Their happiness and gratitude increase their loyalty and productivity. However, their temporary absence from their current position may have some negative impact on your government's efficiency.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_UnfulfilledDream_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep them in their position.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_UnfulfilledDream_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You remind {LEADERNAME} of their duty and insist they remain in their current position. Their bitterness may grow, potentially reducing their loyalty and effectiveness. However, no negative impact on your government's efficiency will occur due to their continued presence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C45_DarkPast_Name</Label>
        <String>The Dark Past</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C45_DarkPast_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always been a valuable asset to your government, but their refusal to be in poorly lit spaces due to an unknown childhood incident has been a challenge.[BR][BR]The situation has recently escalated as {LEADERNAME} has had to attend crucial meetings in a dimly lit conference room on a diplomatic space station. {LEADERNAME} has expressed their discomfort and fear, but missing these meetings could damage our reputation and relationship with other species.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest two options: either accommodate {LEADERNAME}'s fear by demanding the conference room lighting be improved or persuade {LEADERNAME} to face their fear for the greater good.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C45_DarkPast_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Accommodate their fear.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C45_DarkPast_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to accommodate their fear and demand better lighting at the conference room. While this boosts {LEADERNAME}'s loyalty and effectiveness, our insistence on such a seemingly trivial issue may cause other species to view us as weak or overly indulgent.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C45_DarkPast_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Persuade them to face their fear.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C45_DarkPast_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to persuade {LEADERNAME} to face their fear for the greater good. While this may strain their loyalty and cause temporary anxiety, our stance on the matter may earn respect from other species, showcasing our dedication to diplomacy and the ability to overcome personal issues for the greater good.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A25_Shadowless_Name</Label>
        <String>The Shadowless Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A25_Shadowless_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your trusted leaders, possesses a mysterious artifact from an ancient civilization which prevents them from casting a shadow. This unique characteristic has piqued the interest of a powerful and enigmatic organization, who have recently contacted your government to propose a deal.[BR][BR]They offer to share their vast knowledge of advanced technologies with your civilization in exchange for the artifact. However, they warn that without the artifact, {LEADERNAME} may lose their unique abilities and fall into obscurity.[BR][BR]The choice lies in your hands: Will you prioritize the advancement of your civilization, or preserve the uniqueness of {LEADERNAME}?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A25_Shadowless_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Trade the artifact for knowledge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A25_Shadowless_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to trade the artifact for the organization's knowledge. Your civilization gains access to advanced technologies, significantly boosting your research efforts. However, {LEADERNAME} loses their unique abilities and may struggle to maintain their influence and effectiveness in your government.[BR]+120 Research</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A25_Shadowless_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep the artifact and protect {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A25_Shadowless_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} retains their unique abilities and continues to be an influential leader in your government. However, your civilization misses out on the opportunity to gain advanced technologies from the enigmatic organization, and they may not be pleased with your decision to keep the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_HostageChild_Name</Label>
        <String>The Hostage Child</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_HostageChild_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} was raised by their parents' enemies as a hostage. Now, information has come to light that their captors, a powerful faction within the enemy civilization, are in a precarious situation and vulnerable to an attack.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} is torn between seeking revenge for their childhood and the opportunity to weaken the enemy or showing mercy and trying to build a bridge to promote peace. They seek your guidance on how to proceed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_HostageChild_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Seek revenge and weaken the enemy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_HostageChild_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to take advantage of the situation and strike at the vulnerable enemy faction. This will weaken them and give your civilization a strategic advantage. However, it may increase tensions and lead to further conflict down the line.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_HostageChild_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Show mercy and promote peace.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_HostageChild_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} decides to show mercy and use this opportunity to start a dialogue with the enemy faction. This will improve relations and possibly lead to lasting peace. However, the enemy may see this as a sign of weakness and exploit it in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_AncientBloodline_Name</Label>
        <String>The Last Heir</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_AncientBloodline_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, our trusted advisor, has recently discovered that they are the last living member of an ancient bloodline, one that can be traced back to the earliest days of our civilization.[BR][BR]As the heir to this legacy, they have been approached by a society of historians who have dedicated their lives to preserving the knowledge and artifacts left behind by their ancestors. They wish to grant {LEADERNAME} access to their vast collection of ancient knowledge, but warn that some of this information may have the potential to disrupt the stability of our society.[BR][BR]Our advisors are divided on this issue: some believe that the knowledge should be shared and used for the greater good, while others fear that it may cause more harm than good.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_AncientBloodline_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Embrace the knowledge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_AncientBloodline_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to embrace the ancient knowledge, granting {LEADERNAME} access to the historian society's archives. As a result, your civilization gains access to powerful new technologies, but risks unrest and upheaval as some of the information challenges long-held beliefs and societal norms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_AncientBloodline_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Decline the offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_AncientBloodline_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} declines the offer, choosing to maintain the stability of your society over the potential risks of the ancient knowledge. While this decision ensures societal harmony, it may also prevent your civilization from unlocking powerful technologies and information that could have propelled you further into the stars.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_ChildOfProphecy_Name</Label>
        <String>The Child of Prophecy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_ChildOfProphecy_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has a mysterious and enigmatic past, with whispers suggesting they might be the fabled "Child of Prophecy" destined to lead their people to either greatness or doom.[BR][BR]As the legend gains traction, the population is torn between excitement and fear. Some believe that {LEADERNAME} will usher in a new golden era, while others worry about the potential destruction they could bring.[BR][BR]Our advisors have presented two options: Embrace the prophecy and use it to rally our people, or attempt to quell the rumors and downplay {LEADERNAME}'s significance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_ChildOfProphecy_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Embrace the prophecy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_ChildOfProphecy_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to embrace the prophecy. This will significantly boost your civilization's morale and productivity, but also attract the attention of rival factions who may view {LEADERNAME} as a potential threat to be eliminated.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_ChildOfProphecy_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Quell the rumors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_ChildOfProphecy_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to quell the rumors and downplay {LEADERNAME}'s significance. This will maintain the status quo and prevent unnecessary conflicts, but also deny your civilization the potential benefits of rallying behind a legendary figure.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Document_Destroyer_Name</Label>
        <String>The Document Destroyer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Document_Destroyer_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is a valuable leader in your government, known for their preference for verbal communication over written documentation. [BR][BR]Recently, a highly classified document containing sensitive information was accidentally delivered to {LEADERNAME}, who proceeded to shred it without reading. The information within the document was crucial for a time-sensitive operation, and its loss could have severe consequences.[BR][BR]Our advisors are now debating whether to try to recreate the document from memory or to completely abandon the operation and focus on damage control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Document_Destroyer_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Recreate the document.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Document_Destroyer_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You decide to have your advisors attempt to recreate the document from memory. This will buy you some time, but there's a risk that the missing information may lead to errors in the operation and potential harm to your civilization's interests.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Document_Destroyer_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Abandon the operation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Document_Destroyer_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to abandon the operation and focus on damage control. This will prevent any potential harm caused by misinformation, but it also means that your civilization will miss out on a valuable opportunity to advance its interests in the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC3_Disciplinarian_Name</Label>
        <String>The Merciless Disciplinarian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC3_Disciplinarian_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a merciless disciplinarian, expects nothing less than perfection from their subordinates.[BR][BR]Recently, a brilliant scientist under {LEADERNAME}'s supervision made a minor mistake that led to a delay in a crucial research project. {LEADERNAME} is demanding the immediate termination of the scientist, while others argue that the scientist's talent and potential contributions should outweigh the consequences of a single error.[BR][BR]We must decide how to handle this situation and whether to support {LEADERNAME}'s strict disciplinary measures or not.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC3_Disciplinarian_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the termination.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC3_Disciplinarian_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support {LEADERNAME}'s decision to terminate the scientist. This strengthens the discipline within your civilization, but you lose a talented scientist and risk discouraging future innovation due to the fear of making mistakes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC3_Disciplinarian_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Forgive the scientist's mistake.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC3_Disciplinarian_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to forgive the scientist's mistake and allow them to continue working. This fosters a culture of innovation and encourages risk-taking within your civilization. However, {LEADERNAME} becomes discontent, leading to a decrease in their effectiveness and a potential loss of respect from other subordinates.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F21_HereticPast_Name</Label>
        <String>The Heretic Past</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F21_HereticPast_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a valued member of your government, was once accused of holding 'impure' beliefs in their youth. The accusations were, in fact, true. Recently, {LEADERNAME}'s past has resurfaced, and some citizens are demanding an investigation into whether these beliefs still persist.[BR][BR]Our advisors believe that addressing this issue could either strengthen our society's unity or lead to further division. They suggest two possible courses of action: to launch an investigation or to ignore the rumors and focus on the present.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F21_HereticPast_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Investigate {LEADERNAME}'s beliefs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F21_HereticPast_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to investigate {LEADERNAME}'s beliefs. This thorough examination will reveal the truth but may create unrest among your population, leading to a temporary drop in approval ratings. However, if {LEADERNAME} is found to have renounced their previous beliefs, their credibility and your government's reputation will be strengthened.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F21_HereticPast_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Ignore the rumors and focus on the present.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F21_HereticPast_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By ignoring the rumors, your civilization can focus on the present challenges and opportunities. While this decision might be seen as a sign of your government's wisdom and pragmatism, there is a potential risk that {LEADERNAME}'s past could resurface at a later date, leading to more significant consequences and unrest.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C24_Framed_Name</Label>
        <String>The Framed Innocent</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C24_Framed_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves your government, was once framed for the murder of a political rival. Recently, new evidence has surfaced that could potentially clear {LEADERNAME}'s name and bring the true culprit to justice.[BR][BR]However, pursuing this evidence could reopen old wounds and destabilize the political landscape. Our advisors suggest we could either support {LEADERNAME} in their quest for exoneration or suppress the evidence and maintain the status quo.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C24_Framed_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the quest for exoneration.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C24_Framed_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support {LEADERNAME} in their quest for exoneration. The pursuit of justice boosts morale among your people, but it also causes political unrest as factions realign in response to the new revelations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C24_Framed_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Suppress the evidence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C24_Framed_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to suppress the evidence, maintaining the current fragile political balance. {LEADERNAME} remains under a cloud of suspicion, which could affect their performance and loyalty. Additionally, there is a risk that the evidence may resurface in the future, with unpredictable consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PirateFamily_Name</Label>
        <String>Hidden Ties</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PirateFamily_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is a trusted member of your government, but we have recently discovered that their family has a hidden history of secretly supporting space piracy. This support is still ongoing and has been a significant source of wealth for the family.[BR][BR]Our intelligence has traced the funds to a distant pirate fleet, and we can either expose the truth or let {LEADERNAME}'s family continue their illicit operations in exchange for a share of the profits. Our advisors warn that publically revealing this information would have severe consequences for {LEADERNAME} and the stability of our government.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PirateFamily_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Expose the truth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PirateFamily_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to expose the truth. This results in the weakening of the pirate fleet and a boost in our civilization's security. However, the scandal damages {LEADERNAME}'s reputation and causes instability in our government for several months.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PirateFamily_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Accept a share of the profits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PirateFamily_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}'s family agrees to share a portion of their profits with us, increasing our civilization's wealth in the short term. However, this decision may encourage further corruption within our government and could lead to future complications with the pirate fleet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_SilverPlatter_Name</Label>
        <String>The Silver Platter Challenge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_SilverPlatter_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been raised in privilege, with every opportunity handed to them on a silver platter. As a result, they've never faced a true challenge in their life. An influential member of your civilization suggests that testing {LEADERNAME}'s abilities through a simulated crisis would help them grow as a leader.[BR][BR]However, there are concerns that this test may either boost their confidence too much or break their spirit. Your advisors are divided on whether to proceed with the simulation or let {LEADERNAME} remain untested.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_SilverPlatter_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Initiate the simulation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_SilverPlatter_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to initiate the simulation. {LEADERNAME} successfully navigates the crisis, developing a newfound resilience and gaining a valuable skill. However, there's a risk that their confidence may become arrogance, leading to potential overreach in future decisions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_SilverPlatter_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Leave them untested.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_SilverPlatter_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} remains untested, maintaining their current skill set and avoiding any potential negative consequences. However, there may be missed opportunities for growth and development, and their ability to handle future challenges will remain uncertain.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Dreamer_Name</Label>
        <String>The Lucid Dreamer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Dreamer_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your key advisors, is known for their unique ability to control their dreams to rehearse important meetings. They have recently discovered an upcoming secret meeting between rival factions within the government that could potentially disrupt the stability of your empire.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} has shared the details of this meeting with you and suggests two possible courses of action: use their skills to manipulate the outcome of the meeting in your favor or expose the conspirators publicly to demonstrate your strength and control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Dreamer_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Manipulate the meeting.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Dreamer_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to have {LEADERNAME} infiltrate the secret meeting using their lucid dreaming abilities. The outcome of the meeting is manipulated in your favor, resulting in a temporary boost to your influence and power. However, this action may lead to increased suspicion and paranoia among your advisors and allies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Dreamer_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Expose the conspirators.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Dreamer_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to publicly expose the conspirators, demonstrating your strength and control. This results in an immediate increase in your approval rating and the loyalty of your citizens. However, the conspirators may hold a grudge, and there's a chance they will seek revenge in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C12_CriminalRecord_Name</Label>
        <String>Erased Past</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C12_CriminalRecord_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been an invaluable asset to your government, but their past has always been shrouded in mystery. Recently, an investigation has uncovered that {LEADERNAME} had an extensive criminal record before joining your ranks. However, it appears that powerful government contacts erased this history, allowing them to start anew.[BR][BR]As this information begins to spread, some citizens are alarmed by the hidden past of one of your most trusted leaders. Your advisors present two options: allow {LEADERNAME} to address their past and reveal the truth, or suppress the information and discredit the investigation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C12_CriminalRecord_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Reveal the truth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C12_CriminalRecord_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} publicly addresses their past, which leads to a temporary decrease in your civilization's approval rating. However, their honesty earns the trust of many citizens, strengthening their loyalty in the long run.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C12_CriminalRecord_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Suppress the information.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C12_CriminalRecord_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to suppress the information and discredit the investigation. While the majority remains unaware of {LEADERNAME}'s criminal past, some citizens grow suspicious of your government's transparency. There's also the potential for this information to resurface in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GamblingDebt_Name</Label>
        <String>The Gambling Debt</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GamblingDebt_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a trusted member of your government, has unfortunately accumulated a significant amount of gambling debt. This information has come to light after a notorious crime syndicate has contacted your government, demanding repayment for {LEADERNAME}'s debts. [BR][BR]Our advisors suggest two courses of action: pay off the debt to keep the peace and avoid any negative consequences, or confront the crime syndicate and refuse to pay, potentially risking {LEADERNAME}'s safety and the stability of your government.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GamblingDebt_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Pay off the debt.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GamblingDebt_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to pay off {LEADERNAME}'s gambling debt. This will deplete a portion of your government's funds, but will ensure the crime syndicate does not retaliate, and maintain stability within your government.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GamblingDebt_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Refuse to pay.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_GamblingDebt_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>You decide to confront the crime syndicate and refuse to pay {LEADERNAME}'s gambling debt. This bold stance may earn you respect among your citizens, but it could also lead to {LEADERNAME} being targeted by the crime syndicate, and potential consequences for your government down the line.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_Vanity_Name</Label>
        <String>The Vanity Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_Vanity_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, an influential leader in your government, is known for their extreme vanity, often reacting violently to those they perceive as more attractive. [BR][BR]Recently, a rising star within your civilization has caught the public's eye, and their beauty has become the talk of the galaxy. Unsurprisingly, {LEADERNAME} has taken notice and now demands that this individual be eliminated to protect their image.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest that we can either comply with {LEADERNAME}'s request or attempt to diffuse the situation by offering a compromise.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_Vanity_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Eliminate the threat.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_Vanity_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to eliminate the rising star. This decision appeases {LEADERNAME}, who remains loyal to your cause. However, the murder leaves a dark stain on your civilization's reputation, causing a decrease in diplomatic relations with other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_Vanity_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Propose a compromise.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_Vanity_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You suggest that the rising star undergoes cosmetic alterations to appear less attractive. This solution placates {LEADERNAME} for now, but the star's career suffers as a result, and there may be future consequences for your civilization's entertainment industry.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Atonement_Name</Label>
        <String>Path to Atonement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Atonement_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a former assassin now serving your government, has been struggling with deep-seated guilt over their past actions. Recently, they have discovered the existence of a secret organization that targets and eliminates oppressive political figures.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} believes that by joining this organization, they can atone for their past sins and make a difference in the galaxy. However, our advisors warn that this may bring unwanted attention to our civilization and put us at risk.[BR][BR]Should we allow {LEADERNAME} to pursue their path to redemption?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Atonement_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Grant permission to join.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Atonement_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You allow {LEADERNAME} to join the organization. Their newfound purpose boosts their morale and effectiveness, but our civilization becomes a target of those who oppose the organization's goals, leading to potential conflicts and diplomatic challenges.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Atonement_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Forbid involvement.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Atonement_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You forbid {LEADERNAME} from joining the organization, prioritizing the safety of our civilization. Though {LEADERNAME}'s guilt and depression worsen, our political standing remains secure. However, this decision may affect {LEADERNAME}'s loyalty and performance in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Miser_Name</Label>
        <String>The Penny-Pinching Tyrant</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Miser_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is infamous for their tight-fistedness when it comes to finances. Their underlings have been suffering from low wages, outdated equipment, and poor working conditions for years. Recently, a group of them has united and sent a formal complaint to the higher-ups, demanding better treatment and resources.[BR][BR]We must decide how to handle this situation - should we force {LEADERNAME} to allocate more funds to their department or find another way to appease the disgruntled employees?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Miser_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Invest in improvements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Miser_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>We choose to invest in improvements and force {LEADERNAME} to allocate more funds to their department. This results in increased morale and productivity among the employees but may strain our finances for a time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Miser_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Implement non-financial incentives.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD5_Miser_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Instead of forcing {LEADERNAME} to allocate more funds, we implement non-financial incentives and benefits for the employees, such as flexible working hours, additional vacation days, and recognition programs. This may appease the workers to some extent, but their underlying dissatisfaction with {LEADERNAME}'s management style may still fester and resurface later.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Desire_Name</Label>
        <String>The Veiled Desire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Desire_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a prominent figure in your government, is known for their intimidating and ruthless demeanor. However, recent intelligence reports suggest that deep down, {LEADERNAME} is secretly desperate to be liked and accepted by others.[BR][BR]An opportunity has arisen for you to take advantage of this hidden desire. You could either arrange for {LEADERNAME} to attend a series of public events, showing a softer side to their character, or maintain their fearsome reputation by avoiding any attempts to humanize them.[BR][BR]The decision you make will have a lasting impact on how {LEADERNAME} is perceived and their effectiveness within your government.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Desire_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Humanize them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Desire_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to humanize {LEADERNAME}, allowing them to attend public events and soften their image. This will improve their approval ratings and the morale of your civilization, but may also weaken their authority in the eyes of your adversaries.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Desire_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Maintain their fearsome image.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD3_Desire_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} continues to be feared and hated, maintaining their authoritative image. This will keep your adversaries in check, but at the cost of lower approval ratings and the continued alienation of {LEADERNAME} from others within your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Retirement_Name</Label>
        <String>The Long-Awaited Retirement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Retirement_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who tirelessly serves your government, has openly expressed their desire to retire and be done with their duties. [BR][BR]While they have been a valuable asset to your civilization, it is clear that their heart is no longer in it. A luxurious retirement planet has caught their eye, and {LEADERNAME} has requested your permission to retire there. [BR]Our advisors warn that allowing this retirement may create a leadership vacuum, but denying it could lead to a disgruntled and less effective leader.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Retirement_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Grant their retirement wish.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Retirement_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to grant {LEADERNAME}'s retirement wish. They leave with gratitude, but your civilization will need to find a suitable replacement, which may take time and resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Retirement_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Deny their retirement request.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Retirement_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} begrudgingly continues to serve, but their lack of enthusiasm may affect their performance and the morale of those under their command. There is a chance they may eventually accept their role or grow increasingly discontented.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dreams_Name</Label>
        <String>Recurring Dreams</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dreams_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves your government, has been experiencing recurring dreams of themselves in a past life. These dreams have become increasingly vivid, and {LEADERNAME} believes they are not merely dreams but a connection to a past life that may hold valuable information.[BR][BR]Our experts have divided opinions on the matter, with some believing that these dreams may be the result of an undiscovered alien technology affecting {LEADERNAME}'s mind, while others suggest it could be a natural phenomenon that may have uncharted benefits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dreams_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Investigate the dreams further.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dreams_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to investigate the dreams further. This decision will lead to the allocation of resources towards uncovering the truth behind these dreams, which could potentially reveal groundbreaking information or valuable insights. However, this choice may also result in wasted time and resources if the dreams prove to be insignificant.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dreams_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Ignore the dreams and focus on the present.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dreams_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is advised to ignore the dreams and focus on their responsibilities in the present. This choice will allow your government to concentrate on current affairs without being distracted by unproven speculations. However, there is a risk that valuable information may be lost if the dreams hold any truth to them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C31_FathersDeath_Name</Label>
        <String>The Father's Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C31_FathersDeath_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always carried the heavy burden of being responsible for their father's death. As a prominent scientist, their father was on the verge of a breakthrough in a highly experimental field when a terrible accident occurred, costing him his life.[BR][BR]Recently, a team of researchers has discovered the remnants of {LEADERNAME}'s father's work and believes it could lead to significant advancements for our civilization. However, delving into this research carries the risk of further accidents and loss of life.[BR][BR]Our advisors present two options: pursue the research with caution, honoring {LEADERNAME}'s father's legacy, or abandon it altogether, avoiding any potential disasters.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C31_FathersDeath_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Pursue the research</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C31_FathersDeath_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to pursue the research, honoring {LEADERNAME}'s father's legacy. This decision could lead to groundbreaking advancements for our civilization. However, there is a chance that accidents may occur, resulting in loss of life and potential backlash from the public.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C31_FathersDeath_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Abandon the research</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C31_FathersDeath_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to abandon the research, prioritizing the safety and well-being of our people. While this choice may prevent potential accidents, it also means giving up on the immense potential benefits that {LEADERNAME}'s father's research could have brought to our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_RivalSibling_Name</Label>
        <String>The Rival Sibling</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_RivalSibling_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always lived in the shadow of their more famous sibling. Recently, their sibling has become embroiled in a controversial project that could potentially harm your civilization's interests.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} approaches you, asking for your support in publicly condemning their sibling's project. Our advisors note that this could either strengthen your civilization's position or create further animosity between the siblings, potentially affecting {LEADERNAME}'s performance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_RivalSibling_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support {LEADERNAME}'s stance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_RivalSibling_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support {LEADERNAME}'s stance. This decision boosts {LEADERNAME}'s morale and loyalty, but it may also result in strained relations with their influential sibling, possibly affecting future political and economic dealings.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_RivalSibling_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage reconciliation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC9_RivalSibling_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You advise {LEADERNAME} to put aside their personal grudges and work together with their sibling for the greater good of your civilization. This may lead to improved relations between the siblings and potential benefits from their sibling's project, but it could also cause resentment in {LEADERNAME} and affect their loyalty to you.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_ImmortalityChase_Name</Label>
        <String>The Immortality Chase</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_ImmortalityChase_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been tirelessly searching for ways to achieve immortality throughout their life. They have recently come across a long-lost ancient artifact, believed to grant eternal life to its possessor.[BR][BR]However, obtaining this artifact requires venturing into a dangerous and uncharted sector of the galaxy. {LEADERNAME} seeks your permission to embark on this risky quest, potentially uncovering immense power and knowledge.[BR][BR]Our advisors caution that this mission could result in a significant loss of resources and manpower if unsuccessful, but the potential rewards are too great to ignore.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_ImmortalityChase_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Grant permission for the quest.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_ImmortalityChase_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You grant {LEADERNAME} permission to embark on the quest for immortality. If successful, your civilization may gain unprecedented power and knowledge. However, the expedition will be costly and could result in the loss of valuable resources and lives.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_ImmortalityChase_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Deny permission for the quest.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_ImmortalityChase_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You deny {LEADERNAME} permission to pursue the ancient artifact, ensuring that your civilization's resources and manpower remain intact. However, you may have missed an opportunity to unlock the secrets of eternal life and untold power.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CriminalConnections_Name</Label>
        <String>The Criminal Web</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CriminalConnections_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always been an effective and loyal member of your government, but their alarming number of criminal connections has recently come to light.[BR][BR]A high-ranking member of the underworld has approached your administration with a dangerous proposition: they offer valuable resources and information in exchange for leniency in law enforcement for their criminal operations.[BR][BR]Our advisors are torn: some believe that accepting the offer will significantly boost our capabilities, while others argue that the moral compromise will ultimately weaken our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CriminalConnections_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Accept the offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CriminalConnections_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to accept the offer. The resources and information provided greatly enhance your civilization's capabilities for a time, but the underworld's grip on your society strengthens, resulting in increased crime rates and a loss of moral standing among your people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CriminalConnections_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Reject the offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CriminalConnections_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Choosing to uphold your values, you reject the dangerous offer. While your civilization misses out on the potential boost, your people's trust in your leadership strengthens, increasing approval. However, the criminal underworld may seek retribution for your defiance, leading to potential future conflicts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Bureaucrat_Name</Label>
        <String>Due Process Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Bureaucrat_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a lifelong bureaucrat and staunch supporter of due process, is facing a challenging situation. A high-ranking official has been accused of embezzlement, but the evidence is shaky at best. While {LEADERNAME} believes in the importance of due process, they also recognize the need for swift action to maintain public trust.[BR][BR]Our advisors propose two courses of action: Allow the legal system to run its course, potentially allowing the accused to evade punishment, or intervene and force a resolution, which could compromise the integrity of our judicial system.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Bureaucrat_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Uphold due process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Bureaucrat_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to uphold due process, allowing the legal system to handle the case. This decision may lead to the accused official going unpunished, but it will strengthen the integrity of our legal system and reinforce {LEADERNAME}'s commitment to due process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Bureaucrat_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Intervene for a resolution.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Bureaucrat_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to intervene and force a resolution. While this decision might lead to a swifter resolution and maintain public trust, it may also cast doubt on the integrity of our legal system and cause {LEADERNAME} to question their commitment to due process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AssumedIdentity_Name</Label>
        <String>The Assumed Identity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AssumedIdentity_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most trusted advisors, has a curious past. During their younger years, they lived under an assumed identity for several years. This information has recently come to light, and the reasons behind this mysterious period of their life are unclear.[BR][BR]Some express concerns about {LEADERNAME}'s trustworthiness, while others believe there must be a valid reason for such actions. Our intelligence network has located someone from {LEADERNAME}'s past who might be able to shed light on the situation, but we must decide whether to investigate or let the past remain hidden.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AssumedIdentity_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Investigate the past.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AssumedIdentity_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to investigate the past. Uncovering the truth about {LEADERNAME}'s assumed identity may lead to significant revelations, but the investigation could also strain your relationship with {LEADERNAME} and potentially cause unrest among your people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AssumedIdentity_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Let the past stay hidden.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AssumedIdentity_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Choosing to let the past stay hidden, you trust {LEADERNAME}'s judgment and keep the information confidential. While this decision may maintain stability within your government, unresolved questions about {LEADERNAME}'s past may resurface at a later time, potentially causing unforeseen issues.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientTech_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ancient Technology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always been known for their distrust of new technology and preference for the old ways. Recently, they have discovered an ancient artifact, which they believe holds immense power and knowledge from a long-lost civilization.[BR][BR]Although our scientists are eager to study and reverse-engineer this artifact, {LEADERNAME} insists that we should respect the wisdom of the ancients and keep the artifact intact, using it only for guidance.[BR][BR]Our advisors are divided: some argue that we should harness the power of this ancient technology, while others fear that doing so could lead to unforeseen consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientTech_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Respect the ancient wisdom.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientTech_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to respect the ancient wisdom and preserve the artifact. As a result, your people embrace their cultural heritage, leading to increased morale and unity. However, the potential benefits of studying the artifact remain unrealized, and technological advancements may stagnate as a consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientTech_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Study and harness the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientTech_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to study and harness the power of the ancient artifact. This bold move leads to breakthroughs in various fields, providing a significant boost to technological progress. However, the decision to disregard the ancient wisdom angers {LEADERNAME} and a portion of the population, causing a rift within your civilization that may take time to mend.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C45_ExecutionMemory_Name</Label>
        <String>Haunting Memories</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C45_ExecutionMemory_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} had to bear the tragic burden of witnessing their parents' execution. This long-repressed memory resurfaces when a documentary about the event is released, drawing curiosity and sympathy from the public.[BR][BR]Your advisors inform you that this is a critical moment - you can either capitalize on the sympathy and boost {LEADERNAME}'s public image or suppress the documentary to avoid any additional emotional distress for {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C45_ExecutionMemory_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Use the sympathy to boost image.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C45_ExecutionMemory_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to take advantage of the public's sympathy. {LEADERNAME}'s popularity increases, leading to a boost in diplomacy and influence for several months. However, this decision may strain your relationship with {LEADERNAME}, who might feel exploited.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C45_ExecutionMemory_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Suppress the documentary.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C45_ExecutionMemory_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to suppress the documentary to protect {LEADERNAME}'s emotional well-being. {LEADERNAME} gains the Loyal trait and their relationship with you strengthens. However, the censorship may be discovered and lead to a loss of approval and trust among the public.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Name</Label>
        <String>The Defector's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your top scientists, defected from their home planet and brought classified technology to your civilization. This technological edge has given you an advantage. However, the scientist's former government has tracked them down and demands that {LEADERNAME} be returned along with the classified technology.[BR][BR]Your advisors are divided on this issue, with some arguing that complying with the demand could improve diplomatic relations, while others insist that refusing will protect your technological advantage and the scientist's life.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Comply with the demand.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to comply with the demand. {LEADERNAME} and the classified technology are returned to their home planet. Your diplomatic relations with their former government improve, but you lose the technological advantage and a valuable scientist. There's also the potential for a negative impact on your reputation as a safe haven for defectors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Refuse the demand.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to protect {LEADERNAME} and refuse the demand. The technological advantage remains with your civilization, and the scientist continues their work. However, your refusal strains diplomatic relations with the former government and may lead to increased tension or even conflict in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dubious_Discharge_Name</Label>
        <String>Dubious Discharge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dubious_Discharge_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} was once a highly respected military official in your civilization. However, they were discharged under mysterious circumstances that were never fully disclosed to the public.[BR][BR]Recently, an anonymous source has leaked documents that suggest {LEADERNAME}'s discharge was due to a failed secret mission, putting the lives of many soldiers at risk. The media has picked up the story, causing a public uproar.[BR][BR]Our advisors recommend either launching an investigation into the matter or suppressing the information to protect {LEADERNAME} and maintain stability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dubious_Discharge_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Launch an investigation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dubious_Discharge_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to launch an investigation into the matter. If the investigation reveals that {LEADERNAME} was indeed responsible for the failed mission, their reputation will be tarnished, and you may lose their valuable skills. However, if they are cleared of any wrongdoing, their reputation will be restored, and public trust in your government will increase.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dubious_Discharge_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Suppress the information.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dubious_Discharge_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to suppress the information, maintaining stability and protecting {LEADERNAME}. However, there is a risk that the truth may come out eventually, causing public unrest and damaging your government's credibility.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C31_Survivor_Name</Label>
        <String>The Survivor's Call</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C31_Survivor_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most experienced advisors, is famous for surviving a crash landing on a hostile alien planet and living in the wilderness for years. They have been contacted by a group of settlers facing a similar situation, and they seek guidance on how to survive in such a dangerous environment.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} is willing to help the settlers, but doing so would mean taking time away from their current responsibilities. Meanwhile, others argue that the settlers should fend for themselves and learn from their own experiences, as {LEADERNAME} did.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C31_Survivor_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Send {LEADERNAME} to help the settlers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C31_Survivor_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to send {LEADERNAME} to help the settlers. Their expertise will save many lives and create a strong bond with the settlers. However, {LEADERNAME}'s absence will temporarily weaken your government, leading to reduced efficiency in their area of expertise for several months.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C31_Survivor_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Advise the settlers to learn from their experiences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C31_Survivor_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You encourage the settlers to learn from their own experiences, just as {LEADERNAME} did. This decision allows {LEADERNAME} to continue their work uninterrupted, but some settlers may not survive the harsh conditions and the relationship with the settlement may be strained due to perceived indifference.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CB5_Peacekeeper_Name</Label>
        <String>The Peacekeeper's Resolve</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CB5_Peacekeeper_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a key member of your government, lost their family in a devastating interstellar war and has since vowed to prevent such conflicts from happening again.[BR][BR]Recently, tensions have been rising between the Drengin Empire and the Torian Confederation. Both factions have reached out to your government for support. {LEADERNAME} believes that acting as a mediator between the two factions could be a crucial step towards maintaining peace.[BR][BR]However, some of your advisors argue that taking a neutral stance could be seen as a sign of weakness, and it may be better to choose a side to secure a powerful ally.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CB5_Peacekeeper_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Mediate between the factions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CB5_Peacekeeper_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to mediate between the Drengin Empire and the Torian Confederation. While this decision may help prevent an escalation of conflict, your civilization's refusal to take a side may cause temporary diplomatic penalties with both factions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CB5_Peacekeeper_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Choose a side to support.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CB5_Peacekeeper_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By choosing to support either the Drengin Empire or the Torian Confederation, your civilization gains a powerful ally and strengthens its strategic position. However, this decision goes against {LEADERNAME}'s wishes and may lead to future conflicts, undermining their peacekeeping efforts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6ACE_PirateEngineer_Name</Label>
        <String>The Stolen Designs</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6ACE_PirateEngineer_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is a gifted engineer who was forced into piracy after their groundbreaking designs were stolen. Lately, they received an anonymous tip about the location of the thieves and the stolen designs. They seek your assistance in retrieving their work and bringing the culprits to justice. This could be an opportunity to clear {LEADERNAME}'s name and gain public support, or use the situation for a more strategic advantage.[BR][BR]Our advisors caution that this information could be a trap, and we should tread carefully in our response.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6ACE_PirateEngineer_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Help retrieve the designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6ACE_PirateEngineer_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to help {LEADERNAME} in retrieving their stolen designs. This will improve their loyalty and potentially grant your civilization access to their innovative technology. However, it may lead to a dangerous confrontation with the thieves, and your citizens may not support such an aggressive approach.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6ACE_PirateEngineer_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Use the situation for espionage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6ACE_PirateEngineer_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Instead of confronting the thieves directly, you decide to use the situation to your advantage by infiltrating their organization and acquiring valuable information. This could lead to long-term strategic benefits, but {LEADERNAME}'s name will remain tarnished, and they may question your commitment to their cause.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C15_PrisonBreak_Name</Label>
        <String>The Fugitive Past</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C15_PrisonBreak_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been a valuable asset to your government since their escape from a notorious prison colony. However, their past has caught up with them as a dangerous bounty hunter has tracked {LEADERNAME} down and is demanding their return to the prison colony in exchange for a hefty reward.[BR][BR]Our intelligence indicates that this bounty hunter has a formidable reputation and will not give up easily. We are faced with the choice to protect {LEADERNAME} or to send them back to the prison colony, in hopes of gaining favor and resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C15_PrisonBreak_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Protect {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C15_PrisonBreak_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to protect {LEADERNAME}, strengthening their loyalty and potentially gaining valuable information about the prison colony's secrets. However, this may lead to conflict with the bounty hunter and other factions seeking the reward.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C15_PrisonBreak_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Send {LEADERNAME} back.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C15_PrisonBreak_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By sending {LEADERNAME} back to the prison colony, you secure the reward and avoid conflict with the bounty hunter. However, this decision may have a negative impact on your government's morale and the trust of other leaders. Additionally, you lose {LEADERNAME}'s valuable skills and knowledge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_DivineCalling_Name</Label>
        <String>The Divine Calling</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_DivineCalling_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has long believed they were chosen by a higher power to lead their species to glory. Lately, they've been receiving what they believe to be divine visions, guiding them towards a distant star system that supposedly holds the key to our civilization's ultimate triumph.[BR][BR]Our scientists and strategists are skeptical, as there is no concrete evidence to support this claim. They argue that diverting resources towards this expedition could be a costly mistake. However, {LEADERNAME} is insistent, and their devout followers are eager to embark on this "holy mission." The decision falls to you.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_DivineCalling_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the expedition.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_DivineCalling_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support the expedition. This decision pleases {LEADERNAME} and their followers, boosting morale and fervor among your people. However, it strains your resources, as you must divert a significant amount of funds and manpower towards this unproven venture. The outcome remains uncertain, and some members of your government quietly question your judgment.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_DivineCalling_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Deny the request.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_DivineCalling_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By denying the request, you maintain your resources and keep your government focused on more tangible objectives. However, this decision deeply disappoints {LEADERNAME} and their followers, leading to a decrease in morale and a loss of faith in your leadership. Rumors of your rejection of the "divine calling" spread, causing unrest among the populace and sowing seeds of doubt in your government's ability to lead.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_DoubleAgent_Name</Label>
        <String>The Double Agent</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_DoubleAgent_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves as a diplomatic envoy for your government, has a secret: they are also a skilled spy who has been gathering valuable information for your civilization. Recently, {LEADERNAME} has uncovered a plot by a rival power attempting to undermine your government's interests.[BR][BR]Your advisors suggest that you can either use this information to publicly expose the plot, which would embarrass the rival power and strengthen your position, or use the information to secretly manipulate the situation in your favor without revealing your knowledge of their plans.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_DoubleAgent_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Expose the plot.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_DoubleAgent_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to publicly expose the plot, which severely damages the reputation of the rival power and bolsters your own standing among other civilizations. However, this move also puts {LEADERNAME}'s cover at risk and may result in them being targeted by enemy agents in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_DoubleAgent_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Manipulate the situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_DoubleAgent_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to secretly manipulate the situation, using the information to your advantage without revealing your knowledge of the rival's plans. This results in significant gains for your civilization, but also leaves the rival power suspicious and more likely to be aggressive in future dealings, as they are unaware that their scheme has been compromised.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Discovery_Name</Label>
        <String>The Groundbreaking Discovery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Discovery_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has recently made a groundbreaking discovery that could revolutionize our technology and society. However, this discovery has made them a target for multiple factions who seek to acquire the knowledge for their own purposes.[BR][BR]Our intelligence network has intercepted communications indicating that one faction plans to kidnap {LEADERNAME} to extract the information, while another faction aims to sabotage the research facilities and steal the data. We must decide on how to protect {LEADERNAME} and the invaluable discovery.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Discovery_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Secure the Research Facilities</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Discovery_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to prioritize securing the research facilities, preventing any data theft or sabotage. This will ensure that our civilization benefits from the discovery, but it may leave {LEADERNAME} more vulnerable to kidnapping attempts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Discovery_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Protect {LEADERNAME}</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Discovery_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to focus on {LEADERNAME}'s safety, assigning additional security personnel and moving them to a secure location. While this will protect {LEADERNAME} from kidnapping attempts, it might leave the research facilities more exposed to sabotage and data theft.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RebelLeader_Name</Label>
        <String>The Rebel Symbol</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RebelLeader_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a key leader in your government, was once a famed rebel leader on their home planet, and has since become a symbol of resistance against tyranny.[BR][BR]Recently, an oppressed faction from another nearby planet has reached out to {LEADERNAME}, begging for their help in staging a rebellion against their oppressive rulers. If {LEADERNAME} chooses to offer their support, it could potentially strain diplomatic relations with that planet's government.[BR][BR]Our advisors recommend caution, but the decision ultimately lies with {LEADERNAME} and you.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RebelLeader_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the rebellion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RebelLeader_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support the rebellion. {LEADERNAME} will use their experience to help the oppressed faction, potentially leading to a successful uprising. However, this bold move will likely strain diplomatic relations with the planet's government and may have future consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RebelLeader_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Remain neutral.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_RebelLeader_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} reluctantly decides to remain neutral, prioritizing good relations with the planet's government. While this decision may prevent potential conflict, {LEADERNAME} will be seen as a sell-out by the oppressed faction and other rebel sympathizers, possibly damaging their reputation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_Cryosleep_Name</Label>
        <String>The Lost Voyage</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_Cryosleep_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has a unique past, having spent decades in cryosleep after a space voyage went awry.[BR][BR]Now, a message has been received from a distant, uncharted system. It appears that the long-lost sister ship of {LEADERNAME}'s original voyage has been discovered, with the crew still in cryosleep. The inhabitants of this system have no knowledge of cryosleep technology and are demanding guidance on how to proceed.[BR][BR]Our advisors have presented two options: either send an expert team to safely awaken and retrieve the crew or allow the inhabitants to attempt the revival process themselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_Cryosleep_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Send an expert team.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_Cryosleep_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to send an expert team. The crew is safely awakened and returned home, strengthening your civilization with their unique skills and experiences. However, this mission will consume resources and temporarily reduce productivity in other areas.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_Cryosleep_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Allow the inhabitants to try.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_Cryosleep_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} reluctantly agrees to let the inhabitants attempt the revival process. The crew is successfully awakened, but the lack of expertise results in some irreversible complications. As a result, the crew members are not as effective as they could have been, and relations with the inhabitants become strained.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_CloneCrime_Name</Label>
        <String>Clone Criminal</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_CloneCrime_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your trusted leaders, has an identical clone who is a notorious criminal, wreaking havoc across the galaxy. Recently, this criminal has committed a high-profile heist, and some are confusing {LEADERNAME} with their nefarious doppelganger.[BR][BR]Your advisors suggest two possible courses of action: either launch a covert operation to capture the clone and clear {LEADERNAME}'s name, or use this confusion to your advantage, allowing {LEADERNAME} to infiltrate criminal networks and gather valuable intelligence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_CloneCrime_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Capture the clone.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_CloneCrime_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to capture the criminal clone. This will restore {LEADERNAME}'s reputation, but the operation will require significant resources and can potentially lead to unforeseen consequences if the clone escapes or retaliates.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_CloneCrime_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Infiltrate criminal networks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_CloneCrime_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} uses their identical appearance to infiltrate criminal networks. This provides valuable intelligence and opportunities for sabotage, but risks corrupting {LEADERNAME} and may damage their reputation if discovered by the public.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_SimplerLife_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Political Potential</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_SimplerLife_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves your government, once had a promising career in politics. They willingly abandoned their political aspirations to seek a simpler life among the stars.[BR][BR]Recently, a political vacuum has emerged, and many are urging {LEADERNAME} to return to politics and fill the void. Their previous experience and connections could greatly benefit our civilization, but {LEADERNAME} is hesitant to leave their current role.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest that we either encourage {LEADERNAME} to return to politics or assure them that their current position is more valuable to our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_SimplerLife_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage political return.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_SimplerLife_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You encourage {LEADERNAME} to return to politics. Their influence will result in increased diplomacy and trade opportunities. However, their departure from their current role will leave a temporary gap in leadership that could impact efficiency.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_SimplerLife_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Reassure their current value.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD1_SimplerLife_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} feels appreciated and remains in their current position, which will improve their performance and dedication. However, the political vacuum may lead to instability and lost opportunities for our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Artifact_Name</Label>
        <String>The Mysterious Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Artifact_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has been carrying a mysterious alien artifact that is sought after by many factions across the galaxy. Rumors of its power and potential have reached far and wide, drawing the attention of both allies and enemies alike.[BR][BR]One day, an envoy from a powerful civilization arrives at your doorstep, requesting a private audience with {LEADERNAME}. They offer a substantial amount of resources and political support in exchange for the artifact. However, our intelligence warns that their true intentions may not be as benevolent as they claim.[BR][BR]Meanwhile, our scientists have expressed a keen interest in studying the artifact further, believing it could unlock untold technological advancements for our civilization. The decision on how to proceed lies with you.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Artifact_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Trade the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Artifact_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You choose to trade the artifact with the envoy, gaining a significant boost in resources and political support. However, you may have unwittingly empowered a potential adversary, and the consequences of this decision could manifest in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Artifact_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep the artifact for research.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Artifact_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>You decide to keep the artifact and allow your scientists to study it. This choice could lead to groundbreaking technological advancements, but at the cost of potentially angering the envoy's civilization and drawing the attention of other factions seeking the artifact's power.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Genetic_Modification_Name</Label>
        <String>The Genetic Awakening</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Genetic_Modification_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a prominent bioengineer in your administration, has been working on a secret project. It is now revealed that {LEADERNAME} has successfully modified their own genetics to the point of becoming an entirely new species, vastly superior to their original form.[BR][BR]This unprecedented breakthrough has sent shockwaves throughout the galaxy. Some factions are in awe of this achievement, while others are deeply disturbed by its implications. As the leader of your civilization, you must decide how to address this situation publicly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Genetic_Modification_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Embrace the breakthrough.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Genetic_Modification_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to embrace {LEADERNAME}'s breakthrough, celebrating their genius and the potential benefits it could bring to your civilization. This decision boosts your civilization's research capabilities and attracts other brilliant minds to your cause. However, some factions become wary of your civilization, fearing the ethical consequences of playing with the very essence of life.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Genetic_Modification_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Condemn the modification.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Genetic_Modification_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to condemn {LEADERNAME}'s actions, asserting that the sanctity of life should not be tampered with. This decision earns you the respect of factions that share your ethical concerns, strengthening your alliances and diplomatic relations. However, {LEADERNAME} resigns from their position in your administration, taking their extraordinary knowledge with them and leaving a void in your scientific community that may take years to fill.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_Name</Label>
        <String>Dimensional Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a renowned scientist in your government, was attempting to develop advanced technology to improve the lives of your citizens. Unfortunately, during their latest experiment, they accidentally opened a portal to another dimension.[BR][BR]This dimensional breach has attracted the attention of various factions within our society. Some see it as an opportunity for exploration and discovery, while others fear the unknown and the potential risks it brings.[BR][BR]As the leader of your civilization, you must decide how to approach this unexpected situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Embrace the unknown.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to embrace the unknown and allow expeditions into the other dimension. While this decision may lead to new discoveries and technologies, there is a risk of encountering dangerous entities or phenomena that could threaten your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Seal the portal.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You order {LEADERNAME} to seal the portal and prevent any further contact with the other dimension. While this decision may protect your civilization from potential threats, it also stifles scientific progress and the opportunity for valuable discoveries.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B56_FallenHero_Name</Label>
        <String>The Fallen Hero</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B56_FallenHero_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} was once a revered hero in your civilization, known for their exceptional deeds and bravery. However, their fall from grace came after a disastrous decision that cost numerous lives and tarnished their reputation.[BR][BR]Now, a situation has arisen that bears striking similarities to the one that led to their downfall. The people are divided, and many are looking to {LEADERNAME} for guidance. Should they step up and face their past or avoid the situation altogether to prevent further harm?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B56_FallenHero_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage them to face their past.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B56_FallenHero_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You encourage {LEADERNAME} to face their past and take charge of the situation. Their experience and determination could lead to a successful outcome, but there is a risk that their past mistakes will be repeated, resulting in a significant loss of resources and morale.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B56_FallenHero_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Advise them to stay out of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B56_FallenHero_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>You advise {LEADERNAME} to stay out of the situation, letting someone else handle the responsibility. While this may prevent history from repeating itself, it could also hinder {LEADERNAME}'s personal growth and result in a missed opportunity for redemption, causing a decline in their overall effectiveness as a leader.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_Name</Label>
        <String>The Liberation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your trusted advisor, was once a notorious slaver before they chose to leave their past behind and fight for freedom. Recently, a message has been intercepted from a former associate, revealing the existence of a hidden slave camp on a distant planet. {LEADERNAME} is determined to liberate the camp, but some of your officials argue that it would be wiser to avoid stirring up trouble and focus on our own civilization's needs.[BR][BR]Our advisors recommend caution but also acknowledge the potential benefits of supporting {LEADERNAME}'s quest for redemption.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the liberation mission.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support the liberation mission. This will cost resources and potentially strain diplomatic relations with the slavers, but it will also free the slaves, boost morale, and strengthen {LEADERNAME}'s loyalty to your cause.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Focus on our own civilization's needs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to focus on your own civilization's needs, avoiding any potential conflicts and conserving resources. However, this choice may damage your relationship with {LEADERNAME} and other freedom-seeking factions. Furthermore, the slaves' plight will remain unresolved, and the slavers may grow more powerful over time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_SentientPlant_Name</Label>
        <String>The Sentient Flora</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_SentientPlant_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your renowned botanist, has recently discovered a sentient plant species on a distant planet. This groundbreaking discovery has attracted the attention of various factions within your civilization, each with their own agenda.[BR][BR]A group of xenobiologists is eager to study the plant's unique biology, while another faction sees potential in exploiting the species for economic gain. {LEADERNAME} seeks your guidance on how to proceed with this delicate matter.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_SentientPlant_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Protect and study the species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_SentientPlant_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to protect the sentient plant species, allowing the xenobiologists to study their biology and learn valuable insights about their unique form of sentience. This decision will lead to an increase in scientific knowledge, but some factions may resent the missed economic opportunity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_SentientPlant_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Exploit the species for profit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C35_SentientPlant_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to exploit the sentient plant species for economic gain, causing a surge in your civilization's wealth. However, this decision will have negative consequences on your relations with certain factions and there is a risk of an ecological backlash in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Wormhole_Name</Label>
        <String>The Wormhole Anomaly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Wormhole_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most valued leaders, once fell into a wormhole and experienced time at an accelerated rate. [BR][BR]Recently, a group of scientists discovered its possible return. They believe that the wormhole's reappearance could grant {LEADERNAME} the ability to harness the power of accelerated time, providing a significant advantage to our civilization. However, there is a risk that the wormhole's instability may cause severe damage to our research facilities and disrupt the space-time continuum.[BR][BR]Our advisors are torn. Some argue that we should study the wormhole to benefit from its extraordinary properties, while others urge caution, fearing the potentially catastrophic consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Wormhole_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Explore the wormhole.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Wormhole_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to explore the wormhole and its unique properties. If successful, {LEADERNAME} may gain powerful abilities that could greatly benefit our civilization. However, there is a risk that the wormhole's instability may cause significant damage to our research facilities and disrupt the space-time continuum, leading to unpredictable consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Wormhole_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Avoid the wormhole.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Wormhole_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose not to risk exploring the wormhole, prioritizing the safety of our civilization over potential gains. As a result, {LEADERNAME} will not be able to harness the power of accelerated time, and we may miss out on a unique opportunity to advance our technology and knowledge. However, the risk of catastrophic damage to our research facilities and the space-time continuum is averted.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CulturalInfluence_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Influence</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CulturalInfluence_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is known for their time spent on a pre-industrial planet, where they inadvertently influenced the local culture. [BR][BR]Years later, the planet has advanced considerably and is now on the verge of joining the galactic community. However, their culture has developed in a controversial way due to {LEADERNAME}'s influence, and some factions are blaming them for the issues the planet is facing.[BR][BR]Our advisors propose two different approaches: either {LEADERNAME} could publicly apologize and offer to help rectify the situation, or they could embrace the unique culture they helped create and defend their actions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CulturalInfluence_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Apologize and offer assistance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CulturalInfluence_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} publicly apologizes and offers to help the struggling factions on the planet. This action will improve diplomatic relations with the factions and gain their gratitude, but it will also consume resources and time as you work to rectify the situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CulturalInfluence_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Defend the unique culture.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_CulturalInfluence_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} stands by their influence on the planet, arguing that its unique culture is something to be celebrated rather than condemned. This stance may result in increased cultural diversity and potential new allies, but it risks alienating the factions who blame {LEADERNAME} for their troubles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Spaceborn_Name</Label>
        <String>The Spaceborn Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Spaceborn_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has made a name for themselves as an extraordinary leader, born and raised entirely in deep space. They've never set foot on a planet, and their unique upbringing has led to an unparalleled understanding of space travel and technology.[BR][BR]Recently, a group of researchers has discovered a previously unknown planet with a unique and potentially life-altering atmosphere. They have requested {LEADERNAME} to be the first to set foot on the planet, believing their spaceborn background will provide invaluable insights. However, some advisors worry that the unfamiliar environment could prove too much for {LEADERNAME}, potentially weakening their leadership abilities or worse.[BR][BR]The decision lies with you: should {LEADERNAME} take this monumental step, or remain in the familiar confines of space?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Spaceborn_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage the planet visit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Spaceborn_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to encourage {LEADERNAME} to visit the planet. The experience could lead to significant scientific breakthroughs and strengthen {LEADERNAME}'s understanding of both planetary and space environments. However, there is also a risk that the unfamiliar atmosphere and gravity could have adverse effects on {LEADERNAME}'s health and leadership abilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Spaceborn_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep them in space.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Spaceborn_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to keep {LEADERNAME} in space, maintaining their unique and unparalleled expertise in space travel and technology. While this may prevent potential harm to {LEADERNAME} and their abilities, the opportunity for scientific discovery and the chance to broaden {LEADERNAME}'s knowledge will be lost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_LostLegacy_Name</Label>
        <String>The Lost Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_LostLegacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most dedicated leaders, carries the legacy of a lost civilization that they have vowed to rebuild. They have recently discovered the location of an ancient artifact belonging to their ancestors, which could hold the key to reviving this lost culture.[BR][BR]However, the artifact is located in a dangerous and uncharted region of space, filled with cosmic anomalies and potential threats. {LEADERNAME} seeks your guidance on how to proceed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_LostLegacy_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Launch a mission to retrieve the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_LostLegacy_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to launch a mission to retrieve the artifact. The mission has a high chance of success, but it will require resources and personnel. If successful, the artifact could greatly benefit your civilization and boost morale among the descendants of the lost civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_LostLegacy_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Focus on the present, not the past.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_LostLegacy_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is disheartened by your decision to focus on current affairs and not the past. Although your civilization will continue to allocate resources to more pressing matters, {LEADERNAME}'s motivation and productivity may suffer as a result of this choice.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F3C_PacifistWarrior_Name</Label>
        <String>The Unlikely Pacifist</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F3C_PacifistWarrior_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a rare pacifist from the warrior race, has been ostracized for their peaceful beliefs. Despite their dedication to non-violence, they have shown great potential as a leader and valuable contributor to our government.[BR][BR]Recently, a group of their fellow warriors has challenged {LEADERNAME} to prove their worth by participating in a traditional combat trial. Accepting the challenge could strengthen ties with their people, but may also compromise {LEADERNAME}'s pacifist ideals.[BR][BR]On the other hand, declining the challenge would further isolate {LEADERNAME} from their people and potentially weaken our influence over their race.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F3C_PacifistWarrior_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Accept the challenge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F3C_PacifistWarrior_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} reluctantly accepts the challenge, earning the respect of their people and strengthening our influence over their race. However, this act of violence weighs heavily on {LEADERNAME} and may affect their future decisions as a pacifist leader.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F3C_PacifistWarrior_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Decline the challenge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8F3C_PacifistWarrior_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} declines the challenge, staying true to their pacifist beliefs. This decision further alienates them from their people, weakening our diplomatic influence over their race. However, {LEADERNAME} remains a steadfast and uncompromised advocate for peace within our government.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ruthless Strategist</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your brilliant strategist, has become infamous for their ruthless tactics. Their latest plan involves a high-risk, high-reward operation that could potentially cripple the enemy but would result in significant civilian casualties. While the strategy may help turn the tide of the conflict, it could also provoke outrage and moral condemnation from both your own people and the galactic community.[BR][BR]Your advisors are divided, with some arguing that the potential benefits outweigh the risks, while others advocate for a more measured and cautious approach. The choice ultimately falls on you to decide whether to authorize {LEADERNAME}'s ruthless tactics or to seek alternative strategies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Authorize the ruthless strategy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You authorize {LEADERNAME}'s ruthless strategy. The operation is successful, dealing a significant blow to the enemy. However, the civilian casualties and collateral damage are massive, leading to public outrage and diplomatic backlash. The military gains come at a high cost to your civilization's moral standing and reputation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Seek alternative strategies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to seek alternative strategies. {LEADERNAME} begrudgingly agrees to find a more humane approach. The new plan is less effective and takes longer to implement, but it spares most civilians and maintains your civilization's moral high ground. The slower pace of progress may give the enemy time to regroup, but your people and allies respect your commitment to ethical warfare.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B5C_TimeTravel_Name</Label>
        <String>The Time Traveler's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B5C_TimeTravel_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a prominent member of your scientific community, has always claimed to have discovered the secret to time travel. However, they frustratingly admit to not being able to recall the crucial details needed to unlock this groundbreaking technology.[BR][BR]Recently, a mysterious artifact has been found on a distant planet which, according to our experts, could hold the key to unlocking {LEADERNAME}'s lost memories. We must decide whether to investigate further, at the risk of exposing ourselves to potential dangers, or to ignore the artifact and focus on our current objectives.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B5C_TimeTravel_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Investigate the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B5C_TimeTravel_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to investigate the mysterious artifact. Doing so may unlock the secret to time travel, potentially giving your civilization a significant advantage. However, this investigation will consume valuable resources and may attract unwanted attention from rival factions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B5C_TimeTravel_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Ignore the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B5C_TimeTravel_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to ignore the artifact and focus on your current objectives. This allows you to allocate resources to more pressing matters, but it may mean missing out on a unique opportunity to harness the power of time travel for your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_Name</Label>
        <String>Survivor's Guilt</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a respected member of your government, is haunted by their past. They were the sole survivor of a deadly plague that wiped out their entire colony on the outer rim of the galaxy.[BR][BR]A group of scientists has recently discovered a potential cure for the plague, but they need access to the quarantined colony to gather samples. The scientists believe that with {LEADERNAME}'s knowledge of the colony, they could safely enter and collect the necessary data. However, this would require {LEADERNAME} to face their traumatic past.[BR][BR]You must now decide whether to support the scientists' request or protect {LEADERNAME} from reliving their painful memories.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the scientists.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to support the scientists in their quest to find a cure. {LEADERNAME} bravely agrees to help, but their mental health is adversely affected, which may lead to a temporary decrease in their productivity. However, the cure could save countless lives and enhance your civilization's reputation as a protector of life.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Protect {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By choosing to protect {LEADERNAME} from reliving their painful past, you show your commitment to the well-being of your leaders. {LEADERNAME}'s loyalty and productivity will increase, but the opportunity to find a cure for the deadly plague may be lost, and other civilizations may question your priorities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C21_Exile_Name</Label>
        <String>The Fallen Leader</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C21_Exile_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a member of your government, was once a respected ruler of their people. However, a devastating coup d'etat forced them into exile. [BR][BR]Recently, you receive a message from a group of loyalists within {LEADERNAME}'s former civilization. They claim to have evidence that could clear {LEADERNAME}'s name and potentially restore them to power. The loyalists request your assistance in orchestrating a plan to reveal the truth and reclaim their leader's rightful place.[BR][BR]Your advisors caution that getting involved in the internal affairs of another civilization may carry significant risks and consequences, while others argue that restoring {LEADERNAME} could forge a strong alliance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C21_Exile_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the loyalists' plan.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C21_Exile_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to support the loyalists' plan. If successful, you will gain a strong ally in {LEADERNAME}'s former civilization and potentially valuable resources. However, there is a risk of retaliation from the current regime, leading to potential conflict and diplomatic fallout.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C21_Exile_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Stay out of their affairs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C21_Exile_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to stay out of their affairs, maintaining neutrality and avoiding potential conflict. However, this could strain your relationship with {LEADERNAME} and their loyalists, as well as hinder any potential alliance with their former civilization in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C92_Enhancements_Name</Label>
        <String>The Harsh Environment</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C92_Enhancements_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has willingly undergone cybernetic enhancements to survive in harsh environments. Recently, a research team has discovered a potential breakthrough in terraforming technology on the inhospitable planet of Zalara. Due to the hazardous conditions, only someone with cybernetic enhancements like {LEADERNAME} can safely explore the planet and retrieve the necessary data.[BR][BR]However, this mission could have unforeseen consequences on {LEADERNAME}'s physical and mental well-being. The choice is yours: send {LEADERNAME} to Zalara with the potential of great scientific advancement or prioritize their safety and forgo the mission.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C92_Enhancements_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Send them to Zalara.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C92_Enhancements_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You send {LEADERNAME} to Zalara, potentially unlocking groundbreaking terraforming technology. However, this decision may result in negative effects on {LEADERNAME}'s health and mental stability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C92_Enhancements_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep them safe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C92_Enhancements_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You prioritize {LEADERNAME}'s safety and well-being, ensuring their continued service to your empire. However, the potential advancements in terraforming technology will remain unexplored and out of reach.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Disaster_Name</Label>
        <String>First Contact Catastrophe</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Disaster_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is a key member of your government, but their past has always been shrouded in mystery. Recently, classified documents reveal that they were part of a first contact scenario that ended in a disastrous conflict.[BR][BR]It turns out that during their mission, {LEADERNAME}'s team encountered a previously unknown species. As the situation escalated, the conflict led to the destruction of an alien vessel and the loss of life on both sides.[BR][BR]Now, the surviving members of the alien species have reached out to your civilization, seeking justice for the incident. Your advisors present two options: either support {LEADERNAME} and risk diplomatic tensions or distance your government from {LEADERNAME} and hope for a peaceful resolution.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Disaster_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Stand by {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Disaster_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to stand by {LEADERNAME}, emphasizing the importance of loyalty and unity amongst your people. However, this decision may strain diplomatic relations with the alien species and potentially lead to further conflicts in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Disaster_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Distance from {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD2_Disaster_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to distance your government from {LEADERNAME}, hoping to maintain peace with the alien species. While this may lead to a more amicable relationship with the aliens, it could also damage {LEADERNAME}'s morale and weaken your government's internal cohesion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AB4_ParallelFugitive_Name</Label>
        <String>Parallel Fugitive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AB4_ParallelFugitive_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a trusted member of your government, claims to be a fugitive from a parallel universe, constantly evading transdimensional bounty hunters. [BR][BR]Recently, unusual energy signatures have been detected near our borders, and our scientists believe that they could be the result of transdimensional travel. {LEADERNAME} is concerned that their past has caught up with them and they might endanger the civilization.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest two possible courses of action: either help {LEADERNAME} face and confront the bounty hunters, or come up with a plan to send {LEADERNAME} back to their original universe, closing the bridge between dimensions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AB4_ParallelFugitive_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Confront the bounty hunters.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AB4_ParallelFugitive_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to help {LEADERNAME} confront the bounty hunters and potentially risk a confrontation with interdimensional forces. This will temporarily divert resources from other projects, but if successful, it will strengthen your bond with {LEADERNAME} and potentially bring new technologies to your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AB4_ParallelFugitive_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Send {LEADERNAME} back to their universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AB4_ParallelFugitive_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to send {LEADERNAME} back to their original universe, closing the bridge between dimensions. This will ensure the safety of your civilization from any potential interdimensional threats, but you will lose {LEADERNAME}'s unique skills and knowledge. Additionally, there is a small chance of unforeseen consequences due to meddling with transdimensional technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8AC3_PirateRevenge_Name</Label>
        <String>Revenge on Space Pirates</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8AC3_PirateRevenge_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a loyal member of your government, lost their family in a ruthless space pirate attack long ago. Recently, a trusted informant has revealed the location of the pirate hideout responsible for the attack.[BR][BR]The news has shaken {LEADERNAME}, who now seeks your permission to exact revenge on the pirates. Our advisors caution that engaging with these criminals could escalate tensions and endanger other innocent lives.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8AC3_PirateRevenge_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Grant permission for revenge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8AC3_PirateRevenge_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You grant {LEADERNAME} permission to exact their revenge. The operation eliminates the pirate threat, but at the cost of civilian casualties and potential backlash from other pirate factions in the galaxy. {LEADERNAME} gains the Vengeful trait. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8AC3_PirateRevenge_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Deny permission for revenge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8AC3_PirateRevenge_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You deny {LEADERNAME} permission for revenge, choosing to prioritize the safety of innocent lives. {LEADERNAME} is disappointed but understands your decision. However, the pirate threat remains active, and there is a chance that they will strike again in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C12_AncientArtifact_Name</Label>
        <String>Rediscovering the Lost Civilization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C12_AncientArtifact_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, our esteemed historian dedicated to preserving the knowledge of extinct civilizations, has uncovered an ancient artifact belonging to a long-forgotten race. The artifact appears to hold the key to unlocking the secrets of their advanced technology.[BR][BR]However, there is a dilemma. The artifact is highly sought after by various factions and selling it could bring in a significant amount of resources to our civilization. {LEADERNAME} is adamant about preserving the artifact for research purposes, but our advisors argue that the potential financial gains could greatly benefit our people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C12_AncientArtifact_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Preserve the artifact for research.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C12_AncientArtifact_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to preserve the artifact for research purposes. This decision pleases {LEADERNAME} and results in a breakthrough in technology, granting a significant research boost for our civilization. However, we miss out on the potential financial gains from selling the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C12_AncientArtifact_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Sell the artifact for resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C12_AncientArtifact_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Despite {LEADERNAME}'s objections, you decide to sell the artifact for resources. This decision displeases {LEADERNAME} and may affect their loyalty, but it brings in a substantial amount of resources that can be used for the betterment of our civilization. The knowledge contained within the artifact, however, is forever lost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Name</Label>
        <String>The Unexpected Creation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a renowned terraformer in your civilization, is responsible for the accidental creation of a new form of life while working on a terraforming project. This new life form, now known as the {CREATURENAME}, is an intelligent and rapidly evolving species that has been discovered on the terraformed planet.[BR][BR]As the {CREATURENAME} beings begin to develop and establish their own society, your advisors are divided on how to approach this situation. Some argue that we should study and learn from the {CREATURENAME}, while others fear the potential threat they might pose to our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Study and learn from them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to study and learn from the {CREATURENAME}. This decision will lead to scientific advancements and a better understanding of this new form of life. However, as we invest time and resources into studying the {CREATURENAME}, there may be unforeseen consequences and potential risks to our own civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Contain and control the situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is tasked with containing and controlling the situation, ensuring that the {CREATURENAME} do not pose a threat to our civilization. This decision will provide a sense of security for our people, but may also hinder scientific advancements and potential alliances with the {CREATURENAME} in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Redemption_Name</Label>
        <String>Path to Redemption</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Redemption_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, who serves your government, is seeking redemption after accidentally causing a catastrophic environmental disaster on one of your colonies. The incident has left a deep scar on their conscience, and they are determined to make amends.[BR][BR]A recent discovery of a rare and valuable resource on a remote planet has attracted the attention of multiple factions. This resource could help restore the devastated environment caused by the disaster, but it is located in a dangerous and unstable region of space. {LEADERNAME} proposes to lead a risky expedition to secure the resource and restore the environment, potentially risking their own life in the process.[BR][BR]Our advisors caution against this venture, suggesting that we instead invest in safer, long-term solutions to restore the environment and prevent future disasters.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Redemption_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Support the expedition.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Redemption_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to support the expedition. If successful, the rare resource will help restore the environment quickly. However, the mission is dangerous, and {LEADERNAME} might not return, leaving your government without their valuable expertise and leadership.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Redemption_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Invest in long-term solutions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD4_Redemption_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to invest in long-term solutions. This will ensure a safer and more sustainable recovery of the environment, but it may take several years before significant progress is made. {LEADERNAME} may struggle with feelings of guilt and frustration as they continue to seek redemption.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD9_Gladiator_Name</Label>
        <String>The Arena Reckoning</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD9_Gladiator_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a former gladiator who earned their freedom through countless battles, has been approached by a group of oppressed gladiators seeking help in their fight for freedom.[BR][BR]They have shared horrific tales of abuse and mistreatment at the hands of their masters and have heard of {LEADERNAME}'s own journey to freedom. They now implore {LEADERNAME} to use their influence to help them escape their brutal existence.[BR][BR]Our advisors are divided on the matter, with some arguing that intervening could lead to a larger conflict, while others believe that ignoring the plea would be a betrayal of our civilization's values.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD9_Gladiator_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Assist the gladiators.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD9_Gladiator_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to help the gladiators in their fight for freedom. This decision will strain diplomatic relations with factions that support the gladiatorial industry and may lead to increased tensions. However, the liberated gladiators will be grateful and offer their skills and loyalty to your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD9_Gladiator_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Disregard their plea.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7CD9_Gladiator_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} decides not to interfere in the gladiators' situation. This choice maintains the status quo and avoids potential conflicts, but the oppressed gladiators will continue to suffer, and {LEADERNAME} may be haunted by their decision to abandon those who sought their help.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_Name</Label>
        <String>The Revolutionary Energy Source</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, the inventor of a revolutionary energy source, has recently joined your civilization. Their research is coveted by many rival factions who would stop at nothing to obtain it. [BR][BR]We've been informed that a high-ranking scientist from a rival faction is attempting to infiltrate your research facilities to steal the blueprints. It is up to you to decide how to handle this sensitive situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Fortify security measures.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to fortify your research facilities with state-of-the-art security measures. This will effectively thwart any attempts to steal the blueprints, but will also increase your research facility upkeep costs for a while.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Plant a fake blueprint.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to plant a fake blueprint of the energy source, hoping to deceive the rival scientist. If successful, this will buy you some time to improve your security measures, but there's a risk that the rival faction realizes the deception and escalates their attempts to steal the real blueprints.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Communicator_Name</Label>
        <String>The Beast Whisperer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Communicator_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has an extraordinary ability to communicate with non-sentient creatures. This talent has proven useful in diplomatic situations and scientific research, but a recent incident has sparked controversy. [BR][BR]While exploring a newly colonized planet, {LEADERNAME} encountered an indigenous species that seemed prime for domestication. However, after communicating with the creatures, {LEADERNAME} claims that they possess a unique form of intelligence and should be left undisturbed.[BR][BR]Our advisors are split: some believe {LEADERNAME} and argue for the preservation of the creatures, while others insist that their potential benefits to our civilization are too great to ignore.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Communicator_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Preserve the creatures.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Communicator_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to respect {LEADERNAME}'s unique insight and preserve the creatures. This decision leads to increased morale and approval among your people, who praise your commitment to respecting all forms of life. However, your civilization misses out on potential advancements that could have come from domesticating the creatures.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Communicator_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Domesticate the creatures.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Communicator_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} reluctantly agrees to the domestication of the creatures. Your civilization benefits from the advanced materials and technologies developed from studying this species. However, this decision damages {LEADERNAME}'s trust in your leadership, resulting in a slight decrease in their loyalty and effectiveness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Disappearance_Name</Label>
        <String>The Mysterious Disappearance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Disappearance_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, the revered space explorer who vanished for years, has been plagued by recurring nightmares ever since their return. Despite having no memory of what transpired during their disappearance, the dreams seem to hint at hidden knowledge buried deep within {LEADERNAME}'s subconscious.[BR][BR]Recently, an ancient artifact was discovered on a remote planet which bears a striking resemblance to the objects in {LEADERNAME}'s dreams. Our advisors have proposed two courses of action: investigate the artifact, hoping to unlock the secrets of {LEADERNAME}'s past, or ignore it, fearing the potential consequences of unearthing long-forgotten memories.[BR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Disappearance_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Investigate the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Disappearance_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to delve into the mysteries of the artifact. This may lead to valuable discoveries, enhancing {LEADERNAME}'s abilities and providing new technological insights. However, the investigation will consume significant resources and could potentially uncover dangerous secrets that may threaten your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Disappearance_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Ignore the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Disappearance_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Choosing to leave the artifact undisturbed, you focus on maintaining the stability of your civilization. Although this decision may prevent unforeseen dangers, it also means that {LEADERNAME}'s past will remain shrouded in mystery, and any potential benefits of uncovering the truth will be lost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_Name</Label>
        <String>Mutiny Survivor's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is known for surviving a spaceship mutiny, an experience that has shaped their character and ability to make tough decisions.[BR][BR]However, a recent transmission from the mutineers' descendants reveals that they have established a thriving colony on a distant planet. They now seek reconciliation with your civilization and request amnesty for their ancestor's past actions.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} is uneasy about this development and asks for your guidance on whether to forgive the mutineers' descendants or hold them accountable for their ancestor's treachery.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Forgive and reconcile.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to forgive the mutineers' descendants, promoting peace and unity in the galaxy. This decision will boost your civilization's approval rating and potentially provide access to new resources and trade opportunities from the colony. However, some factions in your civilization may view this act of forgiveness as weakness, causing minor unrest among the populace.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Hold them accountable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} takes a hard stance against the mutineers' descendants, holding them accountable for their ancestor's actions. This decision will strengthen your civilization's resolve, improving military morale and causing a temporary boost in ship production. However, the colony will become a potential enemy, and diplomatic relations with other civilizations may be negatively affected by this perceived lack of compassion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientLibrary_Name</Label>
        <String>The Forbidden Knowledge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientLibrary_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most trusted advisors, secretly confesses to you that they once discovered an ancient alien library and learned its forbidden knowledge. This knowledge has been a source of power and insight that has aided your civilization in countless ways. However, recent reports reveal that a rival faction has become aware of {LEADERNAME}'s secret and is demanding access to the library.[BR][BR]Your advisors urge caution in dealing with this delicate situation, as the potential consequences of sharing or withholding the knowledge could have far-reaching effects on your civilization's future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientLibrary_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Share the knowledge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientLibrary_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to share the knowledge from the ancient library with the rival faction. Your civilization gains a temporary boost in diplomacy and trade benefits with them, but the shared knowledge may eventually result in increased competition and the rise of a formidable adversary.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientLibrary_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep the knowledge secret.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_AncientLibrary_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to keep the forbidden knowledge a secret, denying the rival faction's request. This decision may lead to strained diplomatic relations and potential conflict, but the exclusive access to the ancient library's wisdom will continue to give your civilization a significant advantage in technological and strategic advancements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Reincarnation_Name</Label>
        <String>The Reincarnation Revelation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Reincarnation_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always believed they are the reincarnation of a legendary hero from ancient times. Recently, a series of mysterious events have occurred throughout the galaxy, and these events seem to align with the ancient prophecies tied to the hero's return.[BR][BR]Some of your people have started to believe in {LEADERNAME}'s claim and see them as a divine figure. However, skeptics within your government worry that this might be an elaborate hoax, and that endorsing such claims could lead to unrest and division among your people.[BR][BR]What should your response be to this revelation?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Reincarnation_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Embrace the legend.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Reincarnation_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to embrace the legend, publicly endorsing {LEADERNAME}'s claim. This increases your people's morale and faith in your leadership. However, your society becomes more divided as some factions reject the notion, causing potential unrest and tension for the foreseeable future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Reincarnation_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Dismiss the claim.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Reincarnation_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to dismiss {LEADERNAME}'s claim as mere superstition. While this decision might appease the skeptics within your society, it could lead to a loss of faith and loyalty from those who genuinely believe in the legend. {LEADERNAME} may also feel betrayed and lose some of their motivation and dedication to your cause.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_PowerReckoning_Name</Label>
        <String>The Power Reckoning</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_PowerReckoning_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has long been an enigmatic figure within your civilization, wielding strange powers gained from a mysterious bargain with an extra-dimensional entity. Recently, their powers have grown increasingly unstable, causing concern among your people and threatening the safety of those around them.[BR][BR]Our advisors have identified two potential courses of action: we can either attempt to strengthen {LEADERNAME}'s control over their powers, or we can try to sever their connection to the extra-dimensional entity entirely, though both options carry risks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_PowerReckoning_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Strengthen their control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_PowerReckoning_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You opt to strengthen {LEADERNAME}'s control over their powers. As a result, their abilities become even more potent, granting significant advantages in various aspects of your civilization. However, this decision also attracts the attention of the extra-dimensional entity, which may lead to unforeseen consequences in the future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_PowerReckoning_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Sever the connection.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC1_PowerReckoning_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to sever {LEADERNAME}'s connection to the extra-dimensional entity. While this eliminates the immediate threat of their unstable powers, it also renders them significantly less powerful and less useful to your civilization. Moreover, the process of severing the connection is fraught with danger, and there is a chance that {LEADERNAME} may not survive.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C42_Cult_Background_Name</Label>
        <String>The Forgotten Cult</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C42_Cult_Background_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} once belonged to a cult that worshipped a long-dead alien god. They have since left the cult and serve your government loyally. However, recent archaeological discoveries have brought the existence of this alien god back into the spotlight. The cult, emboldened by the news, has reached out to {LEADERNAME}, asking them to return and help in deciphering the ancient alien texts.[BR][BR]Our advisors suggest two courses of action: allow {LEADERNAME} to aid the cult in the hopes of discovering valuable information about the alien god, or forbid any interaction and focus on the present, leaving the past behind.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C42_Cult_Background_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Allow {LEADERNAME} to aid the cult.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C42_Cult_Background_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} will spend time deciphering the ancient texts with the cult, potentially revealing valuable information about the alien god. This may lead to technological advancements or other benefits. However, {LEADERNAME}'s absence may temporarily weaken your government's effectiveness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C42_Cult_Background_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Forbid any interaction with the cult.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C42_Cult_Background_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} will remain focused on their duties within your government, ensuring stability and continuity. However, the opportunity for potential knowledge and technological advancements related to the alien god will be lost, and there may be unforeseen consequences from the angered cult members.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B29_Dystopia_Name</Label>
        <String>Time Traveler's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B29_Dystopia_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a valued member of your government, has a unique backstory: they escaped from a dystopian future and are now determined to prevent it from happening. [BR][BR]One day, {LEADERNAME} receives a message from their future self, detailing a crucial decision that must be made to avert the bleak future. The message is cryptic, and the consequences of the decision are unclear. Your advisors are divided on how to proceed.[BR][BR]Do you trust {LEADERNAME} and follow their guidance, or do you disregard the message and make your own choice?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B29_Dystopia_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Trust {LEADERNAME}'s guidance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B29_Dystopia_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to trust {LEADERNAME}'s guidance. While the decision may have unforeseen consequences, your civilization's morale is boosted by your show of faith in {LEADERNAME}, increasing approval for several months.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B29_Dystopia_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Disregard the message.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B29_Dystopia_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By disregarding the message, you risk the possibility of the dystopian future becoming reality. However, your decision to rely on your own judgment may lead to discoveries that could ultimately strengthen your civilization in ways previously unimagined.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_RobotRevelation_Name</Label>
        <String>The Robot Revelation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_RobotRevelation_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your trusted leaders, has been showing signs of extreme fatigue and malfunctions. After a thorough examination by your top scientists, it has been revealed that {LEADERNAME} is not a biological being but an advanced humanoid robot, completely unaware of their true nature.[BR][BR]This shocking revelation has the potential to destabilize {LEADERNAME}'s position within your government and create unrest among your citizens. You must decide how to handle this information and determine the best course of action for your civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_RobotRevelation_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Keep the secret.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_RobotRevelation_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to keep the secret about {LEADERNAME}'s true nature. Your scientists will discreetly repair and maintain their robotic body, ensuring they can continue to serve your civilization. However, there is always a risk that the secret may be exposed in the future, with potentially disastrous consequences for your government's reputation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_RobotRevelation_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Reveal the truth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AC5_RobotRevelation_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to reveal the truth about {LEADERNAME}'s robotic nature. This bold move will have immediate consequences, as your people struggle to accept that they have been led by an artificial being. However, in the long run, your government's honesty and transparency may be appreciated and could lead to increased trust from your citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C5D_PsychicBond_Name</Label>
        <String>The Psychic Bond</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C5D_PsychicBond_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has a rare psychic bond with a dangerous alien creature that has been kept a secret from the public. Recently, the creature has escaped containment and is causing havoc across nearby colonies.[BR][BR]{LEADERNAME} believes they can use their psychic connection to locate and subdue the creature, but fears the potential backlash if their secret bond is discovered. Our advisors suggest capturing the creature without {LEADERNAME}'s involvement to avoid controversy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C5D_PsychicBond_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Allow {LEADERNAME} to handle it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C5D_PsychicBond_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You allow {LEADERNAME} to use their psychic connection to locate and subdue the creature. The operation is a success, but their secret bond is exposed, leading to a temporary decline in public trust and morale.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C5D_PsychicBond_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Capture the creature covertly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x8C5D_PsychicBond_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You order a covert operation to capture the creature without {LEADERNAME}'s involvement. The mission is successful, and the creature is contained without revealing the psychic bond. However, the creature's rampage has caused significant damage to the affected colonies, straining resources and relationships with other factions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A35_Asteroid_Name</Label>
        <String>The Desolate Asteroid</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A35_Asteroid_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of our most affluent leaders, gained their wealth after discovering a rare mineral deposit on a desolate asteroid. Recently, a rival faction has contested our claim to the asteroid, stating that they had initially discovered it and we are trespassing on their territory.[BR][BR]Our legal team has confirmed that our claim is legitimate, but the opposing faction is adamant about their ownership. We must make a decision on how to proceed in this delicate situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A35_Asteroid_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Defend our claim.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A35_Asteroid_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to stand firm and defend our claim to the asteroid. This course of action will strengthen our economy and solidify {LEADERNAME}'s status but may strain relations with the rival faction and potentially escalate to conflict.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A35_Asteroid_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Negotiate a compromise.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A35_Asteroid_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to negotiate a compromise with the rival faction, sharing the asteroid's resources and profits. This decision may lead to improved relations with the rival faction, but will decrease {LEADERNAME}'s wealth and influence within our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Archaeologist_Name</Label>
        <String>The Lost Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Archaeologist_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your esteemed archaeologist, has discovered the location of a potentially significant artifact belonging to an ancient and long-lost civilization. This artifact could hold the key to unlocking their advanced technology or provide valuable insights into their culture and history.[BR][BR]However, the artifact is buried deep within the territory of a hostile alien empire. To retrieve it, we would have to risk diplomatic tensions, or even military conflict. Our advisors are divided on the best course of action: some argue for diplomacy and negotiation, while others suggest a covert operation to retrieve the artifact without detection.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Archaeologist_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Attempt diplomatic negotiations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Archaeologist_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to attempt diplomatic negotiations, which may improve relations with the alien empire and potentially gain access to the artifact without conflict. However, this approach could also backfire, leading to increased tensions and the loss of valuable time and resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Archaeologist_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Conduct a covert operation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Archaeologist_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>You decide to conduct a covert operation, sending a team of skilled agents to retrieve the artifact without the alien empire's knowledge. If successful, this approach could yield the artifact and invaluable information. However, if the operation is discovered, it could lead to a diplomatic crisis and even war.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C1D_TwinMystery_Name</Label>
        <String>The Twin Enigma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C1D_TwinMystery_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has always been reserved about their past, but recently, they've revealed a secret that adds a layer of depth to their character. They have a twin, who disappeared under mysterious circumstances years ago.[BR][BR]Now, a clue pointing towards the twin's whereabouts has surfaced on a distant colony. However, some advisors caution that this may be a trap by our enemies to lure {LEADERNAME} and destabilize our leadership.[BR][BR]What should we do?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C1D_TwinMystery_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Investigate the clue.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C1D_TwinMystery_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You choose to investigate. This might lead to the return of the missing twin and a boost in morale, but also carries a risk of exposing {LEADERNAME} and your government to unforeseen dangers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C1D_TwinMystery_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Ignore the clue.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C1D_TwinMystery_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} understands the risks and the necessity to maintain stability. However, their focus might be affected by the unanswered questions about their twin, potentially impacting their performance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x5F1E_Vendetta_Name</Label>
        <String>The Unsettled Vendetta</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x5F1E_Vendetta_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} has opened up about a personal vendetta against a notorious pirate lord who, in the past, decimated a colony under {LEADERNAME}'s care.[BR][BR]News arrives that the pirate lord's fleet has been spotted in an uncharted system. {LEADERNAME} requests permission to mobilize a fleet to bring the criminal to justice. However, our advisors argue that devoting resources to this personal quest may expose our civilization to unnecessary risk.[BR][BR]What is our course of action?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x5F1E_Vendetta_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Allow the vendetta to be settled.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x5F1E_Vendetta_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You give the green light. This action could bring a dangerous criminal to justice, boosting security and {LEADERNAME}'s morale, but at a potential cost of resources and ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x5F1E_Vendetta_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Forbid the pursuit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x5F1E_Vendetta_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} is ordered to let go of the past, which could potentially strain your relationship with them. Nonetheless, it preserves resources and keeps the focus on the broader strategic picture.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9E4B_AvoidedService_Name</Label>
        <String>Duty Undone</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9E4B_AvoidedService_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, known for their strategic expertise, confesses a secret from their past: they managed to avoid mandatory service in the Stellar Marines during the Arcean conflicts.[BR][BR]The news has leaked and is starting to cause unrest among our troops who feel betrayed. {LEADERNAME} proposes a public address to clarify the situation and seeks your counsel on how to handle this delicate issue.[BR][BR]What is the best course of action?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9E4B_AvoidedService_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Admit and Apologize.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9E4B_AvoidedService_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} confesses and apologizes publicly. This could improve trust and loyalty among your subjects, but potentially damage the leader's reputation and impact their effectiveness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9E4B_AvoidedService_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Deny and Discredit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9E4B_AvoidedService_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} vehemently denies the allegations and attempts to discredit the sources. This might maintain the leader's effectiveness, but it could deepen the unrest if not everyone is convinced.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B3C_FailedMedSchool_Name</Label>
        <String>Exposed Experiments</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B3C_FailedMedSchool_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your trusted medical advisor, harbors a dark secret from their past. Before becoming a vital member of your government, {LEADERNAME} was pursuing a medical degree. Unfortunately, this quest for knowledge turned sinister as {LEADERNAME} began illegal and unethical experiments on alien species. [BR][BR]These transgressions have now come to light, and the outraged alien governments demand {LEADERNAME}'s extradition. They have vowed retribution if their demands are not met. Yet, handing over {LEADERNAME} will leave a significant void in your medical sector.[BR][BR]What will be your course of action?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B3C_FailedMedSchool_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Protect {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B3C_FailedMedSchool_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Defending {LEADERNAME} will strain your diplomatic relationships, causing a significant decrease in diplomacy and trade for a prolonged period. However, your medical sector will remain strong and effective.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B3C_FailedMedSchool_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Extradite {LEADERNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7B3C_FailedMedSchool_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} will face justice for their actions, appeasing the alien governments and improving your standing with them. However, this choice will result in the loss of a highly skilled individual, thus significantly weakening your medical sector.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9A4E_NoSenseOfSmell_Name</Label>
        <String>A Scentless Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9A4E_NoSenseOfSmell_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your most competent envoy, has always had an unusual deficiency: a complete lack of olfactory sense. This was never a problem, until now. [BR][BR]The Yor Singularity, a synthetic race, has developed an odd form of communication involving intricate combinations of chemical scents. This has opened a new realm of diplomacy. An upcoming intergalactic summit necessitates your envoy's ability to comprehend these 'scent-messages.'[BR][BR]You face a peculiar dilemma: what should you do with {LEADERNAME}?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9A4E_NoSenseOfSmell_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Develop an artificial olfactory device.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9A4E_NoSenseOfSmell_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Investing in cutting-edge technology will allow {LEADERNAME} to decipher the Yor's scented language, opening doors to deeper relations with them. However, the investment will temporarily drain your resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9A4E_NoSenseOfSmell_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Assign another envoy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9A4E_NoSenseOfSmell_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Assigning another envoy will save resources but risks misinterpretation of the Yor's scent-messages, potentially souring your diplomatic relationships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xB2F1_DeceasedFriend_Name</Label>
        <String>The Phantom Friend</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xB2F1_DeceasedFriend_Dec</Label>
        <String>Whispers echo through your corridors. Your ever-faithful aide, {LEADERNAME}, has been spotted masquerading as a friend who passed away years ago. The strange impersonation wouldn't have been much of a concern, until a shocking piece of information surfaces: {LEADERNAME} might have been the one who murdered the deceased friend.[BR][BR]It is an explosive revelation. How should you handle this?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xB2F1_DeceasedFriend_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Initiate an investigation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xB2F1_DeceasedFriend_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>An investigation may clear {LEADERNAME}'s name if they're innocent, and justice will be served if they're guilty. However, the process might sow discord among your ranks and consume valuable resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xB2F1_DeceasedFriend_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Dismiss the allegations as rumors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xB2F1_DeceasedFriend_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Dismissing the allegations will maintain unity and conserve resources. However, you may risk harboring a potential murderer, and the unresolved rumors might tarnish your leadership's image.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xC3D2_WharfRat_Name</Label>
        <String>The Wharf Rat and the Arnorian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xC3D2_WharfRat_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, one of your most resourceful aides who has a background as a wharf rat, seems to have attracted a remarkable ally. An ancient Arnorian, a representative of an advanced and enigmatic race known for their mysterious ways, has been clandestinely guiding {LEADERNAME}, expressing gratitude for your fostering of their protg's growth.[BR][BR]As a reward for your actions, the Arnorian offers to benefit your civilization in one of two ways. You must choose wisely.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xC3D2_WharfRat_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Request advanced technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xC3D2_WharfRat_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Requesting advanced technology from the Arnorian will significantly boost your civilization's scientific development. However, the sudden and unexplained leap forward might cause concern among your people and other civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xC3D2_WharfRat_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Ask for wisdom and guidance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xC3D2_WharfRat_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By asking for wisdom and guidance, you can foster a deeper understanding of the cosmos, significantly improving your diplomacy and influence. However, the subtlety of this choice may leave some of your people feeling that a grand opportunity was wasted.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xD5F3_MilitaryChild_Name</Label>
        <String>The Child of the Stars</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xD5F3_MilitaryChild_Dec</Label>
        <String>While reminiscing about their past, {LEADERNAME}, a child of a military family who spent their youth patrolling the vast expanse of the solar system, mentions an artifact they found during their travels. They offer to give this artifact to the cause, believing its latent powers could provide a crucial advantage to our civilization.[BR][BR]Our scientists have examined the artifact and discovered that it holds the potential to significantly boost the speed of our ships within our territory. Alternatively, {LEADERNAME} has suggested that they may be able to unlock other potential powers if allowed to keep and study the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xD5F3_MilitaryChild_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Take the artifact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xD5F3_MilitaryChild_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>By taking the artifact, we can unlock its power to boost the speed of our ships within our territory. However, this will inevitably draw attention from other civilizations who may seek the artifact for themselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xD5F3_MilitaryChild_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Let {LEADERNAME} keep it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0xD5F3_MilitaryChild_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By allowing {LEADERNAME} to keep the artifact, we open the door to other potential powers that might be unlocked. However, the full potential of the artifact remains unknown, and it could also attract dangerous interest.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_0x62A3_Name</Label>
        <String>The Rare Resource Proposition</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_0x62A3_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} contacts you with news.[BR][BR] A mining conglomerate has discovered a deposit of crystalized Elerium on {PLANETNAME}, a material vital for advanced energy systems and weaponry. The conglomerate offers two proposals. [BR][BR]The first is to mine the resource using an AI based strip mining, which will bring immediate economic benefits but could harm the local environment and populace. [BR][BR]The second is to mine it sustainably, ensuring the well-being of the planet but at a slower economic pace.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_1_0x62A3_Name</Label>
        <String>Mine it all now. Who cares about alien whales and other space fish?</String> 
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_1_0x62A3_Dec</Label>
        <String>You will gain credits immediately but it will create a bit of an environmental catastrophe.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_2_0x62A3_Name</Label>
        <String>Take your time. We are in no hurry.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_2_0x62A3_Dec</Label>
        <String>You will use slower but gentler techniques to extract the resource.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_0x72B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Artifact found</String>
    </StringTable>


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_0x72B4_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} reaches out with intriguing news.[BR][BR] A mysterious ancient artifact has been unearthed on {PLANETNAME}. The artifact emits a unique frequency. Experts present two choices: Harvest the frequency as an energy source, which can be a boon for our reserves, or dedicate resources to decode it for ancient knowledge. The choice is yours.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_1_0x72B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Harvest the energy.</String> 
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_1_0x72B4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We will benefit from a sudden boost in energy, but may face backlash for destroying a piece of history.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_2_0x72B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Decode its secrets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_2_0x72B4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We'll gain knowledge possibly accelerating our technological growth, but will miss out on the immediate energy boost.</String>
    </StringTable>


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_0x82C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Controversial Visit</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_0x82C5_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} sends an urgent transmission.[BR][BR] Ambassador Zaraq from the {PLAYERFACTION:1} wishes to visit {PLANETNAME} for a diplomatic summit. [BR][BR]The ambassador is not popular.[BR][BR]Really really not popular.[BR][BR]Do we grant the visit or decline diplomatically?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_1_0x82C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Grant the visit.</String> 
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_1_0x82C5_Dec</Label>
        <String>Strengthening ties with the {PLAYERFACTION:1} might lead to new opportunities, but risks unrest among our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_2_0x82C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline the visit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_2_0x82C5_Dec</Label>
        <String>Peace within the colony will be maintained, but our relations with the {PLAYERFACTION:1} suffer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_0x92D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Harvesting Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>Governor {LEADERNAME} contacts you with an intriguing proposition. [BR][BR]The {PLAYERFACTION:1} have expressed interest in harvesting a unique plant from {PLANETNAME}. This flora produces a resin that is a potent ingredient for various beneficial chemicals. However, this resin can also be refined into a potent and addictive drug. [BR][BR]Allowing the harvest would bolster relations and boost planetary income, but could also lead to increased crime rates on the colony.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_1_0x92D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Allow the harvest. Our finances could use the boost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_1_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>Relations with {PLAYERFACTION:1} will improve and the planet's economy will improve, but crime will rise on {PLANETNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_2_0x92D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Deny the request. We don't want the syndicate to show up.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_2_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>Relations with {PLAYERFACTION:1} will deteriorate but at least the crime will remain unchanged on {PLANETNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Relations_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>You spurned our Ambassador</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_0xA7F4_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ancient Enigma</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_0xA7F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>Governor {LEADERNAME} sends you a transmission detailing the discovery of an ancient Arnorian facility on {PLANETNAME}. [BR][BR]The energy signal it emits could be of great value, but the indigenous species we've encountered on the planet consider it sacred ground. [BR][BR]Should we harness its energy or respect the local beliefs?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_1_0xA7F4_Name</Label>
        <String>Extract the energy. Might makes right.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_1_0xA7F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We will harness the facility's energy, boosting our surplus manufacturing reserves but possibly straining relations with the indigenous species on {PLANETNAME}.[BR][BR]No immediate consequences to be seen.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_2_0xA7F4_Name</Label>
        <String>Respect the sacred site. We shouldn't interfere.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_2_0xA7F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We decide to honor the indigenous species' beliefs, ensuring peace on {PLANETNAME} but foregoing the potential energy resource.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_0xB8A2_Name</Label>
        <String>The Plague</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_0xB8A2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Governor {LEADERNAME} reaches out with alarming news: a mysterious illness has struck {PLANETNAME}. A locally developed experimental drug might combat the disease, but its potential side effects are unknown. [BR][BR]Relying solely on approved treatments will curb the epidemic but slow the planet's growth for years. How should we proceed?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_1_0xB8A2_Name</Label>
        <String>Compel the population to use the experimental drug.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_1_0xB8A2_Dec</Label>
        <String>The experimental drug is distributed widely, potentially preventing further devastation but introducing the risk of unknown side effects. </String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_2_0xB8A2_Name</Label>
        <String>Use only approved treatments. Safety first.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_2_0xB8A2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By using only the tried-and-tested methods, we ensure the well-being of our citizens, even if it means a setback for {PLANETNAME}'s growth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_0xD4E2_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Exchange Proposition</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_0xD4E2_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached Governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with an intriguing offer. They wish to establish a cultural exchange office on our planet, promising aid in our manufacturing endeavors. [BR][BR]However, our intelligence suggests this could serve as a cover for their espionage activities. [BR][BR]Accepting their offer might bolster our production, but at the potential risk of a spy network. Rejecting might offend them. How should we proceed?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_1_0xD4E2_Name</Label>
        <String>Accept the offer. We'll take the risk for the aid.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_1_0xD4E2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We decide to welcome the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} and their cultural exchange office, receiving their manufacturing aid but also exposing ourselves to potential espionage. [BR][BR]No immediate consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_2_0xD4E2_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline politely. We cannot risk our security.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_2_0xD4E2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We choose to prioritize our security, declining the offer of the {PLAYERFACTION:1} . This might sour our relations, but our planet's security remains uncompromised. [BR][BR]No immediate consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_0xF3A8_Name</Label>
        <String>Observation Post</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached Governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with an unusual request. They wish to set up an observation post to study our society and culture. In exchange, they are offering us advanced technology. [BR][BR]However, our citizens are deeply uncomfortable with the idea of being under the watchful eyes of the {PLAYERFACTION:1}. [BR][BR]While their technology is tempting, we must consider the well-being of our people. Declining might be seen as an insult to the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}. What should we do?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_1_0xF3A8_Name</Label>
        <String>Accept the offer. We could use some tech.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_1_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>We grant the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} their observation post in exchange for their technology. However, our citizens may feel uneasy about their new observers. [BR][BR]No immediate consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_2_0xF3A8_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline. This isn't an ant farm.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_2_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>We prioritize the well-being and comfort of our citizens, denying the {PLAYERFACTION:1} request.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Diplomatic_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>You denied our observation post</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_0xG4B9_Name</Label>
        <String>Codex Offer</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached the governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with a unique offer: they are willing to share a codex of Universal Truths in exchange for some ancient relics that have little value to us but are of great importance to them.[BR][BR]The Codex would increase the cultural value of this planet given its historic value.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_1_0xG4B9_Name</Label>
        <String>Accept the Offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_1_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've chosen to trade the relics for the codex, hoping the knowledge within will increase this world's influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_2_0xG4B9_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline the Offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_2_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>We respectfully decline the {PLAYERFACTION:1} proposal, choosing to safeguard the relics. This may affect relations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Diplomatic_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>You declined our Codex</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_0xH5C1_Name</Label>
    <String>Historic Revelation</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>The ancient {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached the governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with a profound offer: they wish to share their ancient history that reveals the tales of the Arnor, Dread Lords, and the momentous Precursor wars.[BR][BR]Such knowledge can be both a blessing and a curse, reshaping the beliefs and culture of the local population.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_1_0xH5C1_Name</Label>
    <String>Accept the Revelation.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_1_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By accepting this history it undermines many traditional beliefs.  It will give us a short-term burst of knowledge but some unrest for a time.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_2_0xH5C1_Name</Label>
    <String>Decline the Offer.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_2_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We decline the offer, choosing to let our population remain blissfully ignorant.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Diplomatic_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Your civilization is provincial</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_0xJ6D2_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Agreement Proposal</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with a lucrative trade agreement. This deal promises to greatly elevate the planet's economy, but locals have voiced their concerns over the influx of alien visitors it might bring.[BR][BR]The potential for cultural enrichment is immense, yet so is the potential for tension.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_1_0xJ6D2_Name</Label>
    <String>Accept the Trade Agreement.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_1_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We embrace the trade deal, anticipating the economic boom it will bring. However, we must also be prepared for potential cultural clashes due to the new alien visitors and their various smells.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_2_0xJ6D2_Name</Label>
    <String>Nope. No thanks.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_2_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Choosing the wishes of the local population, we decline the trade deal, potentially souring relations with the {PLAYERFACTION:1}.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Diplomatic_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>You refused our trade offer.</String>
</StringTable>



</StringTableList>