<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9AB4_HealthDiscovery_Name</Label>
        <String>The Unexpected Discovery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9AB4_HealthDiscovery_Desc</Label>
        <String>While the quest for immortality led by {LEADERNAME} did not uncover the secret to eternal life, it resulted in an unexpected and groundbreaking discovery. The expedition team has found advanced techniques that significantly improve health, prenatal care, and overall life expectancy. This knowledge can be used to boost our population growth.[BR][BR]Implementing these techniques will have a lasting impact on the health and wellbeing of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9AB4_HealthDiscovery_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Implement the health advancements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x9AB4_HealthDiscovery_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>By adopting these new health techniques, we can ensure a healthier, stronger population, boosting our growth rates. While it's not the immortality we sought, it's a significant step forward for our civilization's future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Name</Label>
        <String>The Defector's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}'s close friend, a top scientist, defected from their home planet with classified technology, bringing it to your civilization. This has given you a technological edge. However, their former government demands their return, along with the technology. Your advisors are split: some suggest compliance to improve diplomatic relations, while others recommend refusal to protect your friend and maintain your advantage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Comply with the demand.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You comply with the demand, returning your friend and the technology. Diplomatic relations improve, but it costs you the technological advantage and strains your leadership, as your friend's trust is betrayed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Refuse the demand.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Refusing to surrender your friend and the technology, you keep the advantage. Your loyalty and intelligence as a leader are reinforced, but diplomatic relations suffer significantly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice1_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>+3 Relations with the {PLAYERFACTION:1} for 50 months[BR]{GOVERNORNAME} loses the Smart Friend trait</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC3_DefectingScientist_Choice2_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>-5 Relations with the {PLAYERFACTION:1} for 50 months</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_Dimension_choice1_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>Gain 3 charges of [HS=HS_ArtifactWormhole]Wormhole Generator[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C61_Liberation_choice_0_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>2 Free Citizens on {PLANETNAME}</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB5_PlagueSurvivor_choice_0_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>Future outcome unknown</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7C32_Tactics_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, your brilliant strategist, has become infamous for their ruthless tactics. Their latest plan could drastically increase the effectiveness of planetary sieges, but such tactics would result in significant civilian casualties. While the strategy may help turn the tide of conflict, it could also provoke outrage and moral condemnation from your people and the galactic community.[BR][BR]Your advisors are divided, with some arguing that the potential benefits outweigh the risks, while others advocate for a more measured and cautious approach. The choice ultimately falls on you to decide whether to authorize {LEADERNAME}'s ruthless tactics or to seek alternative strategies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB6_PlagueBreakthrough_Name</Label>
        <String>Plague Research Breakthrough</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB6_PlagueBreakthrough_Dec</Label>
        <String>Following {LEADERNAME}'s courageous decision to assist the scientists, a significant breakthrough has been made in controlling the deadly plague. The team, with {LEADERNAME}'s help, discovered a method to significantly reduce the spread of the disease. This achievement not only helps in combating the plague but also reduces overall pollution levels. {LEADERNAME}, despite their personal turmoil, has shown exceptional resolve and social acumen in this crisis. However, the emotional toll of revisiting their past is still evident.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB6_PlagueBreakthrough_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Recognize the team's success and {LEADERNAME}'s contribution.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB6_PlagueBreakthrough_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>You publicly commend the research team's success and {LEADERNAME}'s invaluable contribution. This achievement not only bolsters {LEADERNAME}'s reputation but also marks a pivotal moment in your civilization's scientific advancements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7AC5_Terraformer_Choice1_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>4 Free Irradiated Citizens on {PLANETNAME}</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_Name</Label>
        <String>Revolutionary Energy Source</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, a visionary in your ranks, has developed a revolutionary new energy source. This breakthrough promises to redefine our civilization's energy landscape. However, its implementation comes with crucial decisions that will impact our society and environment.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Implement the new energy source.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>By choosing to implement this new energy source, we significantly boost our mineral production at the cost of increased pollution. The benefits are tangible, but the environmental impact cannot be ignored.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Monetize the invention.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Opting to monetize the invention, we sell the technology to other civilizations. This decision brings a substantial influx of credits, providing immediate financial gain without directly affecting our environmental footprint.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x6AB7_EnergyInnovation_choice_0_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>{GOVERNORNAME} gains the Energy Source Inventor trait</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC5_EnergySource_choice_1_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>Future outcome unknown</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC6_RivalRetaliation_Name</Label>
        <String>Tragic Outcome of Deception</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC6_RivalRetaliation_Dec</Label>
        <String>The fallout from planting the fake blueprints has taken a grim turn. Rival factions, enraged upon discovering the deception, have escalated their efforts to obtain the real technology. In a drastic move, they attempted to kidnap {LEADERNAME}, the inventor of the revolutionary energy source. Tragically, the confrontation led to {LEADERNAME}'s untimely death, leaving a void in your leadership and a sour note in diplomatic relations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC6_RivalRetaliation_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Mourn the loss.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC6_RivalRetaliation_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>In the wake of this tragic event, you choose to mourn the loss of {LEADERNAME} and take measures to prevent such incidents in the future. The incident has strained your diplomatic relations, and the need for heightened security is evident.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7BC6_RivalRetaliation_choice_0_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} dies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_0x7A14_MutinySurvivor_choice_0_BonusDec</Label>
        <String>2 Free Citizens on {PLANETNAME}</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>