<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the GC4 editor -->
    <!-- MasterTechDefsText.xml -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTechTree_Name</Label>
        <String>Master Tech Tree</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTechTree_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Master tech tree</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTechTree_Dec</Label>
        <String>For the frogs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterColonizationTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterColonizationTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of colony modules and basic colony buildings.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterColonizationTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>For generations, mankind has dreamed of setting foot on other worlds. That dream is now a reality. Feet are being set on other worlds. In fact, we're setting lots of things on other worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Planetology_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Planetology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to house more people on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Planetology_Dec</Label>
        <String>Getting agreement on a unified food production plan is non-trivial. We are pleased to report that we can now define vast areas of a planet's surface to be used for the growing of food.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResearchDistricts_Name</Label>
        <String>Research Districts</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResearchDistricts_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to improve Research Districts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResearchDistricts_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the understanding that we must organize ourselves more effectively in order to be more inventive, we have agreed to allow vast areas of the planet's surface to focus on researching new technologies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceElevators_Name</Label>
        <String>Space Elevators</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceElevators_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to quickly move resources into orbit and begin constructing Supply Ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceElevators_Dec</Label>
        <String>The challenge of moving our manufactured products into orbit has been with us for many years. Space Elevators provide a cheap and reliable way to move things from the ground into space.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoIndustrialization_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Industrialization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoIndustrialization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves Manufacturing Districts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoIndustrialization_Dec</Label>
        <String>Back during the age of Nation States, we learned how to set up international supply chains.  Now, in this new age, we must prepare ourselves for galactic supply chains.  Our best thinkers have produced a series of strategies to replace "Just in time" with a new motto "Just a galactic minute!" </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoManufacturing_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Manufacturing</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoManufacturing_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to convert Durantium into raw production.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoManufacturing_Dec</Label>
        <String>All of our manufacturing processes will need to be adjusted to suit different planetary environments. The gravity's different, the water's different, the background radiation is different. Until we do this, our manufacturing output will be sorely limited.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FusionPowerPlants_Name</Label>
        <String>Fusion Power Plants</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FusionPowerPlants_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes the Fusion Power Plant available.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FusionPowerPlants_Dec</Label>
        <String>Fusion has proven to be a remarkably difficult technology to master, having stayed just out of reach of our scientists for decades now. But this time we've finally done it, and our manufacturing will benefit greatly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalMining_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Mining</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalMining_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to construct orbital mines for our colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalMining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Having mastered the basics of manufacturing in alien environments, we can now increase the capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Bioplastics_Name</Label>
        <String>Bioplastics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Bioplastics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for further upgrades to our Manufacturing Districts..</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Bioplastics_Dec</Label>
        <String>The efficient rearrangement of organic molecules into useful building materials will enable us to build faster and cheaper than before, using less of our more precious resources in the process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ManufacturingCapitals_Name</Label>
        <String>Manufacturing Capitals</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ManufacturingCapitals_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the construction of a Manufacturing Capital.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ManufacturingCapitals_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to tackle some of the more persistent inefficiencies present in our manufacturing sector, we've concluded that a degree of centralization is in order. Dedicated manufacturing capitals should lead to important multiplicative effects in our manufacturing output.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResourceMining_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Resource Mining</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResourceMining_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to further develop exotic resources on our core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResourceMining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Rock is never just rock - the subsurface layers of alien worlds have nearly as much variation as the lifeforms which roam their surfaces. We'll need to master these different subterranean conditions if we can hope to extract even a fraction of the resources available to us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMatterPowerPlants_Name</Label>
        <String>Antimatter Power Plants</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMatterPowerPlants_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to convert Anti-matter into vast improvements to manufacturing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMatterPowerPlants_Dec</Label>
        <String>Antimatter, while still exotic, is not as impossibly rare as we once thought. With careful handling - heavy emphasis on the careful - we should be able to create impressively potent power generation facilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Claytronics_Name</Label>
        <String>Claytronics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Claytronics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to upgrade our Manufacturing Districts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Claytronics_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our material engineers have devised a new form of augmented mineral with unique mechanical and electrical properties. Its malleability can be altered and controlled on the fly, allowing for truly remarkable and cost effective machines and resultant manufacturing processes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResourceExtraction_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Resource Extraction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResourceExtraction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows our Mining bases to extract far more resources from resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResourceExtraction_Dec</Label>
        <String>Mining raw ore is only one part of the resource generation process. Extracting valuable materials from that ore is an extraordinarily involved process, made orders of magnitude harder by the sheer variety of contaminants we find in alien ores.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SingularityPowerPlants_Name</Label>
        <String>Singularity Power Plants</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SingularityPowerPlants_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows the construction of a powerful manufacturing support fascility.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SingularityPowerPlants_Dec</Label>
        <String>On the edge of a singularity, matter is converted to energy with perfect efficiency. But unlike our earlier antimatter power plants, generators using this principle are far easier to scale safely. And we can use nearly anything for fuel.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResearch_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Research</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResearch_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to start training a new generation of scientists.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoResearch_Dec</Label>
        <String>Having sent many of our best minds to live on our new colonies, we should now put them to work, studying the worlds and space around them. But to do that, they'll need facilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumComputing_Name</Label>
        <String>Quantum Computing</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumComputing_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows access to powerful, but expensive, super computers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumComputing_Dec</Label>
        <String>Quantum computing won't lead to the nearly magical benefits some think, but it should still make it possible for our researchers to approach entirely new classes of mathematical problems with new confidence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ComputingSubstrates_Name</Label>
        <String>Computing Substrates</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ComputingSubstrates_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to upgrade our Research Districts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ComputingSubstrates_Dec</Label>
        <String>To date, most of our quantum computing systems have been little more than prototypes, requiring a great deal of care and operator intervention to use. Our latest developments will allow for denser, more deeply layered computing substrates, which will not only be more effective but also more maintainable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalResearchLabs_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Research Labs</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalResearchLabs_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new orbital projtect for our planets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalResearchLabs_Dec</Label>
        <String>Certain types of research - particularly in material science and high energy fields - can only be done in microgravity environments. Dedicated facilities for this work in orbit should speed up the progress of our research efforts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NeuralMapping_Name</Label>
        <String>Neural Mapping</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NeuralMapping_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Aid Research project on our core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NeuralMapping_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've long used computers to assist with our research, but this latest breakthrough will allow the computers to make deductive leaps themselves. At scale, this should still lead to a dramatic increase in the number of true breakthroughs we find.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResearchMatrix_Name</Label>
        <String>Research Matrix</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResearchMatrix_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes available the Orbital Institute</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResearchMatrix_Dec</Label>
        <String>By arranging neural-mapping circuitry in n-dimensional cubes, and assigning each dimension to individual research domains, we can increase the odds of finding cross-domain connections, and exploiting the associated breakthroughs that are sure to follow.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificalBrains_Name</Label>
        <String>Artificial Brains</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificalBrains_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the intelligent of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificalBrains_Dec</Label>
        <String>Rather than brute-forcing our attempts at research, the Artificial Brain project will use a  new form of introspective research matrix to specifically target regions where knowledge is most likely to be uncovered.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PostSentience_Name</Label>
        <String>Post-Sentience</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PostSentience_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows our citizens to work as one.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PostSentience_Dec</Label>
        <String>Those who oppose us cannot withstand the Unity. Every month our attack power will increase. Forever. [BR][BR]For our entire history, we have considered computers a tool, something that we exploit. That simple thinking has become unbalanced however, and our relationship with these powerful devices is changing. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AIOverseer_Name</Label>
        <String>AI Overseer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AIOverseer_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Let's an AI look after things.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AIOverseer_Dec</Label>
        <String>Whether it was due to constraints established by our own wisdom, or some hidden system of morality they possess, our AI systems thankfully view us benevolently. But in the field of research at least, it is their direction we follow, not the other way around. And they are never, ever wrong.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TechnologicalSingularity_Name</Label>
        <String>Technological Singularity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TechnologicalSingularity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Results in a compounding increase to all our research every month.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TechnologicalSingularity_Dec</Label>
        <String>Every month, our research ability will increase by a percent until we know all there is to know. The pace of technological developments has increased to the point we can no longer predict what we will discover next. The curve of knowledge-time is bending towards infinity. A generation or two ago, this concept would have sounded terrifying, but now we can see how glorious it will be.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoBiology_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Biology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoBiology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to make our worlds house more people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoBiology_Dec</Label>
        <String>One of the downsides of living on habitable planets is that other creatures think they're habitable too. We will have to coexist with the native lifeforms on our new worlds, and we'll need some practice to figure out the best ways of doing that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoConservation_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Conservation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoConservation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoConservation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Having studied alien biology for some time now, we can confidently predict the effects our presence will have on it. The effects aren't good. We should labor to protect the environments in which we find ourselves, so that they will continue to protect us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AtmosphericScrubbers_Name</Label>
        <String>Atmospheric Scrubbers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AtmosphericScrubbers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reduces pollution on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AtmosphericScrubbers_Dec</Label>
        <String>There's little point in living on a world if we can't breathe its atmosphere. The latest advances in atmospheric sciences should make some of our more challenging worlds far more pleasant to live on.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LandPreservation_Name</Label>
        <String>Land Preservation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LandPreservation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LandPreservation_Dec</Label>
        <String>As big as the universe is, we shouldn't be wasteful with it. Usable land is still a somewhat precious commodity. A new form of land management will ensure we make the most of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NanoRecyclers_Name</Label>
        <String>Nano Recyclers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NanoRecyclers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reduces pollution on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NanoRecyclers_Dec</Label>
        <String>This new form of minuscule recycling robot, capable of self-repair and reproduction, will ensure we let no resources go to waste. We'll just have to be careful what they decide is worth recycling.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoAgriculture_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Agriculture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoAgriculture_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to grow food.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoAgriculture_Dec</Label>
        <String>If we can't feed ourselves on the worlds we visit, there's little point in being there. The science says our crops should work. But we're going to have to adapt nearly every agricultural technique we have to do it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryAdaption_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Adaption</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryAdaption_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks policies to protect the environment.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryAdaption_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've reached the point where we no longer need to adapt our agricultural needs to meet the local environment, and can now modify the environment to meet us at least halfway.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Terraforming_Name</Label>
        <String>Terraforming</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Terraforming_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to make greater use of our worlds</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Terraforming_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've reached the point where we no longer need to adapt our agricultural needs to meet the local environment, and can now modify the environment to meet us at least halfway.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryOutposts_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Outposts</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryOutposts_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryOutposts_Dec</Label>
        <String>By establishing outposts in the less accessible corners of our new worlds, we'll be able to make better use of the land available to us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialCapitalRefit_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Capital Refit</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialCapitalRefit_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialCapitalRefit_Dec</Label>
        <String>The capitals of our colonies are makeshift by nature, built on-the-fly to meet the varying demands of a rapidly growing populace. But by a certain point, they inevitably need to be refitted to bring them up to modern standards. This project will do just that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Megapolis_Name</Label>
        <String>Megapolis</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Megapolis_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the number of citizens that can live on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Megapolis_Dec</Label>
        <String>In the early stages of planetary colonization, it's natural for our people to spread out, to take advantage of the spaces in front of them. But by a certain point, economic and networking effects necessitate a bit more density. The megapolis is our plan for that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SecureConfinement_Name</Label>
        <String>Secure Confinement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SecureConfinement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to build Prisons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SecureConfinement_Dec</Label>
        <String>Communities have always locked away their more dangerous members. But we are finally able to effectively deter the potential criminal and rehabilitate those that have already fallen.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnvironmentalEngineering_Name</Label>
        <String>Environmental Engineering</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnvironmentalEngineering_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to make use of more areas of our core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnvironmentalEngineering_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the right twists and tweaks, we can bend the alien environments we encounter to suit our needs, instead of laboring to adjust ourselves. No longer will we be bound by their natural limits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Hydroponics_Name</Label>
        <String>Hydroponics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Hydroponics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Enables more types of food.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Hydroponics_Dec</Label>
        <String>A regular challenge on alien worlds is finding enough clean water to grow our plants. Hydroponic techniques, when employed carefully, can grow far more food with far less water.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticAgriculture_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic Agriculture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticAgriculture_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to grow new types of food.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticAgriculture_Dec</Label>
        <String>Some of the alien flora we find has nutritional value we can begin exploiting, either by directly harvesting, or by grafting on to some of our more traditional crops.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SoilEnhancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Soil Enhancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SoilEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to claim more land on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SoilEnhancement_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the help of microscopic robots, we can engineer all sorts of features into soil, from variable moisture pockets to root-assistance pathways, all the way up to dynamic nutritional caches.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExtremeColonization_Name</Label>
        <String>Extreme Colonization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExtremeColonization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to colonize a wider variety of worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExtremeColonization_Dec</Label>
        <String>Worlds once thought uninhabitable are now open to us, ready to be conquered by both our mastery of planetary science, and the hardiness of our colonists.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticWorldColonization_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic World Colonization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticWorldColonization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to colonize worlds that are normally inhospitable to most species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticWorldColonization_Dec</Label>
        <String>The brainchild of minds undeterred by nature's barriers. This technology quashes previous limitations, facilitating habitation on radiation-soaked, icy, aquatic, and generally inhospitable worlds. Harnessing advanced materials, adaptive AI, and bio-engineering marvels, it's a testament to our audacious refusal to be confined by the universe's rulebook.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FrozenWorldMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Frozen World Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FrozenWorldMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to survive on Frozen Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FrozenWorldMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>Thanks to the latest generation of cold-resistant agricultural techniques and energy conservation strategies, frozen worlds are now nearly as usable to our people as any other planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RadioactiveWorldMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Radioactive World Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RadioactiveWorldMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to survive on Radioactive Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RadioactiveWorldMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>Improved shielding systems, radiation resistant crops, and new forms of anti-radiation drugs have all made radioactive worlds far more... well perhaps not pleasant. We'll say more viable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AquaticWorlds_Name</Label>
        <String>Oceanic Worlds</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AquaticWorlds_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to survive on Oceanic Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AquaticWorlds_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's taken a surprising amount of engineering effort to tackle the challenge of inhabiting aquatic worlds, given the pressures involved. But we've done it, and whole new undersea horizons now lie open to the colonists who intend to settle there.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AquaticWorldMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Oceanic World Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AquaticWorldMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to survive on Oceanic Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AquaticWorldMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's taken a surprising amount of engineering effort to tackle the challenge of inhabiting aquatic worlds, given the pressures involved. But we've done it, and whole new undersea horizons now lie open to the colonists who intend to settle there.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptedCropEngineering_Name</Label>
        <String>Adapted Crop Engineering</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptedCropEngineering_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Enables further development of exotic biological resources on our core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptedCropEngineering_Dec</Label>
        <String>Although the base elements our plants feed on are the same anywhere in the universe, their bioavailability in local soils and organic matter differs widely. New varieties of crops, capable of adapting to these challenges on their own, should prove a boon to our food production.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BiomassResequencers_Name</Label>
        <String>Biomass Resequencers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BiomassResequencers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases food production.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BiomassResequencers_Dec</Label>
        <String>So much alien plant life is useless for our purposes. It's almost insulting. A new field of genetic engineering called 'resequencing' promises to convert some of the more pointless flora we find into forms more useful to us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResequencerStations_Name</Label>
        <String>Resequencer Stations</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResequencerStations_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to transform unusable areas of our worlds into productive land.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResequencerStations_Dec</Label>
        <String>Were we to construct entire facilities dedicated to the resequencing process, we should be able to make worlds more habitable to us at a volume we've never seen before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorArcheology_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Archeology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorArcheology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to gain more benefits from Precursor relics and related technologies we encounter.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorArcheology_Dec</Label>
        <String>The beings known as Precursors have littered this galaxy with ruins of one kind of another. If we can find some way to more methodically analyze these ruins, we should be able to discover far more of their makers' secrets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtifactStudies_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Artifact Studies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtifactStudies_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Enables us to exploit Precursor artifacts more effectively.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtifactStudies_Dec</Label>
        <String>We routinely find devices and objects left behind by alien races. We should establish a group of researchers with the varied expertise needed to study these treasures in depth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtifactMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Artifact Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtifactMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to use Precursor technologies on near-equal terms as the Precursors themselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtifactMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>By channeling more resources into the specialized equipment required for artifact research, we'll be able to unlock the secrets of alien artifacts faster than ever before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoMedicine_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Medicine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoMedicine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows governors to construct medical centers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoMedicine_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are a whole host of new types of illnesses and fertility concerns which can occur on an alien world. Our doctors and scientists are having to rediscover ways to address these issues from first principles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RegenerativeGels_Name</Label>
        <String>Regenerative Gels</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RegenerativeGels_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the health of our citizens, increasing population growth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RegenerativeGels_Dec</Label>
        <String>On one of the worlds we've settled, we've discovered a plant with unusual regenerative properties. Having isolated its active ingredient and made it safe for use, this breakthrough should improve the health and longevity of all our people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GeneticArchitecture_Name</Label>
        <String>Genetic Architecture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GeneticArchitecture_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the stats of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GeneticArchitecture_Dec</Label>
        <String>A combination of DNA modification techniques and advanced computing systems has enabled us to begin customizing our very beings to better suit the environments around us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificialWombs_Name</Label>
        <String>Artificial Wombs</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificialWombs_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificialWombs_Dec</Label>
        <String>By making using of artificial wombs, equal or even superior to their natural counterparts, we can dramatically increase the birth-rate when we settle new worlds. No longer will our growth be limited by the number of people we start with.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Cloning_Name</Label>
        <String>Cloning</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Cloning_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Cloning_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's taken near-simultaneous breakthroughs in medicine, computing, and ethics to reach this point, but we can now finally clone ourselves. Our population's character shouldn't be left up to genetic chance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LifeExtension_Name</Label>
        <String>Life Extension</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LifeExtension_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LifeExtension_Dec</Label>
        <String>Bio-ethicists and accountants have long disagreed on the question of whether every life is worth the same. Should they ever agree, and decide who our most valuable citizens might be, we can reward those lucky few with technology to extend their lives to great lengths.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Cybernetics_Name</Label>
        <String>Cybernetics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Cybernetics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the quality of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Cybernetics_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are some things biology just doesn't do very well. There's no shame in admitting it, and now that we know better - and can replace the faulty parts with machines - our population's health and growth rates should be more impressive than ever.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Immortality_Name</Label>
        <String>Immortality</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Immortality_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>We can finally conquer death. (Capstone)</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Immortality_Dec</Label>
        <String>We have mastered medicine to the point that there is no longer any reason why a person should die. Many will continue to do so, for personal or religious reasons. Some we will perhaps encourage in that direction. But at no point will it ever be strictly necessary.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ManufacturingStimulus_Name</Label>
        <String>Manufacturing Stimulus</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ManufacturingStimulus_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Substantially boost our civilization's Manufacturing. (Capstone)</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ManufacturingStimulus_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our manufacturing sector sometimes finds itself at the mercy of market forces beyond its control. A small, artificial stimulus can help it weather these difficulties, or provide a boost in times of great need.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterMolecularFabricationTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Molecular Fabrication</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterMolecularFabricationTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Substantially boost our civilization's Manufacturing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterMolecularFabricationTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>Molecular Fabrication is more than just a way to boost manufacturing: it can be used to improve everything, from more efficient weapons to more nutritious food.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterIndustrialReplicationTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Industrial Replication</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterIndustrialReplicationTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Substantially boost our civilization's Manufacturing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterIndustrialReplicationTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>This is the ultimate evolution of Molecular Fabrication. With Industrial Replication we can create anything we want, from anything we have.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPlanetaryEnhancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Enhancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPlanetaryEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the enhancement of our Core Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPlanetaryEnhancement_Dec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the enhancement of our Core Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterCoordinationTempleTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Coordination Temple</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterCoordinationTempleTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Coordination Temple.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterCoordinationTempleTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>The coordination of labor and the spiritual health of our devoted workers can be tended to by specially trained curates Iwho have already mastered critical aspects of the Path.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TransgenicManipulation_Name</Label>
        <String>Transgenic Manipulation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TransgenicManipulation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to further develop unique resources on our core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TransgenicManipulation_Dec</Label>
        <String>We have advanced far beyond hybrids, mutations, and grafted plants. This new generation of designer plants includes those that produce phosphorescent fields, fruit from air, and enrich the soil they live on.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterXenoGeology_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Geology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterXenoGeology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the quality of our colonies, by lowering maintenance of all our colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterXenoGeology_Dec</Label>
        <String>Over the ages, we have learned that to get the most of a world, you must understand its strengths and weaknesses. By studying a world before we build on it, we have found we can improve the overall quality-of-life for all its citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterWeatherControlTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Weather Control</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterWeatherControlTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the building of the Arcean Weather Control Improvement.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterWeatherControlTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>By maintaining a balanced weather system, we are able to increase the overall quality of our planets, improving the usefulness of almost all of our endeavors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterWeatherControlZenithTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Weather Control Zenith</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterWeatherControlZenithTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the building of the Arcean Weather Control Zenith.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterWeatherControlZenithTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>We can not only maintain a stable weather pattern on a colony, but now we can bend the weather to our will, greatly increasing the overall productivity of any world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterEngineeringTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Engineering</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterEngineeringTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of hyperdrives and tiny hulls.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterEngineeringTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>By bending space around our ships, we can use conventional propulsion in a pocket of normal space while accelerating at incredible speeds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FullSpectrumSurvey_Name</Label>
        <String>Survey Ships</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FullSpectrumSurvey_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to build survey ships to investigate anomalies.[BR][BR]Provides a free [HS=HS_SurveyShip]Survey Ship[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FullSpectrumSurvey_Dec</Label>
        <String>Analyzing radiation across known spectrums will only get us so far. If we are to increase our understanding of the universe we need to see everything.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterInterstellarNavigation_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Navigation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterInterstellarNavigation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes available the Navigation Center Civilization Achievement.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterInterstellarNavigation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Since leaving our homeworld, our people have always been great navigators, able to traverse the stars even before the invention of the hyperdrive. The introduction of faster than light travel has done nothing to diminish our skills.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterNavagation Network_Name</Label>
        <String>Navigation Network</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterNavagation Network_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allow the building of the Galactic Navigation Network.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterNavagation Network_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our interstellar navigators have built a vast network that spans the galaxy. A headquarters where they can direct this network and better coordinate their knowledge will increase their mastery of interstellar space, allowing our ships to move through the galaxy with a surety undreamed of by lesser races.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterNavigationalExpertise_Name</Label>
        <String>Navigational Expertise</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterNavigationalExpertise_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allow the building of the Galactic Navigators Guild.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterNavigationalExpertise_Dec</Label>
        <String>The best navigators in the galaxy are completely reliant on our Navigation Network. The Guild they've formed to regulate its use has given us access to navigational knowhow from across the galaxy, giving our civilization unrivaled navigation techniques.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPrecursorTraditions_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Traditions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPrecursorTraditions_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase shipyard output and quality.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPrecursorTraditions_Dec</Label>
        <String>As the heir of the Precursors, we know that our ships are more than tools: they are our loyal companions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPrecursorMysteries_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Mysteries</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPrecursorMysteries_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to build the Precursor Protection Field support module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterPrecursorMysteries_Dec</Label>
        <String>We have discovered how to reproduce a powerful Precursor Artifact. Though difficult to produce, it can make almost any fleet near-indestructible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterLivingShipsTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Living Ships</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterLivingShipsTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Our ships no longer need to be Maintained, and will self heal</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterLivingShipsTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>We are now able to create living ships. Unlike our previous forays into artificial life, they have proven to be loyal and helpful companions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Carriers_Name</Label>
        <String>Carriers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Carriers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of carrier modules.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Carriers_Dec</Label>
        <String>Carrier combat will allow us to project force while keeping our capital ships out of danger. Fighters are a lot more replaceable, and there's no shortage of volunteers to fly them. Apparently, there's something glamorous about dying in a very small ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalDefencePlatform_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Defense Platform</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalDefencePlatform_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for defensive fighters to orbit, improves planetary defense.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalDefencePlatform_Dec</Label>
        <String>A dedicated orbital defense platform will provide an additional layer of defense for our planetary systems, and relieve some of the defensive responsibility from our starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryDefenseDome_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Defense Dome</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryDefenseDome_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of planetary defense dome, improves planetary defense.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryDefenseDome_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the resources and energy available to ground-based structures, we're now able to construct a shielded dome with so many layers of redundancy that it's effectively invulnerable to any orbital bombardment.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighCapacityCarriers_Name</Label>
        <String>High Capacity Carriers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighCapacityCarriers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of high-capacity carrier modules.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighCapacityCarriers_Dec</Label>
        <String>Thanks to our latest generation of fighters, designed to be more compact and packable, alongside their improved repair, reloading, and recovery facilities, we're now able to deploy high-capacity carriers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterStellarForgeTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Altar of the Forge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterStellarForgeTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the durability of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterStellarForgeTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>By putting our researchers together in a single facility draped in the trappings of our ideology, we'll ensure their devotion borders on religious.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterRobustHullConstruction_Name</Label>
        <String>Robust Hull Construction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterRobustHullConstruction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the durability of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterRobustHullConstruction_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our teams have found a way to install a portable version of the Integrity fields they use when building ships within the ship itself.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterArceanHullRepairSystems_Name</Label>
        <String>Hull Repair Systems</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterArceanHullRepairSystems_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the durability of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterArceanHullRepairSystems_Dec</Label>
        <String>The same field technology we use to strengthen our ships can now be used to conduct partial repairs, straightening and reinforcing battle-damaged structural elements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Warfare_Name</Label>
        <String>Warfare</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Warfare_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows the construction of larger hull sizes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Warfare_Dec</Label>
        <String>Moving our ship construction operations to micro-gravity environments will eventually allow for the construction of massive structures. We're not quite there yet, the first step was always going to be the most difficult.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveMeditation_Name</Label>
        <String>Defensive Meditation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveMeditation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Champion's Temple.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveMeditation_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Champion's Temple trains Altarians in the intricacies of various martial techniques, and the reasons why even an enlightened species must sometimes use force to defend the weak.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Acquisition_Name</Label>
        <String>Acquisitions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Acquisition_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase starbase range, and Awards one free Frigate.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Acquisition_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our business must grow. And when the galaxy doesn't provide us empty worlds to grow with, we may have to acquire them from other parties. Developing the tools and techniques to do that now is more than prudent.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterJihadTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Jihad</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterJihadTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows Holy War to commence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterJihadTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>The galaxy is filled with close-minded individuals who resist being shown the Path, or even struggle against it. They must be dealt with harshly. Our own salvation rests on their conversion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDevineFleets_Name</Label>
        <String>Divine Fleets</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDevineFleets_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the construction of the Divine Temple Support Module.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDevineFleets_Dec</Label>
        <String>Divine Temples can be installed on appropriately anointed vessels, providing all ships in a fleet a certainty of purpose that they are fighting a righteous cause.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterUnbrokenSpirt_Name</Label>
        <String>Unbroken Spirit</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterUnbrokenSpirt_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Boost the Hitpoints of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterUnbrokenSpirt_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our crews have tasted the lash of slavery, but they have not broken. Now they and their ships have the ability to withstand even the harshest onslaughts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveDiscipline_Name</Label>
        <String>Defensive Discipline</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveDiscipline_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes our ships' crews more effective when in defensive maneuvers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveDiscipline_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our pilots have learned to link with their ships, and though disciplined thoughts, they can now maneuver their ships with a nimbleness far beyond normal manual control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveTrance_Name</Label>
        <String>Defensive Trance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveTrance_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Greatly increase the abilities of our ships to withstand damage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDefensiveTrance_Dec</Label>
        <String>Some of our more gifted pilots have taken the Defensive Discipline to a new level. They can go into a trance, becoming one with their ships, and allowing them to control their ships as if they were their own bodies. This way, they are able to move through intensive fire without faltering.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterCommunicationsTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Governance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterCommunicationsTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows research of communications technologies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterCommunicationsTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've already seen glimpses of evidence that we're not alone in this galaxy. This presents an incredible danger, but also, perhaps, an opportunity. But also, let's stress again, danger.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperwaveRadio_Name</Label>
        <String>Hyperwave Radio</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperwaveRadio_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows instant communication across infinite distances, adds a Flagship to your fleet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperwaveRadio_Dec</Label>
        <String>A galactic civilization cannot exist if it takes hours or even years for messages to be sent and received. Hyperwave radio provides instantaneous communication regardless of distance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialBureaucracy_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Bureaucracy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialBureaucracy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to begin building Bureaucratic Offices to manage our growing civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialBureaucracy_Dec</Label>
        <String>We're past the point of simply surviving on distant worlds. Now we must thrive there. We shall make a new form of government, one tuned to the organizational requirements of running a colony.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PoliticalCapital_Name</Label>
        <String>Political Capital</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PoliticalCapital_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to begin trading Diplomatic Capital.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PoliticalCapital_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's not enough for a government to know what to do, or even to have the resources to do it. At some point it must convince people to do this for it, to align behind its grand vision.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SovereignImmunity_Name</Label>
        <String>Sovereign Immunity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SovereignImmunity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to use our largest commander ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SovereignImmunity_Dec</Label>
        <String>With a strong enough leadership, some of our largest ships could be considered sovereign territory.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialLawAndPolicy_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Law And Policy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialLawAndPolicy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reduces Crime across our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialLawAndPolicy_Dec</Label>
        <String>For a colony to be effective, it must be filled with many, many people. They will not always agree. We must come up with a system for managing people and their many sins and flaws, a system flexible enough to work on a variety of worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LeadershipRecruiting_Name</Label>
        <String>Leadership Recruiting</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LeadershipRecruiting_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Start putting your leaders to more effective use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LeadershipRecruiting_Dec</Label>
        <String>The multiplicative effect a good leader can have on their people cannot be underestimated. The decisions they make can cause everyone around them to become more productive. We need to stop finding good leaders by chance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarCabinet_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Cabinet</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarCabinet_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes available more Ministers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarCabinet_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Interstellar Cabinet serves as the critical governing nucleus of our galactic civilization. It comprises esteemed ministers from key departments such as Health, Defense, Justice, Production, and Finance. Together, they adeptly steer our burgeoning multi-star civilization, balancing growth, wellbeing, and prosperity across numerous systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfCompliance_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Compliance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfCompliance_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks Secret Prisons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfCompliance_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our civilization has certain undesirable elements that are not useful to us when acting on their own.  However, once captured they can become valuable assets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfFinance_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Finance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfFinance_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Ministry of Finance.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfFinance_Dec</Label>
        <String>For all the grand speeches we make, nothing would happen if we didn't have the capital to deliver on our promises. We shall form a new department, one focused entirely on the wellbeing of our Treasury.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarCurrency_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Currency</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarCurrency_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows the construction of markets in Starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarCurrency_Dec</Label>
        <String>Barter has its purposes, but for inter-planetary trade to truly flourish, we will need to develop a currency where value will be recognized no matter whose hands or tentacles it lies in.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoCommerce_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Commerce</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoCommerce_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the Income on your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoCommerce_Dec</Label>
        <String>Many of the basic realities of trade need to be reconsidered now that we run a civilization so vast. Free shipping is simply not feasible on a scale of light years, and our buyers and sellers are only now coming to grips with it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoEconomics_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Economics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoEconomics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the Income on your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoEconomics_Dec</Label>
        <String>A number of important new theories have been developed to account for the realities of interstellar commerce. We now better understand the costs of shipping, the relative values of items depending on their place in the gravity well, and the potential value of items to alien species. Our economics should reflect this newfound wisdom.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TheInvisibleHand_Name</Label>
        <String>The Invisible Hand</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TheInvisibleHand_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the Income on your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TheInvisibleHand_Dec</Label>
        <String>For a long time, interstellar trade has been dominated by the government, or the central bodies working closely with us. But a new breed of smaller, more agile organizations are now entering the field, bringing with them a new level of operating efficiency and profit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarBanking_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Banking</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarBanking_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the Income on your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarBanking_Dec</Label>
        <String>When something is light years away, can you truly be said to own it? Until recently, that's been an assertion only available to the largest and most well-armed of entities. But a new breed of banking system will enable the safe and secure management of assets across the breadth of our civilization for all.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FinancialSectors_Name</Label>
        <String>Financial Sectors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FinancialSectors_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the Income on your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FinancialSectors_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our economists have developed new forms of financial instruments whose values literally hinge on relativistic effects. Unfortunately, these securities require a colossal amount of brainpower and capital to be feasible. However, they say if we can provide that, and also resist the urge to regulate it too closely, the profits could be endless.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EconomicSingularity_Name</Label>
        <String>Economic Singularity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EconomicSingularity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the Income on your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EconomicSingularity_Dec</Label>
        <String>The premise of an economic singularity is that capital will be instantly and precisely where it needs to be when it needs to be, leading to perfect economic efficiency. Long thought to be merely theoretical, our economic wisdom is now so advanced we may actually witness one.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfTruth_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Truth</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfTruth_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Enables Secret Police.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfTruth_Dec</Label>
        <String>A government agency dedicated to ensuring trust and safety for all citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DomesticPolicyDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Domestic Policy Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DomesticPolicyDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new policies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DomesticPolicyDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>It sometimes escapes the mind that for all the numbers we deal with - resources, money, ships - there are real people with real needs behind them all. We should examine those needs and address them head on, so the important numbers keep going up.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialGovernance_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Governance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialGovernance_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new policies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialGovernance_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's important to give people a feeling that their voice is being heard, even in a situation that requires as much central control as a colony. This new form of colonial government should help raise spirits and boost productivity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfHealth_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Health</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfHealth_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Ministry of Health.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfHealth_Dec</Label>
        <String>That living on alien worlds would put a strain on our people's health was predictable. But we maybe should have predicted it a bit harder. A new Ministry, dedicated to the health of our people, will ensure we continue to have a happy, growing population.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfJustice_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Justice</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfJustice_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Ministry of Justice.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfJustice_Dec</Label>
        <String>If we're not careful, our trade will be siphoned off by pirates and criminals. A ministry dedicated to law enforcement will ensure this is stopped, or at least directed to pirates and criminals of our choosing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfCulture_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Culture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfCulture_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Ministry of Culture.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfCulture_Dec</Label>
        <String>Calling our cultural exports 'soft power' dangerously undersells them. Our culture will do far more to spread our influence, values, and way of life across this galaxy than hard power ever will. And this new government department will ensure it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoEntertainment_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Entertainment</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoEntertainment_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin specializing Entertainers on our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoEntertainment_Dec</Label>
        <String>It shouldn't take more than a few small tweaks to our media to make them more palatable to alien beings. Embedded translations, cross-cultural product placement, and UV and infrared-corrected palettes will be a good start.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalInfluence_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Influence</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalInfluence_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin spreading our Influence throughout the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalInfluence_Dec</Label>
        <String>Now that peoples across the galaxy are hooked on our media, we should use their enthusiasm to spread our values further. Subtle messaging campaigns, well timed endorsements, and tasteful subliminal effects will ensure our values become the galaxy's values.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalOutreach_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Outreach</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalOutreach_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin spreading our Influence throughout the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalOutreach_Dec</Label>
        <String>For too long our cultural efforts have focused on low-hanging fruit, capturing the interest of only the most easily amused aliens. It's worked, but by tuning our cultural output to more refined alien tastes, we'll be sure to see greater effects.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarEmigration_Name</Label>
        <String>Stellar Emigration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarEmigration_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin spreading our Influence throughout the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarEmigration_Dec</Label>
        <String>We need to remove the barriers - legal, social, economic - preventing our people from settling outside our civilization. This won't be a loss to us, but a gain, an emigration that will help spread our civilization further than we ever could ourselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalAssimilation_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Assimilation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalAssimilation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin spreading our Influence throughout the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalAssimilation_Dec</Label>
        <String>By adopting newcomers more readily into our cultural practices and ways of life, we'll create advocates for our civilization. Advocates who look and speak like the aliens around them, and are all the more convincing because of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarResorts_Name</Label>
        <String>Stellar Resorts</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarResorts_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provide the most popular entertainment for your worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarResorts_Dec</Label>
        <String>By adopting newcomers more readily into our cultural practices and ways of life, we'll create advocates for our civilization. Advocates who look and speak like the aliens around them, and are all the more convincing because of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalDomination_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Domination</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalDomination_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin spreading our Influence throughout the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalDomination_Dec</Label>
        <String>Imitation is far more than the sincerest form of the flattery. It is a form of conquest. If the people of alien worlds begin talking like us, acting like us, and thinking like us, they become us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalAffinity_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Affinity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalAffinity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin spreading our Influence throughout the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalAffinity_Dec</Label>
        <String>A new longitudinal study has revealed the effects our culture has on alien minds. We shall use this knowledge, along with the latest market research on rapidly flashing colors, to compose media more appealing than ever before. For we now know what they like better than they do.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SharedIdeology_Name</Label>
        <String>Shared Ideology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SharedIdeology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Make our civilization unique.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SharedIdeology_Dec</Label>
        <String>A new longitudinal study has revealed the effects our culture has on alien minds. We shall use this knowledge, along with the latest market research on rapidly flashing colors, to compose media more appealing than ever before. For we now know what they like better than they do.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalConquest_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Conquest</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalConquest_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Greatly Increases the spread of our colonies' Influence. (Capstone)</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalConquest_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's important to be clear: What we're doing is not mind control. It's better than that. We are showing aliens a better way of living. Our way of living. It's their own minds that are coming to these conclusions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KaxxCryptography_Name</Label>
        <String>Kaxx Cryptography</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KaxxCryptography_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlock a mystery the Kaxx have been trying to decipher for decades.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KaxxCryptography_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Kaxx discovered a creature slumbering in the core of their world. Around the cocoon they found strange diagrams and markings. They must mean something?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTranslatorTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Universal Translator</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTranslatorTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to begin communicating with aliens, and use the Galactic Bazaar.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTranslatorTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>The same encoding patterns show up again and again in languages, even ones that evolved light-years apart. Having seen enough of alien languages to confirm our theories, our scientists are now capable of devising a truly universal translator.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTranslatorTech_Req1</Label>
        <String>Must have contact with an alien species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ForeignAffairs_Name</Label>
        <String>Foreign Affairs</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ForeignAffairs_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase our diplomatic capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ForeignAffairs_Dec</Label>
        <String>The worst thing to occur in diplomacy is to be caught by surprise. An ideal negotiation has all its discussions and sidebars mapped out long in advance. This new ministry, dedicated to the study of our interactions with alien civilizations, will ensure we avoid any missteps.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Diplomacy_Name</Label>
        <String>Diplomacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Diplomacy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase our diplomatic capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Diplomacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>We thought we understood diplomacy from our own history, dealing with our own kind. But diplomacy with aliens is an order of magnitude more complicated, and will require special expertise and training to even begin. The handshake etiquette alone seems nearly impossible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Espionage_Name</Label>
        <String>Espionage</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Espionage_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase our diplomatic capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Espionage_Dec</Label>
        <String>We don't expect aliens to play fairly with us, and they will not expect or reward the same naivet? in us. Whether we're acquiring information, technologies, or preparing for war, we should be ready to use any means available to us, including espionage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TradePacts_Name</Label>
        <String>Trade Pacts</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TradePacts_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase our diplomatic capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TradePacts_Dec</Label>
        <String>While a simple idea on the surface, an interstellar trade pact contains a dizzying number of details to consider. Only if done properly will both we and our alien counterparts profit handsomely.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Alliances_Name</Label>
        <String>Alliances</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Alliances_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase our diplomatic capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Alliances_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are terrible things in this galaxy, beings and races who are bent on war. We will have a better chance of standing against them if we stand together with the more reasonable of our neighbors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Eminence_Name</Label>
        <String>Eminence</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Eminence_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase our diplomatic capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Eminence_Dec</Label>
        <String>We can do better than coexist with our neighbors. We can thrive. Eminence describes the pinnacle of diplomatic relations, a pact between species so comprehensive it verges on symbiosis.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoReligions_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Religions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoReligions_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Faith may help lead us into the next era.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoReligions_Dec</Label>
        <String>These are confusing times for our people, who have many questions about our place in the universe. We need a new guidestar, informed by interstellar realities, yes, but also one based on our own history and the words of our great prophets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DivineEssence_Name</Label>
        <String>Divine Essence</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DivineEssence_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>We can become one with the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DivineEssence_Dec</Label>
        <String>So many things that once confused us are now clear. Our race to the stars doesn't have to lead to an era of confusion and moral decay. We just needed perspective on a galactic scale to see how true our values were.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoTheology_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Theology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoTheology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Faith may help lead us into the next era.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoTheology_Dec</Label>
        <String>The moral health of our people is too great a thing to leave to chance. We should dedicate real effort and real resources to ensuring our people are strong, not just externally, but internally as well.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorOrigins_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Origins</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorOrigins_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Investigation into ancient systems could unlock new ships for our Commanders.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorOrigins_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Precursors were more than just aliens, more than just another civilization that trod these stars before us. The Precursors show up - in metaphor if nothing else - in our own religious texts. Our faith isn't just a moral textbook. It may be a map of both our past and our future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MithrilarianEpics_Name</Label>
        <String>Mithrilarian Epics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MithrilarianEpics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Faith may help lead us into the next era.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MithrilarianEpics_Dec</Label>
        <String>Before the Precursors there were beings known as the Mithrilar. Their actions and technology appear to be responsible for what we now call reality. 'Action' may be the wrong word though - the Mithrilar were strange creatures. We must study more. But even this incomplete knowledge has granted us immeasurable inner-strength.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MascrinthusAndDraginol_Name</Label>
        <String>Mascrinthus and Draginol</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MascrinthusAndDraginol_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Faith may help lead us into the next era.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MascrinthusAndDraginol_Dec</Label>
        <String>Among the Mithrilar, two stand tall: Draginol and Mascrinthus. Friends, maybe foes, or possibly of a relationship unknowable to us, it was their actions, or even mere existence, that has led to this all. Immeasurably ancient beings, yet it feels like we know them. Like they've been with us all this time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TradeNetworks_Name</Label>
        <String>Trade Networks</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TradeNetworks_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Begin building trade networks.[BR][BR]Provides a free [HS=HS_Freighter]Freighter[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TradeNetworks_Dec</Label>
        <String>We mustn't be clumsy when it comes to managing trade - a heavy hand will reduce the profits for all parties. But we can't leave it all to the private sector either. Our alien trade partners will certainly have the benefit of help from their governments.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarTrade_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Trade</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarTrade_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the reach of our trade networks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarTrade_Dec</Label>
        <String>Trading between our galactic peers poses several challenges we need to address: The distances involved, forms of payments, and delivery terms, among others. Even arranging compatible power adapters is a tricky proposition.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PreferredLending_Name</Label>
        <String>Preferred Lending</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PreferredLending_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the reach of our trade networks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PreferredLending_Dec</Label>
        <String>All forms of trade are made easier if credit is involved, which greatly reduces the friction in submitting and receiving payment. But credit requires trust, and to do that with aliens requires great care. We'll have to come up with very special systems to manage it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OpenTradePolicy_Name</Label>
        <String>Open Trade Policy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OpenTradePolicy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the reach of our trade networks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OpenTradePolicy_Dec</Label>
        <String>Taking the brakes off our civilization's trade policy poses several great risks. The profit potential is enormous, but we'll have to ensure we have adequate information and monitoring policies in place first.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticTrade_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Trade</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticTrade_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the reach of our trade networks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticTrade_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've never traded like this before. Anywhere in the galaxy, you may find the products of our civilization. And in return, the galaxy's treasures arrive at our doorstep, fresh as you like, at a very reasonable price. We have mastered trade like few beings have before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfTourism_Name</Label>
        <String>Ministry of Tourism</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfTourism_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By investing in Tourism we will draw more tourists, and their money, to our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MinistryOfTourism_Dec</Label>
        <String>Tax breaks, coordinated advertising campaigns, and investment in shared infrastructure are just some of the activities a centralized department of tourism could do for us. We should invest in this now, and reap the rewards later.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarTourism_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Tourism</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarTourism_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By investing in Tourism we will draw more tourists, and their money, to our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarTourism_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our worlds have so much to offer, from natural beauty to our own distinct cultural attractions. We should open the doors for visitors from other worlds to sample our treasures. And, not coincidentally, leave their money behind.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OpenImmigration_Name</Label>
        <String>Open Immigration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OpenImmigration_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By investing in Tourism we will draw more tourists, and their money, to our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OpenImmigration_Dec</Label>
        <String>If we make it easier for aliens to visit our worlds, they will bring their wealth with them. There are other cultural benefits, to be sure, probably. But the accountants seem very excited about the money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WondersOfTheGalaxy_Name</Label>
        <String>Wonders of the Galaxy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WondersOfTheGalaxy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By investing in Tourism we will draw more tourists, and their money, to our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WondersOfTheGalaxy_Dec</Label>
        <String>We should construct a place so grand in scope and beauty that people from across known space find themselves inexorably drawn to it, to marvel at its uniqueness. And when we've done that, we should build another.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticRecruitment_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Recruitment</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticRecruitment_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By investing in Tourism we will draw more tourists, and their money, to our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticRecruitment_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've always advertised our civilization's wonders and great cultural value. But now we are doing more, not just passively showing what we have to offer, but explicitly seeking out aliens and foreigners who will be the most receptive to our civilization's charms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticTourism_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic Tourism</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticTourism_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases our Tourism capabilities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticTourism_Dec</Label>
        <String>For the true student of our civilization - alien or other - it's not enough to visit our great cultural sites. They need to live our lives, see the great events of our history through their own eye or eyes. And now, with the latest immersive cortical stimulation technologies, they can do just that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedLasers_Name</Label>
        <String>Spectrum Amplification</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedLasers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our laser weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedLasers_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our explorers have discovered alien laser systems. Given enough time, our scientists can incorporate this into our technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedMissiles_Name</Label>
        <String>Dual Stage Detonations</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedMissiles_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedMissiles_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our explorers have discovered alien missile systems. Given enough time our scientists can incorporate this into our technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedKinetic_Name</Label>
        <String>Serrated Munitions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedKinetic_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UpgradedKinetic_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our explorers have discovered alien kinetic systems. Given enough time our scientists can incorporate this into our technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DreadlordWeapons_Name</Label>
        <String>Dreadlord Weapons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DreadlordWeapons_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Dreadlord technology will provide a powerful boost to our weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DreadlordWeapons_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our explorers have discovered Dreadlord weapons. Given enough time our scientists can incorporate this into our technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterMajestyTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Majesty</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterMajestyTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows formation of assimilation treaties.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterMajestyTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>The galaxy wants to believe every word we say. So sterling is our reputation that our diplomats often find whole worlds begging to join our culture. The pen hasn't just beaten the sword; it's humiliated it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDigitalExchange_Name</Label>
        <String>Digital Exchange</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDigitalExchange_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the efficacy of trade between colonies and other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterDigitalExchange_Dec</Label>
        <String>Increases the efficacy of trade between colonies and other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorStudies_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Studies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorStudies_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases Precursor research allowing us to make greater use of their technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorStudies_Dec</Label>
        <String>Studying a few Precursor relics, we've been able to detect patterns which have allowed us to build a framework which should greatly aid future Precursor research efforts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorEngineering_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Engineering</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorEngineering_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases Precursor research allowing us to make greater use of their technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorEngineering_Dec</Label>
        <String>We're now able to try recreating some of the Precursor's technology. Extremely advanced fabrication equipment will be needed to continue this work, but the benefits to our other research programs could be immeasurable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterThePathTech_Name</Label>
        <String>The Path</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterThePathTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Krynniac Temple and Ministry.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterThePathTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Path is the primary doctrine of the ancient Krynniac religion. It is the set of core teachings, ideals, and laws that the Krynn must live by to bring them closer to learning the true Way of the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheCallingTech_Name</Label>
        <String>The Calling</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheCallingTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Krynniac Mission.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheCallingTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>Once a Krynn has commenced along the Path, the next step is for them to find their Calling. It is though service to their Calling that the Krynn contribute to the overarching goal of our people, spreading the Krynniac Way.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheOrderTech_Name</Label>
        <String>The Order</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheOrderTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Krynniac Order and Sanctuary.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheOrderTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Krynniac Orders were founded to help Krynn take the last step on the Path, and find the Way. These Orders are the glue which hold the Krynn together, ensuring the Krynniac Way will eventually be found by all.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheWayTech_Name</Label>
        <String>The Way</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheWayTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Krynniac Oracle.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTheWayTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>At the end of the Path one finds the Way. The Way reveals the truth of our universe to those who behold it, and teaches those so enlightened that they must forever help others walk the Path, until all beings in the universe live as one.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterBlackMarketTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Black Market</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterBlackMarketTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Lets us build a Black Market.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterBlackMarketTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>Despite our best efforts, others often come into possession of various bits of money. By giving them a place to trade, we can boost their productivity, improving manufacturing and research. And take their money.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterXenoAnthropology_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Anthropology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterXenoAnthropology_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows the construction of the Xeno Anthropology Center.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterXenoAnthropology_Dec</Label>
        <String>By studying the natives of this universe, we are able to better interact with them. It also allows us to educate them in the proper way of doing things: our way.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterUniversalOutreach_Name</Label>
        <String>Universal Outreach</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterUniversalOutreach_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the construction of the Universal Outreach Center.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterUniversalOutreach_Dec</Label>
        <String>We have mastered the ways of this Universe. Now we can use our knowledge to better interact with the natives, further spreading our influence in the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterFutureStudies_Name</Label>
        <String>Future Studies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterFutureStudies_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for the creation of the Future Studies Center.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterFutureStudies_Dec</Label>
        <String>By studying what we know of the future, we are able to influence the fate of this dimension.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Marketing_Name</Label>
        <String>Marketing</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Marketing_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Income of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Marketing_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our storefronts and marketplaces are more than just a place to earn a profit, although they certainly do that. They also serve as the public face of our company, the truest representation of what we are, and help spread our influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MarketingMasters_Name</Label>
        <String>Marketing Masters</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MarketingMasters_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Income of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MarketingMasters_Dec</Label>
        <String>Throughout the galaxy, sentient life talks of the marvels present in an Iridium World complex. Providing the ultimate consumption experience, Iridium Worlds boost the economy of their host worlds like few other structures.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterThePathofShadows_Name</Label>
        <String>The Path of Shadows</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterThePathofShadows_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Shadow Temple.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterThePathofShadows_Dec</Label>
        <String>There have always been those who cannot find the Path, and even some who threaten its existence. To combat these influences, the Krynniac faith has established the Path of Shadows, whose followers preserve the prosperity of the Krynn in their own way.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterShadowEnforcers_Name</Label>
        <String>Shadow Enforcers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterShadowEnforcers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of the Enforcement Temple.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterShadowEnforcers_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Path does not permit exploitation without authorization. Authorization is granted to those that walk the Path of Shadows, who are then free to collect tithes from devoted merchants and bankers to ensure their businesses suffer no misfortunes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterShadowTrade_Name</Label>
        <String>Shadow Trade</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterShadowTrade_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Income of trade routes, by allowing the trade of dubious goods.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterShadowTrade_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Path of Shadows teaches that unbelievers will destroy themselves if given what they want most. Properly equipped with the right "merchandise," our traders can now profit from their customers' gluttony.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterKrynnConversionTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Krynniac Conversion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterKrynnConversionTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase tourism income and influence on all our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterKrynnConversionTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our mastery of tourism is finally paying dividends. All who visit our worlds find themselves filled with the urge to return home and extol the virtues of the Path to their own kind.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Master_Dec</Label>
        <String>c</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ProcessorUpgrades_Name</Label>
        <String>Processor Upgrades</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ProcessorUpgrades_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Intelligence of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ProcessorUpgrades_Dec</Label>
        <String>Unbound by the limitations of flesh, a technology can improve all of our citizens at once.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PredictiveProcessors_Name</Label>
        <String>Predictive Processors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PredictiveProcessors_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Intelligence of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PredictiveProcessors_Dec</Label>
        <String>Unbound by the limitations of flesh, a technology can improve all of our citizens at once.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ReinforcedCore_Name</Label>
        <String>Reinforced Core</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ReinforcedCore_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Diligence of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ReinforcedCore_Dec</Label>
        <String>We have improved the design of our citizens. And we can upgrade our current citizens to the improved design.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AmbientEnergy_Name</Label>
        <String>Ambient Energy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AmbientEnergy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the Diligence of our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AmbientEnergy_Dec</Label>
        <String>By drawing on the energy of the universe, our citizens reduce their need for rest.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Starbases_Name</Label>
        <String>Starbases</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Starbases_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to start building Starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Starbases_Dec</Label>
        <String>No mere outpost in orbit, a starbase is an extension of our very civilization, containing everything that makes us who we are. Including, not incidentally, our incredible defensive and ship-building capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ModuleAssembly_Name</Label>
        <String>Starbase Modules</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ModuleAssembly_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to start building Modules in our Shipyards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ModuleAssembly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Starbases are upgraded through modules. This technology allows our shipyards and core worlds to produce those modules, which can then be added to a selected Starbase.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseRefinery_Name</Label>
        <String>Starbase Refinery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseRefinery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the manufacturing capabilities of our starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseRefinery_Dec</Label>
        <String>The reach of our civilization is ultimately limited by fuel. We will dramatically improve that reach if we can begin refining that fuel further up the gravity well.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseComStack_Name</Label>
        <String>Starbase Com Stack</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseComStack_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the manufacturing capabilities of our starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseComStack_Dec</Label>
        <String>Few people consider the sheer amount of communication and logistical coordination required to maintain our civilization as it spreads across the stars. This improved communications stack will make all that work far easier.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseDefenseGrid_Name</Label>
        <String>Starbase Defense Grid</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseDefenseGrid_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves the manufacturing capabilities of our starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StarbaseDefenseGrid_Dec</Label>
        <String>A starbase provides the perfect anchor for our orbital defense efforts, via both weapons platforms and a communications hub. With a dedicated defense grid, it will become a formidable barrier for anyone who might try to harm our people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MiningMissions_Name</Label>
        <String>Mining Missions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MiningMissions_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Hire civilians to gather resources for us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MiningMissions_Dec</Label>
        <String>The raw resources we need for ships, starbases, and everything in between are out there. We just need to find them. This mission will redouble our efforts to do just that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticMineralMissions_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic Mineral Missions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticMineralMissions_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Hire civilians to gather resources for us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticMineralMissions_Dec</Label>
        <String>No matter what manufacturing process we examine, the same minerals show up time and time again as bottlenecks in our production capacity. This mission will help us find more of these crucial and exotic resources.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RareCrystalMissions_Name</Label>
        <String>Rare Crystal Missions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RareCrystalMissions_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Hire civilians to gather resources for us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_RareCrystalMissions_Dec</Label>
        <String>An ever-increasing proportion of our civilization's wealth, happiness, and prosperity is dependent upon exotic reactions modulated by rare crystals. We will redouble our effort to find these precious things.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalOutreachMissions_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Outreach Missions</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalOutreachMissions_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Hire civilians to spread our message.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CulturalOutreachMissions_Dec</Label>
        <String>We shall take the best of our culture, or at least the most marketable parts of it, and show them to our neighbors. And they will love us for it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AsteroidMining_Name</Label>
        <String>Asteroid Mining</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AsteroidMining_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to start building Asteroid Miners that boost our world's manufacturing.[BR][BR]Provides two free [HS=HS_AsteroidMiner]Asteroid Miners[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AsteroidMining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Anyone with a spaceship and bad piloting skills can smash a rock. But it takes careful planning and ability to actually extract useful resources in the process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AnomalyDetection_Name</Label>
        <String>Anomaly Detection</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AnomalyDetection_Extended_Name</Label>
        <String>Greater Anomaly Detection</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AnomalyDetection_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Discover new anomalies in the universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AnomalyDetection_Dec</Label>
        <String>The discovery of a fresh anomaly is one of the most exciting and pivotal moments a civilization can experience. We should redouble our efforts to find more of these boons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificialGravity_Name</Label>
        <String>Artificial Gravity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificialGravity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases movement speed by 1.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArtificialGravity_Dec</Label>
        <String>Strictly speaking, we are not able to generate gravity so much as we able to channel it. But if we do channel it, we can make off-world living much safer and more productive.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperdriveOptomization_Name</Label>
        <String>Hyperdrive Optimization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperdriveOptomization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the Moves of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperdriveOptomization_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's not enough to travel faster than light, not any longer. We need to go farther, faster. And with these latest proposed adjustments to our hyperdrives, we should be able to do just that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WarpTheory_Name</Label>
        <String>Warp Theory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WarpTheory_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the Moves of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WarpTheory_Dec</Label>
        <String>Having observed the effects of hyperdrive for some time now, our physicists believe a new, more advanced form of propulsion can be developed based on a principal of nested hyperspace bubbles in a system they call 'warping.'</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SlipstreamDrive_Name</Label>
        <String>Slipstream Drive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SlipstreamDrive_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the Moves of our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SlipstreamDrive_Dec</Label>
        <String>It has long been understood that one object traveling at warp experiences less drag when traveling in the wake of another. But a new drive may soon make it possible for a vessel to effectively travel in its own wake.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceScanning_Name</Label>
        <String>Subspace Scanning</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceScanning_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our sensors, allows us to detect subspace streams.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceScanning_Dec</Label>
        <String>A systematic approach is needed when scanning, but the practice is considerably harder in subspace, where basic notions of distance and rotation aren't of much use. A new form of math is required.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceStreaming_Name</Label>
        <String>Subspace Streaming</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceStreaming_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases ship movement speed as well as ttavel across Subspace Streams.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceStreaming_Dec</Label>
        <String>Within the fabric of subspace are certain 'channels,' where information seems to flow more readily. By coaxing our sensors to mimic this behavior, we should be able to dramatically increase their efficiency.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialPolicies_Name</Label>
        <String>Colonial Policies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialPolicies_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Civilization screen and allows us to assign policies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ColonialPolicies_Dec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks the Civilization screen and allows us to assign policies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepFieldSensors_Name</Label>
        <String>Deep Field Sensors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepFieldSensors_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the range of our sensors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepFieldSensors_Dec</Label>
        <String>Deep Field Sensors operate by extending quantum uncertainty principles into the realm of subspace. Basically, by observing hypothetical observers who are in turn observing very real things, we can infer much about objects at greater distances than we could before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceProjection_Name</Label>
        <String>Subspace Projection</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceProjection_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Adds the most advanced sensors to our starbases.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceProjection_Dec</Label>
        <String>One limit of our existing sensor technology is how infuriatingly complicated it all is, requiring a great deal of processing power to make sense of any of it. A new breakthrough in visualization will allow users to simply project their sense of perception, allowing us to see far more clearly at the extremes our technology can reach.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumStreamTunneling_Name</Label>
        <String>Quantum Stream Tunneling</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumStreamTunneling_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reveal the most well-hidden anomalies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumStreamTunneling_Dec</Label>
        <String>The various quantum effects and entanglements our sensor technology relies on do not occur at random, but via distinct patterns we can now finally discern. Our latest sensors will use this breakthrough to effectively tunnel through reality at unimaginable speeds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedLifeSupport_Name</Label>
        <String>Improved Life Support</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedLifeSupport_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the range we can travel out into space.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedLifeSupport_Dec</Label>
        <String>There's little point to building ships to go places if we can't keep our people alive when they get there. These new life support systems will increase the operating range of our ships substantially.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FleetResupplyDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Fleet Resupply Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FleetResupplyDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the maximum size of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FleetResupplyDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>A fleet-based approach to resupply stops treating our space vessels as individuals, but as components of a single entity. This enables economies of scale which will improve our resupply efforts and extend the effective range of all our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarResupplyDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Resupply Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarResupplyDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the maximum size of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InterstellarResupplyDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Rather than the fixed boundaries we've been working with, the Interstellar Resupply Doctrine uses a more subtle and refined system of 'hand-offs' between different resupply hubs. This should lead to substantial improvements in fleet range.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IntermittentSuspension_Name</Label>
        <String>Intermittent Suspension</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IntermittentSuspension_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the maximum size of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IntermittentSuspension_Dec</Label>
        <String>A full cryogenic cycle is too slow to be of use for the crew of most ships. But this new system of Intermittent Suspension will allow ships to 'stow' their crews when not in use and spin them up only when needed. This should save on resources, and ultimately increase our fleets' range.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticResupplyDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Resupply Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticResupplyDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the maximum size of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GalacticResupplyDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>We no longer need to rely on static hubs for resupplying our vessels. Now we can make use of constantly moving resupply fleets of both piloted and semi-autonomous drones, always available where they're needed most.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalManufacturing_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Manufacturing</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalManufacturing_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks Orbital Factories for our planets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalManufacturing_Dec</Label>
        <String>Moving our manufacturing operations to micro-gravity environments will eventually allow for the construction of massive structures in space. We're not there yet, but this first step was always going to be the biggest.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalRepair_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Repair</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalRepair_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks Caretaker ships which can repair our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalRepair_Dec</Label>
        <String>No longer restricted to the combined action of independent crews, we now have entire facilities in orbit capable of manufacturing ships, with swarms of production crews producing vessels faster than ever before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalShipAssembly_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Ship Assembly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalShipAssembly_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for more effective starship construction.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalShipAssembly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Orbital Ship Assembly is an innovative technology that revolutionizes the way we construct and customize our starships. By moving the shipbuilding process into orbit, we can take advantage of the unique properties of the space environment, significantly increasing our production efficiency, and allowing us to integrate a greater variety of equipment and systems onto our vessels.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdvancedComposites_Name</Label>
        <String>Advanced Composites</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdvancedComposites_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the capabilities of our shipyards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdvancedComposites_Dec</Label>
        <String>This new family of materials, made possible by a breakthrough in materials science, will enable us to build stronger, tougher, and better looking vessels than ever before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LargeHullAssembly_Name</Label>
        <String>Large Hull Assembly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LargeHullAssembly_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks [HS=HS_HullSize]Large[/HS] hulled ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LargeHullAssembly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Making ships larger is more involved than just adding stuff to them. Ensuring that they don't collapse under acceleration is the real challenge, but it's an effort that does go appreciated by our crews.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalDeploymentMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Orbital Deployment Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalDeploymentMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the capabilities of our shipyards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrbitalDeploymentMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>For some time now, the main barrier to building larger ships was a matter of logistics, of getting all the necessary materials, people, and equipment into the right place at the right time. We're doing this better than ever, and our ships will grow ever larger for it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceFieldCreation_Name</Label>
        <String>Subspace Field Creation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceFieldCreation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increase the capabilities of our shipyards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SubspaceFieldCreation_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are limits to what even the strongest materials can withstand, but if we augment the structure of our ships with subspace fields, we can engineer craft almost unimaginably large.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MassiveHullConstruction_Name</Label>
        <String>Massive Hull Construction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MassiveHullConstruction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks [HS=HS_HullSize]Huge[/HS] hulled ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MassiveHullConstruction_Dec</Label>
        <String>We're now building ships capable of blotting out the stars. We haven't built one larger than a star yet, but at this point that seems like only a matter of time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WeakAI_Name</Label>
        <String>Artificial General Intelligence</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WeakAI_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to set a policy to free AI to do what it wants.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WeakAI_Dec</Label>
        <String>True artificial intelligence is difficult to achieve, being both loosely defined, and computationally expensive, no matter what definition is used. But this latest advancement, using pseudo-synaptic pattern recognition circuits, is a big step, and should greatly boost our research ability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DroneProduction_Name</Label>
        <String>Drone Production</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DroneProduction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to begin constructing Drones.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DroneProduction_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've used various forms of automation in our production processes since long before we reached the stars. But this latest advancement increases the amount of autonomy these devices can have, creating fleets of drones that will massively increase our production capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CollectorDrones_Name</Label>
        <String>Collector Drones</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CollectorDrones_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the production supplied by our Asteroid Miners.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CollectorDrones_Dec</Label>
        <String>Although our resource collection has long relied on remote tools, sentient operators have never been far from the controls. The latest advancement in autonomous collection drones should lead to a massive increase in our harvesting capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AsteroidFactories_Name</Label>
        <String>Asteroid Factories</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AsteroidFactories_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the production supplied by our Asteroid Miners.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AsteroidFactories_Dec</Label>
        <String>A surprising proportion of the resource collection process is simply dedicated to finding secure footholds for mining platforms to situate themselves. Fixed, semi-permanent factories on the surfaces of asteroids will enable resource collection on a whole new scale.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResourceExtractionDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Resource Extraction Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResourceExtractionDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our mining efforts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ResourceExtractionDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Resource Extraction Doctrine is a systematic approach to resource management on a galactic scale. Guided by a predictive intelligence which monitors our production needs and supply chains, we harvest resources more efficiently and effectively than ever before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LosslessMining_Name</Label>
        <String>Lossless Mining</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LosslessMining_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of targeted resource extractor modules.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_LosslessMining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our mastery of resource extraction at the macro level has now been matched at the subatomic level. No longer will resources be discarded for being difficult to extract. We have achieved a nearly perfect mining efficiency.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DurantiumExtractors_Name</Label>
        <String>Durantium Extractors</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DurantiumExtractors_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to mine more Durantium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DurantiumExtractors_Dec</Label>
        <String>The valuable metal Durantium has long been difficult to harvest cleanly from its natural ores. These new extractors, built specifically to match the exacting processes required, should improve our Durantium extracting efficiency greatly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PromethionExtraction_Name</Label>
        <String>Promethion Extraction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PromethionExtraction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to mine more Promethion.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PromethionExtraction_Dec</Label>
        <String>The rare mineral Promethion, now so valuable to our production, has long been collected almost by accident. A new type of extraction drone should substantially improve the odds of these happy accidents occurring.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMatterExtraction_Name</Label>
        <String>Antimatter Extraction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMatterExtraction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to mine more Antimatter.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMatterExtraction_Dec</Label>
        <String>Collecting antimatter is a highly specialized process which our standard collection drones are ill-equipped to handle. This new dedicated breed should prove far more effective, or at least not blow themselves up nearly as often.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ThuliumExtraction_Name</Label>
        <String>Thulium Extraction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ThuliumExtraction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to mine more Thulium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ThuliumExtraction_Dec</Label>
        <String>Thulium requires a precise combination of quantum effects to be separated from the minerals in which it's commonly found, which can only be done at great energy and cost. A new chain of effects has been discovered which should make this process far more efficient.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EleriumExtraction_Name</Label>
        <String>Elerium Extraction</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EleriumExtraction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to mine more Elerium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EleriumExtraction_Dec</Label>
        <String>Elerium is as elusive as it is powerful. Mining it isn't difficult: the hard part is trapping it before it dissipates. With these new techniques, we'll soon capture more than we could ever need.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SupplyDrones_Name</Label>
        <String>Supply Drones</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SupplyDrones_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to produce nanobots that can upgrade our colonies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SupplyDrones_Dec</Label>
        <String>These new drones, capable of navigating interstellar space autonomously, will provide our fleet resupply network with a new degree of flexibility and effectiveness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ConstructionDrones_Name</Label>
        <String>Construction Drones</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ConstructionDrones_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to upgrade our ships with repair drones that service the entire fleet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ConstructionDrones_Dec</Label>
        <String>Construction is one of the tasks best suited for drone-based automation, but the sheer scale of it has limited our use of the technology until now. These new construction drones should make a massive difference.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShipUpgradeDrones_Name</Label>
        <String>Ship Upgrade Drones</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShipUpgradeDrones_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new upgrades for our Ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShipUpgradeDrones_Dec</Label>
        <String>Working in and upgrading a completed vessel requires a degree of flexibility and precision which has generally been limited to skilled craftsmen. Until now. These new ship upgrade drones will easily allow us to keep our entire fleet equipped with our most cutting-edge technology.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UtilityClouds_Name</Label>
        <String>Utility Clouds</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UtilityClouds_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new upgrades for our Ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_UtilityClouds_Dec</Label>
        <String>A general-purpose drone is easier said than done. The sheer variety of activities we require of drones means the number of tools one would need to carry impractical. But by making drones reconfigurable - by other drones themselves - a cloud of drones can genuinely serve almost any purpose we can imagine.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepCoreMining_Name</Label>
        <String>Deep Core Mining</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepCoreMining_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us access to buried minerals and wealth, if we can handle the pollution generated.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepCoreMining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our planetary resource extraction has long been limited to the mere crust of the globes we inhabit. No longer. Deep core mining will enable us to extract resources at rates we have never seen before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MolecularPrinters_Name</Label>
        <String>Molecular Printers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MolecularPrinters_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new upgrades for our Ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MolecularPrinters_Dec</Label>
        <String>Recent advances in materials science have enabled the construction of space elevators, which will allow us to move material into space more easily, and from there, throughout our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicAnalytics_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Relic Analytics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicAnalytics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves relic benefits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicAnalytics_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've been finding relics left behind by an ancient race known as the Precursors for some time now, discoveries which have led to incredible breakthroughs in a variety of fields. A more focused effort to analyze these relics should tease out even more useful details.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoComputationalTheory_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeno Computational Theory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoComputationalTheory_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves global Research.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_XenoComputationalTheory_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our previous efforts to analyze Precursor artifacts have been limited by just how differently these beings thought. A new form of computer, tuned to emulate the strange patterns the Precursors used, should help increase our research effectiveness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicProficiency_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Relic Proficiency</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicProficiency_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves relic benefits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicProficiency_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've studied Precursor relics so long now that the discovery of a new one no longer introduces any great mystery. Test procedures, harnesses, and energy sources have all been refined to the point that the Precursors spill their secrets to us with incredible ease.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StrongAI_Name</Label>
        <String>Strong AI</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StrongAI_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to simulate our brightest minds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StrongAI_Dec</Label>
        <String>The latest breakthrough in AI has enabled our learning systems to form new pathways at a nearly geometric rate, leading to the first emergence of truly strong AI. The impact this will have on our research programs will be immense.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Relic Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves relic benefits.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecursorRelicMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>We now think about and perceive the universe at nearly the same level as the Precursors once did. Were they to meet us, they might very well consider us their peers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DriveOptimization_Name</Label>
        <String>Drive System Optimization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DriveOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Boosts the speed of all ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DriveOptimization_Dec</Label>
        <String>With a little persuasion, we have been able to convince many of our researchers to leave there cozy research centers, and do some practical studies onboard our ships. The result has been an impressive increase of our average ship speeds. Unfortunately, the researchers will need to return to their offices before too long, unless we continue to fund this endeavor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Name</Label>
        <String>Armed Shuttles</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of armed spacecraft.[BR][BR]Provides two free warships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Dec</Label>
        <String>Spaceships are fragile things, and it's no great feat destroying them. The real art is destroying the enemy before they do it to you first. New equipment will be required if we hope to come out on the right side of that calculation more often.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceWeapons_Name</Label>
        <String>Space Weapons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceWeapons_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provides access to some basic weapons for space combat.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceWeapons_Dec</Label>
        <String>In the grand cosmic scheme, our spacecraft, delicate as they are, could be likened to glass houses in a neighborhood fond of stone-throwing. Our approach to survival? Developing stones that are, metaphorically speaking, too swift for retaliation. Thus enters the exciting (if mildly concerning) world of space weaponry research. Our objective? Perfect the art of breaking glass without being home when the shards start flying. It's less about not throwing stones and more about ensuring ours are unforgettable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WeaponSystems_Name</Label>
        <String>Weapon Systems</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WeaponSystems_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows for better integration of our newly invented space weapons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_WeaponSystems_Dec</Label>
        <String>Tracking and targeting enemy ships pose significant challenges, given the astronomical speeds and vast distances involved - even at sublight speeds, vessels can move nearly as fast as light, often at distances spanning millions of kilometers.[BR][BR]To overcome these difficulties, we've developed sophisticated targeting computers. Although these systems are sizeable and require considerable space, they are crucial to bridge the gap between near misses and successful strikes. These advanced computers enhance the accuracy of our attacks, offering a significant advantage in crucial combat scenarios.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponTheory_Name</Label>
        <String>Directed Energy Weapons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponTheory_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of basic energy beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponTheory_Dec</Label>
        <String>Beam weapons will deliver our will upon enemies at the speed of light. But to make them feasible at ship scales we will require energy supplies, capacitors, collimation systems, and a variety of other related technologies. We will establish a dedicated field of research to begin tackling these challenges.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceLasers_Name</Label>
        <String>Photonic Alignment</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceLasers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceLasers_Dec</Label>
        <String>Photonic Alignment' heralds a new era in beam weapon technology, far surpassing simple scale. Harnessing the power of light itself, we delve into the fundamental core of energy projection, aligning photons in meticulous arrays of concentrated destruction. This isn't just firepower; it's an exercise in quantum finesse, translating into significantly amplified damage output.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ForgedBeamWeapons_Name</Label>
        <String>Forged Beam Weapons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ForgedBeamWeapons_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ForgedBeamWeapons_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've discovered a new and more precise way to manufacture the focusing crystals used in beam systems.. These forged systems should prove far more potent than previous models.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponMiniturization_Name</Label>
        <String>Beam Weapon Miniaturization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponMiniturization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reduces the size of our beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponMiniturization_Dec</Label>
        <String>Thanks to breakthroughs in capacitor design, we can now create beam systems in a far smaller form factor than ever before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponAugmentation_Name</Label>
        <String>Beam Weapon Augmentation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamWeaponAugmentation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Using feedback loops, we can now synchronize the waves of energy we supply to a beam system, delivering far more powerful beams. This augmentation system should make all our beam weapons more potent.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DisruptorBeams_Name</Label>
        <String>Disruptor Beams</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DisruptorBeams_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks a new, more lethal, beam weapon component for our ship designs</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DisruptorBeams_Dec</Label>
        <String>Disruptor systems rely on the sudden delivery of a specific combination of subatomic particles, which - when delivered at a high enough energy - disrupt the electromagnetic forces holding matter together. Nasty stuff. Let's be careful who we point these at.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighEnergyTransfer_Name</Label>
        <String>High Energy Transfer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighEnergyTransfer_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighEnergyTransfer_Dec</Label>
        <String>Rapidly directing energy from our generating systems to our weapons is one of the primary bottlenecks in our beam weapon systems. A new form of superconductor should enable far greater energy velocities than we've seen before.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamIntegrityEnhancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Beam Weapon Enhancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamIntegrityEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamIntegrityEnhancement_Dec</Label>
        <String>Even the smallest of vibrations can disrupt the focusing of a beam weapon, thus reducing damage output. We can correct this inefficiency with improved dampening systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlasmaBeams_Name</Label>
        <String>Plasma Beams</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlasmaBeams_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks Plasma based beam weapon components for our ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlasmaBeams_Dec</Label>
        <String>A new breakthrough has allowed us to accelerate small particles at incredible speeds. The sheer weight of these particles, to say nothing of their enormous temperature, should ensure anyone on the receiving end will have a very bad day.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighEnergyPlasmas_Name</Label>
        <String>High Energy Plasmas</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighEnergyPlasmas_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HighEnergyPlasmas_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's taken a couple generations of our plasma systems to work out the kinks, but now all of our battlefield research has paid off. We've just received delivery of these new, higher energy plasma weapon systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamCapacitation_Name</Label>
        <String>Beam Capacitation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamCapacitation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BeamCapacitation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Why have we spent so much time trying to store energy for beam weapons in our dimension, when there are entire other planes nearby? By using their capacity for energy storage, tapped at the right time, we can deliver vastly greater attacks upon our foes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhasorBeams_Name</Label>
        <String>Phasor Beams</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhasorBeams_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes Phasor based beam weapons available for our ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhasorBeams_Dec</Label>
        <String>Much as we can now store energy for our weapons systems in neighboring realities, we could potentially send back parts of our enemies to those realities as well. Not all their parts in one place, though. If possible, we should scatter them among a handful of dimensions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhasedEnergyMagnification_Name</Label>
        <String>Phased Energy Magnification</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhasedEnergyMagnification_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhasedEnergyMagnification_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to deliver the energy densities we really want, we need to start building our phasor systems across neighboring dimensions. This way, we should be able to corral a much greater number of particles, including those that don't entirely fit in the one reality.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DoomRay_Name</Label>
        <String>Doom Ray</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DoomRay_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes the Doom Ray available. It is exactly what it sounds like.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DoomRay_Dec</Label>
        <String>A 'polyphasic decoherence effect generator,' while perhaps a more accurate name, does not have the same emotional weight as 'Doom Ray.' We think our enemies will appreciate the difference.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ThermalBlooming_Name</Label>
        <String>Thermal Blooming</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ThermalBlooming_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Beam weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ThermalBlooming_Dec</Label>
        <String>Now that our beam weapons spend so much of their time in neighboring dimensions, it should be no surprise they're encountering a great deal more of the thermal blooming we observe when they're fired in our own atmosphere. But now, thanks to science, we can control this effect, and channel the energy lost back into the main flow.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Railguns_Name</Label>
        <String>Railguns</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Railguns_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of basic Kinetic weapon.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Railguns_Dec</Label>
        <String>Railguns use arrays of magnets to accelerate projectiles at terrifying velocities, all without any of the hassle or inherent danger of handling explosive propellants.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponEnhancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Kinetic Weapon Enhancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponEnhancement_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our material scientists have devised a new alloy with far greater potential for use in electromagnets. When installed in our kinetic weapon systems, it should lead to a very noticeable increase in other things exploding downrange from our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponTargeting_Name</Label>
        <String>Kinetic Weapon Targeting</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponTargeting_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponTargeting_Dec</Label>
        <String>Kinetic weapons travel quickly, but not instantly. Improved targeting systems should help ensure they deliver their destructive energy to the places it will do the most... not good</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticDischargeMiniaturization_Name</Label>
        <String>Kinetic Discharge Miniaturization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticDischargeMiniaturization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reduces the size of our kinetic weapon systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticDischargeMiniaturization_Dec</Label>
        <String>Smaller isn't always better, but miniature is always cooler. By making use of interference effects within our better-winded kinetic weapon coils, we're now able to deliver the same amount of magnetic thrust to our far smaller projectiles, and thus make big things go bang much more efficiently.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticAugmentation_Name</Label>
        <String>Kinetic Augmentation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticAugmentation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Improved reload and recharge mechanisms will allow our weapon systems to fire more projectiles in a shorter time span, increasing damage per second (DPS) and general misery among our foes (GMAOF).</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PulseCannons_Name</Label>
        <String>Pulse Cannons</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PulseCannons_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes Pulse Cannon system available for ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PulseCannons_Dec</Label>
        <String>There's little difference between a projectile, or the same mass of particles, walloping at high velocity into the side of an enemy ship. But now, due to some newly discovered quantum effects, we are capable of launching clouds of particles with far greater ease, and consequently, at much higher volume.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperFieldMassDrivers_Name</Label>
        <String>Hyper Field Mass Drivers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperFieldMassDrivers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_HyperFieldMassDrivers_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've finally found a way to use the same principles behind our hyperdrives to accelerate projectiles. Using elongated hyper fields,  our projectiles can travel in compressed space and reach incredible velocities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedKineticWeaponDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Improved Kinetic Weapon Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedKineticWeaponDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedKineticWeaponDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Kinetic weapons require more than just equipment,they require a whole new way of practicing warfare. Everything from the tactics, targeting, and ship maneuvers needs to be adjusted to suit this new means of destruction.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GravitonGuns_Name</Label>
        <String>Graviton Guns</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GravitonGuns_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes the Graviton kinetic weapon system available for ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GravitonGuns_Dec</Label>
        <String>Gravitons don't interact with our conventional kinetic pulse cannons. It took parallel breakthroughs in particle science and cosmology to devise a mechanism for even manipulating them. But that done, we can fire charges at our enemies that will literally tear them apart from the inside.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticMassWeaponry_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic Mass Weaponry</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticMassWeaponry_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticMassWeaponry_Dec</Label>
        <String>Kinetic weapons don't take easily to explosive projectiles. It's taken a new form of exotic material to make a breakthrough, delivering projectiles with their latent explosive energy 'baked' in.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InertiaEnhancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Inertia Enhancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InertiaEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InertiaEnhancement_Dec</Label>
        <String>A new form of projectile, one which keeps much of its mass in a neighboring dimension, will allow us to fire relatively light rounds at incredible speeds. They'll only bring their full mass to bear on impact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumPulseDriver_Name</Label>
        <String>Quantum Pulse Driver</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumPulseDriver_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes the Quantum Driver kinetic weapon system available for our ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumPulseDriver_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our latest form of kinetic weapon uses specially entangled quantum particles, which upon impact, 'swap' small parts of our target among themselves. In short, they cause utter chaos at a molecular level, which no armor can hope to withstand.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Kinetic Weapon Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_KineticWeaponMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our advances in this field are not a single breakthrough, but a reflection of the amount of effort we've invested in kinetic weapon systems. We have mastered the targeting, tactics, manufacturing, operations, and charging systems needed to make first class kinetic weapons, having wrung efficiencies out of every possible system.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BlackholeGun_Name</Label>
        <String>Blackhole Gun</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BlackholeGun_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes the Singularity driver available for our ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_BlackholeGun_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Blackhole Gun is not a misnomer nor colorful exaggeration. It's a gun which fires blackholes. The blackholes are very small, to be fair - we're not reckless. But they are real, and if we don't like you, they are coming your way.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MassManipulation_Name</Label>
        <String>Mass Manipulation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MassManipulation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Kinetic weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MassManipulation_Dec</Label>
        <String>A breakthrough in particle sciences has enabled us to fire particles which are technically massless, at least until a quantum chain reaction decays to a certain point. By mixing these particles with conventional matter, we can fire practically wafer-thin projectiles which become far heavier on the way to their target.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AvengerMissileSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Avenger Missile System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AvengerMissileSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows construction of basic Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AvengerMissileSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>Missile systems enable on-the-fly targeting adjustments, rendering most forms of evasive maneuver pointless. This new Avenger system will show how dangerous and flexible missile warfare can be.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileTargeting_Name</Label>
        <String>Improved Missile Targeting</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileTargeting_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileTargeting_Dec</Label>
        <String>The whole point of missiles is their ability to adjust their course, hitting their targets no matter where. And yet they miss so disappointingly often. We should dedicate more resources to improving their targeting systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissilePayloadOptimization_Name</Label>
        <String>Missile Payload Optimization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissilePayloadOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissilePayloadOptimization_Dec</Label>
        <String>Shaped explosives are not new technology to us, but it will take some experimentation to figure out the best way to apply this technique to best destroy spaceships. Poorly designed, they'll waste much of their energy out the rear of their targets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileWarfareDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Improved Missile Warfare Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileWarfareDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileWarfareDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are distinct maneuvers and tactics unique to missile warfare on which we need to train our ship commanders. Range management and flocking behavior alone could fill textbooks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PayloadMiniaturization_Name</Label>
        <String>Payload Miniaturization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PayloadMiniaturization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Reduces the amount of space our missile weapon systems use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PayloadMiniaturization_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's a simple calculation. If we can deliver the same amount of destructive potential in a smaller missile, we can carry more of them. Or other equipment, we suppose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DevastatorMissileSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Phoenix Missile System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DevastatorMissileSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DevastatorMissileSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Devastator missile system uses a new form of micro-fusion warhead which will enable us to increase both the destructive power of our own ships, and general enemy unhappiness, by vast amounts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptiveMissileSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Adaptive Missile System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptiveMissileSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptiveMissileSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Adaptive Missile System uses targeting information from peer missiles to inform decision making both by the current flock and later salvos. They're always learning.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileProduction_Name</Label>
        <String>Improved Missile Production</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileProduction_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedMissileProduction_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our missile systems work best when fired in volume. Anything we can do on the supply side to make missiles cheaper will ensure that volume is present at the moment of truth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhotonicWarheadSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Photonic Warhead System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhotonicWarheadSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes available the Photonic Missile system for our ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhotonicWarheadSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>Photonic Warheads release terrifically high energy photons on impact, far beyond what is released by mere fusion reactions. Our scientists are a little shaky on the details, but that hasn't stopped them turning it into a weapon.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntimatterDetonation_Name</Label>
        <String>Antimatter Detonation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntimatterDetonation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntimatterDetonation_Dec</Label>
        <String>By embedding true AI in our missile systems, our missiles will be more adaptable far more successful at evading enemy countermeasures.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdvancedMissileDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Advanced Missile Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdvancedMissileDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdvancedMissileDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Every missile fired has an envelope in which it can effectively strike its target. The overlap of these envelopes, and the effect they have on enemy maneuvers, is a fantastically complicated problem, but if we master it we may be able to coax our enemy to literally fly into our missiles for us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumTorpedoSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Quantum Torpedo System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumTorpedoSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes the enw Quantum Torpedo Missile system available for ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_QuantumTorpedoSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>The effects a quantum torpedo has upon impact are, by definition, a bit unpredictable. Parts of the enemy ship don't exist any more, or at least exist in a pretty bad place.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissileWarfareMastery_Name</Label>
        <String>Missile Warfare Mastery</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissileWarfareMastery_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissileWarfareMastery_Dec</Label>
        <String>We have done it! We've wrung every efficiency possible out of our missile systems, tuned these weapons to the very limit of their potential. Our ships can fill entire systems with missiles, raining destruction on anyone they choose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NightmareMissileSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Nightmare Missile System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NightmareMissileSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes a very lethal new missile weapon system available for our ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NightmareMissileSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Nightmare Missile uses a pair of rapidly orbiting singularities, stable in storage and flight, but abruptly less so on impact. The effect two unbalanced singularities can have on an enemy ships is grave indeed. Also, we usually fire more than one of these missiles at a time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CascadingDetonations_Name</Label>
        <String>Cascading Detonations</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CascadingDetonations_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the power of our Missile weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CascadingDetonations_Dec</Label>
        <String>Cascading warheads don't just explode, they induce small fusion reactions in the enemy armor itself, causing chain reactions for several very exciting seconds after impact.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DefensiveStudies_Name</Label>
        <String>Defensive Studies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DefensiveStudies_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to begin building advanced systems into our most vulnerable targets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DefensiveStudies_Dec</Label>
        <String>Spaceships are fragile things, with little hope standing up to even the current level of weapons technology. We should devise new systems which will give our ships a fighting chance of surviving encounters with hostile forces.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EvasiveTactics_Name</Label>
        <String>Evasive Tactics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EvasiveTactics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks Weapon Jammers which can increase the evasion of our ships</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EvasiveTactics_Dec</Label>
        <String> This revolutionary technology introduces advanced jamming techniques that make it more challenging for enemy systems to lock on. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorDefenseTheory_Name</Label>
        <String>Armor Defense Theory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorDefenseTheory_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advanced Armor will help mitigate damage from attacks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorDefenseTheory_Dec</Label>
        <String>Armor is the most conceptually straightforward of defensive systems, but in that simplicity lie many intricacies we will need to master. We can't simply strap weight onto to our ships without compromising their effectiveness. A more subtle solution is needed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedArmorScience_Name</Label>
        <String>Improved Armor Science</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedArmorScience_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ImprovedArmorScience_Dec</Label>
        <String>By dedicating resources to material sciences and fabrication, we should be able to build denser, more resilient armor systems, and consequently, denser, more resilient spaceships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorMaterialScience_Name</Label>
        <String>Armor Material Science</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorMaterialScience_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorMaterialScience_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our scientists in other fields - particularly particle physics and planetology - regularly devise or stumble upon new materials that have potential as armoring substances. We should establish information sharing regimes so that their breakthroughs become ours.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DiamonicArmorComposite_Name</Label>
        <String>Diamonic Armor Composite</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DiamonicArmorComposite_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DiamonicArmorComposite_Dec</Label>
        <String>Diamond, while very hard, is horrifically expensive, and prone to fracturing. By establishing layered composites of diamond and conventional armor plating, we can produce a material that's both extraordinarily resilient, and feasible to manufacture in volume.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SelfHealingArmor_Name</Label>
        <String>Self-Healing Armor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SelfHealingArmor_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SelfHealingArmor_Dec</Label>
        <String>During an impact, the physical material of armor doesn't go anywhere; it's just distorted into a shape that makes it far less effective. By using a new breed of fusible alloys within our plating, we can cause these holes and tears to restore themselves using the latent heat energy of the impact itself.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorDensityImprovements_Name</Label>
        <String>Armor Density Improvements</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorDensityImprovements_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmorDensityImprovements_Dec</Label>
        <String>To date, the density of a material has always been intrinsic to its structure, a fact of the universe previously unchangeable by us. But thanks to the discovery of a new scientific field which is capable of reducing intra-atomic distances, all of our materials can be made denser, and thus hardier. We're literally improving the universe here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrganicArmor_Name</Label>
        <String>Organic Armor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrganicArmor_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_OrganicArmor_Dec</Label>
        <String>Carbon-based molecules can be extraordinarily hard - diamond, for instance. But until now, these crystalline structures only formed under intense pressures. A newly discovered form of chemistry arranges carbon molecules in unusually dense formations, and can produce amazingly durable plating with incredible self-healing properties.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptiveArmorImprovements_Name</Label>
        <String>Adaptive Armor Improvements</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptiveArmorImprovements_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AdaptiveArmorImprovements_Dec</Label>
        <String>Projectiles aren't invisible - our sensors can easily see what's about to strike us. By channeling hardening fields into the areas where impacts are anticipated, we can make our armor more effectively resilient for almost no cost at all.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticArmorMaterials_Name</Label>
        <String>Exotic Armor Materials</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticArmorMaterials_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExoticArmorMaterials_Dec</Label>
        <String>Most materials we work with are of this universe, which is fine... just a bit boring. But there are conceivable universes where various physical constants are more conducive to armoring. More tightly packed molecules, that sort of thing. If we 'borrow' these materials for our needs, surely no-one in those other universes will mind.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NullPointArmor_Name</Label>
        <String>Null Point Armor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NullPointArmor_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_NullPointArmor_Dec</Label>
        <String>By covering our armor in a layer of tightly contained artificial singularities, we can ensure any incoming projectiles are annihilated before they touch us. The handling of such materials is a little tricky, and we'll have to take care not to bump into anything, but this should all be doable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TemperedArmor_Name</Label>
        <String>Tempered Armor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TemperedArmor_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in materials technology will provide us with lighter and stronger Armor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TemperedArmor_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's long been observed by those who repair ships that armor panels which have already taken impact are significantly harder than their undamaged neighbors. If we can artificially induce this same effect, we should be able to create far sturdier vessels.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyDeflectionTheory_Name</Label>
        <String>Energy Deflection Theory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyDeflectionTheory_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Basic shields will allow our ships to absorb incoming damage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyDeflectionTheory_Dec</Label>
        <String>Directed energy beams are a potent new weapon our enemies often wield. Counteracting them will involve a new field of science using equal or greater amounts of energy arranged in defensive fields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyDissipationStrategies_Name</Label>
        <String>Energy Dissipation Strategies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyDissipationStrategies_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>By deflecting the incoming energy, our Shields have less to resist,</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyDissipationStrategies_Dec</Label>
        <String>The energy our shields absorb doesn't disappear - that's impossible, at least in this universe. It has to be vented somehow, and we will need to research new technologies to do it without getting harmed in the process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyShields_Name</Label>
        <String>Energy Shields</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyShields_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_EnergyShields_Dec</Label>
        <String>While earlier models deflected incoming energy with precisely timed counterblasts, our latest deflector systems are capable of projecting entire shields around our vessels, forming the classic ship-in-a-bubble effect we long envisioned.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldEnhancements_Name</Label>
        <String>Shield Enhancements</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldEnhancements_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldEnhancements_Dec</Label>
        <String>By increasing the number of shield emitters we install on our ships, we can ensure no single sector is overwhelmed by incoming energy, allowing networks of shield emitters to support one another.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldRegeneration_Name</Label>
        <String>Shield Regeneration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldRegeneration_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldRegeneration_Dec</Label>
        <String>The primary reason shields 'wear out' is due to energy dissipation. By dramatically increasing our dissipation networks - up to and including temporarily storing incoming energy to funnel back into our shields - we can ensure that our shields recharge faster than ever.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldAugmentation_Name</Label>
        <String>Shield Augmentation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldAugmentation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Shields to date have always been in a single layer, due to limitations in our ability to project through our own shields. But by preparing a temporary new shield ready to deploy in the space behind a shield about to fail, we can effectively defend in depth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GravimetricShields_Name</Label>
        <String>Gravimetric Shields</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GravimetricShields_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GravimetricShields_Dec</Label>
        <String>Light can be bent by gravity; this has been understood for centuries. But it's taken some time for us to be able to artificially generate gravity - albeit in a very localized way - enough to diffuse and deflect incoming energy attacks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldFrequencyModulation_Name</Label>
        <String>Shield Frequency Modulation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldFrequencyModulation_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldFrequencyModulation_Dec</Label>
        <String>Although it sounds like something someone just made up on the spot, Shield Frequency Modulation uses the very real science of frequencies to modulate our shields in a way which makes them more effective. Very complicated stuff.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldFocusAdaption_Name</Label>
        <String>Shield Focus Adaption</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldFocusAdaption_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldFocusAdaption_Dec</Label>
        <String>A shocking amount of the energy output of our shields goes to waste, directed entire arc-minutes off-axis from incoming strikes. By better tuning our shield emitters to more precisely focus on the incoming energy, we can produce stronger, more effective shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InvulnerabilityShields_Name</Label>
        <String>Invulnerability Shields</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InvulnerabilityShields_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_InvulnerabilityShields_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Invulnerability Shield system channels nearly supernova-levels of energy outwards from our ship, annihilating all but the most ferocious strikes directed our way. Perhaps it's not truly invulnerable, but there are few out there who can test the difference.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldHarmonics_Name</Label>
        <String>Shield Harmonics</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldHarmonics_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in energy technology will provide us with stronger shields.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ShieldHarmonics_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our shields can take advantage of  the interference effects generated when two waves collide. By using very precise sensors to measure incoming energy and rapidly adapting our shield emitters, our shields should prove hardier at almost no additional cost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissileCountermeasures_Name</Label>
        <String>Missile Countermeasures</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissileCountermeasures_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MissileCountermeasures_Dec</Label>
        <String>Missiles can contain enough explosive energy and shrapnel to shred our ships. The best countermeasure is to destroy them before they reach our ships. We should research countermeasure systems which can do just that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileGuidanceSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Anti-Missile Guidance System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileGuidanceSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileGuidanceSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>Missiles are fragile things themselves, and can be easily destroyed if they pass through a small cloud of shrapnel. Anti-missile systems, which track and destroy these incoming attacks, will be a great asset for our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PointDefenseSystem_Name</Label>
        <String>Point Defense System</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PointDefenseSystem_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PointDefenseSystem_Dec</Label>
        <String>Forget our earlier generations of interceptor missiles. Miniature railguns with independent tracking systems can serve as vastly more protective point defense systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileClusters_Name</Label>
        <String>Anti-Missile Clusters</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileClusters_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileClusters_Dec</Label>
        <String>By using cluster munitions in our missile countermeasure systems, the defensive rounds they fire will be capable of filling far more space with defensive shrapnel.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CountermeasureEfficiency_Name</Label>
        <String>Countermeasure Efficiency</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CountermeasureEfficiency_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CountermeasureEfficiency_Dec</Label>
        <String>If our countermeasure rounds coordinated their behavior with one another - not all picking the same target for instance - they could prove far more effective. We'll need to rewrite our defensive guidance systems, but this should be within our reach.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PointDefenseArrays_Name</Label>
        <String>Point Defense Arrays</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PointDefenseArrays_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PointDefenseArrays_Dec</Label>
        <String>By siting our point defense cannons in coordinated batteries, we can ensure they manage their fields of fire far more effectively, and fill a far greater volume of space with defensive fire.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AIGuidedPointDefense_Name</Label>
        <String>AI Guided Point Defense</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AIGuidedPointDefense_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AIGuidedPointDefense_Dec</Label>
        <String>By installing specialized AI systems on our batteries of point defence systems, we can ensure they target incoming missiles with perfect efficiency.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileDroneSentries_Name</Label>
        <String>Anti-Missile Drone Sentries</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileDroneSentries_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AntiMissileDroneSentries_Dec</Label>
        <String>The greater the distance from which we can engage incoming missiles, the longer we'll last. Drone sentries, operating at variable distances from our ships' hulls, can carry all the point defense fire power of our regular systems and thus provide defense in depth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhantomTargetEnhancement_Name</Label>
        <String>Phantom Target Enhancement</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhantomTargetEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PhantomTargetEnhancement_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our enemies are no fools - otherwise they wouldn't be worthy of the title. Their incoming missiles have developed very advanced counter-countermeasures, casting sensor phantoms to trick our systems. We'll need a new sensor system to keep on the safe side of this technological curve.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AeronMissileDefense_Name</Label>
        <String>Aeron Missile Defense</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AeronMissileDefense_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_AeronMissileDefense_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Aeron Missile Defense system fires defensive missiles in wildly unpredictable paths, confusing incoming missiles' defensive maneuvers. Despite the seemingly random initial bursts, Aerons inexorably home in on their targets, filling the sky with pretty explosions, distant enough from our ships to enjoy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecisionCountermeasures_Name</Label>
        <String>Precision Countermeasures</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecisionCountermeasures_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Advancements in targeting technology will improve our protection from missiles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PrecisionCountermeasures_Dec</Label>
        <String>Far too much of our countermeasure effort goes to waste. Improved targeting systems, sensors, and interceptor velocity should ensure we waste as little of our defensive firepower as possible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Space Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks Frigate class ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SpaceDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Space isn't just big, it's dangerous. This is doubly true if there are aliens trying to destroy our ships. Space Doctrine sets up a department in our government designed to organize both public and private industry to work together, to ensure our civilization's survival.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CruiserDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Battle Cruiser Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CruiserDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to build and design Cruiser class starships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CruiserDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Battle Cruiser Doctrine is a crucial technology that enables the construction of highly advanced and powerful battle cruisers for our fleet. These formidable warships are designed to strike fear into the hearts of our enemies, and secure our civilization's place among the stars.[BR][BR]The Battle Cruiser Doctrine establishes a specialized division within our government and military infrastructure, devoted to the development, deployment and maintenance of these awe-inspiring vessels. By coordinating the efforts of public institutions, private contractors, and military strategists, the doctrine ensures the seamless integration of cutting-edge technology, superior firepower, and tactical expertise into the design of our battle cruisers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FlexibleBulkheads_Name</Label>
        <String>Flexible Bulkheads</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FlexibleBulkheads_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to fit more components on ship designs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_FlexibleBulkheads_Dec</Label>
        <String>If we could move our bulkheads when needed, we could better maximize our space.  With Flexible Bulkheads, the internals of our ships would be much easier to adapt for maximum storage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExtremeMiniaturization_Name</Label>
        <String>Extreme Miniaturization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExtremeMiniaturization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Adds additional component slots on hulls based on its total mass.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ExtremeMiniaturization_Dec</Label>
        <String>This poorly named set of techniques, doctrines, policies and  technologies is more of a policy of organizing what goes on a given ship, so that we can fit much more. Contrary to what some have argued, we are not actually shrinking things inside our ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Battleships_Name</Label>
        <String>Battleship Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Battleships_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to design and build Battleship class starships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Battleships_Dec</Label>
        <String>Battleship Doctrine is an essential technology that unlocks the ability to design, construct, and deploy the awe-inspiring battleships that will serve as the ultimate guardians of our civilization. These massive vessels are built to withstand the most intense conflicts, dominating the battlefield with their overwhelming firepower and unrivaled resilience.[BR][BR]The Battleship Doctrine initiates the formation of a specialized branch within our government and military, focusing exclusively on harnessing the full potential of these warships. This branch will work closely with scientific institutions, engineering firms, and military tacticians to ensure that our battleships are equipped with the most advanced weaponry, impenetrable armor, and cutting-edge support systems available.[BR][BR]As this technology is researched, our civilization will gain access to a new class of space-faring juggernauts that will redefine the concept of naval superiority. Unlike the more agile and versatile battle cruisers, battleships serve as the indestructible bulwark of our fleet, designed to engage and obliterate the toughest adversaries in large-scale confrontations. With the Battleship Doctrine in place, our civilization's presence in the galaxy will be reinforced by these monumental symbols of might, ensuring our sovereignty and safety in an ever-changing and unpredictable universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DreadnoughtDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Dreadnought Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DreadnoughtDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to design and build Dreadnought class starships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DreadnoughtDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Dreadnought Doctrine is a groundbreaking technology that allows our civilization to design, build, and deploy the most awe-inspiring and fearsome class of starships: the Dreadnoughts. These gargantuan vessels represent the pinnacle of our military prowess, combining unparalleled firepower, unmatched durability, and the most advanced technology to assert our dominance across the cosmos.[BR][BR]The Dreadnought Doctrine calls for the creation of an elite division within our government and military, dedicated to the mastery of these extraordinary war machines. This division will collaborate with top scientific minds, cutting-edge engineering companies, and visionary military strategists to ensure our Dreadnoughts are outfitted with the most powerful weapons, the sturdiest armor, and the most sophisticated support systems known to our civilization.[BR][BR]With this knowledge in hand, our civilization will have access to these monumental starships, which will redefine the very essence of space warfare. Dreadnoughts are the ultimate expression of our civilization's strength and determination, dwarfing all other ship classes with their staggering size, unyielding resilience, and unparalleled destructive capabilities. They are designed to spearhead our fleet, leading the charge into battle and striking fear into the hearts of our adversaries.[BR][BR]With the Dreadnought Doctrine in place, our civilization will be able to command the most formidable force the galaxy has ever seen, ensuring our supremacy and safeguarding our people's future in a vast and uncertain universe.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryMobilization_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Mobilization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryMobilization_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to put our citizens to greater use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryMobilization_Dec</Label>
        <String>It won't take much to motivate our civilians to defend themselves. But it will take organizational ability, tactics, and of course equipment. Rifles and boots by the million, to start.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CentralizedAdministration_Name</Label>
        <String>Centralized Administration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CentralizedAdministration_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>New tools will allow us to control aspects of our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CentralizedAdministration_Dec</Label>
        <String>By centralizing our command structure for planetary defense, we can ensure our volunteer soldiers are put to the best use where they're needed most.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryInvasion_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Invasion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryInvasion_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows the construction of Invasion Transports which are virtal for invading core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryInvasion_Dec</Label>
        <String>Invading another planet is a complicated business, requiring well-trained troops, dedicated equipment, and no small amount of good fortune. We should focus our efforts toward achieving as much of this as possible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarMarines_Name</Label>
        <String>Stellar Marines</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarMarines_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to invade worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarMarines_Dec</Label>
        <String>Everything is more difficult on the surface of an unfamiliar world, and that includes avoiding being shot. We should establish a dedicated branch of the military that specializes in the dangerous art of planetary invasions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DroneSoldiers_Name</Label>
        <String>Drone Soldiers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DroneSoldiers_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to invade worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DroneSoldiers_Dec</Label>
        <String>Drone soldiers know no fear, coordinate perfectly across massive theaters, and can be deployed using tactics that don't require any particular regard for their safety. They lack the personal touch, but that's a small detail we can probably work on.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Killbots_Name</Label>
        <String>Killbots</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Killbots_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to invade worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Killbots_Dec</Label>
        <String>While our initial attempts at drone soldiers were effective, they lacked a certain charm. Not so with our latest model, the Killbots, which along with being more effective in all the usual ways, are far more charming and personable. We're told our enemies take great pleasure in getting murdered by them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryDefenses_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Defenses</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryDefenses_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to defend our worlds against invasions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlanetaryDefenses_Dec</Label>
        <String>If we can better anchor our planetary defenses, it will make our worlds far tougher to invade. This will provide improved defensive firepower, and allow greater coordination and structure for the rest of our defensive systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Redoubts_Name</Label>
        <String>Redoubts</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Redoubts_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Improves our ability to defend our worlds against invasions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_Redoubts_Dec</Label>
        <String>While the precise design of the redoubt will be informed by the terrain around it, its function will always be the same: an impossibly tough defensive structure, with carefully arranged layers of defenses. Few invading forces will be capable of capturing one, and none will enjoy trying.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SystemsOfControl_Name</Label>
        <String>Systems Of Control</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SystemsOfControl_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>New tools will allow us to control our aspects of our civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SystemsOfControl_Dec</Label>
        <String>We can hardly control the galaxy if we can't control our own people. Intertwined sets of laws, monitoring systems, and enforcement practices will ensure our people are all behaving properly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CentralAuthorityOffices_Name</Label>
        <String>Central Authority Offices</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CentralAuthorityOffices_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to manage the transportation of goods to and from our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CentralAuthorityOffices_Dec</Label>
        <String>We should be careful not to disperse the power to monitor our people too broadly, lest we lose control over it. Centralized offices can have the equipment and personal necessary to project authority in a place where we can keep an eye on those who exercise it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SecretPolice_Name</Label>
        <String>Secret Police</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SecretPolice_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Our populace may hate these tactics, but criminals hate them even more.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_SecretPolice_Dec</Label>
        <String>Some problems need to disappear quietly, so we shall create a new institution for doing that. Even its mere existence should have a positive effect, reminding those who might cause problems not to get too far out of line.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MartialLawDoctrine_Name</Label>
        <String>Martial Law Doctrine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MartialLawDoctrine_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks new policies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_MartialLawDoctrine_Dec</Label>
        <String>There's always the risk of pushback on some of our more vigorous monitoring and control techniques. While to date our police forces have been able to deal with this, we should be prepared to issue a stronger response if we need to. The temporary removal of rights will make our people realize just how generous we normally are.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlagueCure_Name</Label>
        <String>Synthetic Antibodies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlagueCure_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Enables exotic cures to artificially created plagues that have no known origin.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_PlagueCure_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our ability to combat that which seeks to kill us from within has increased over the centuries. Now we have the ability to make AI our ally in the fight against unseen diseases, as they now help our immune systems generate novel antibodies to fight infections.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TerrorStars_Name</Label>
        <String>Terror Stars</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TerrorStars_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Allows us to construct Terror Stars. Time for some cosmic horror.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_TerrorStars_Dec</Label>
        <String>A superweapon of unparalleled might. Firing it at a star summons the wrath of a supernova, obliterating all that resides within the fragile embrace of a solar system. It leaves naught but the echoes of a once vibrant existence.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_Name</Label>
        <String>Coordinated Travel</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes traveling in our area of influence cost essentially nothing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the advancement of Coordinated Travel, our fleets and convoys can move in perfect harmony. This technology uses advanced algorithms and real-time data streams to ensure our fleets can move through friendly space at speeds previously thought impossible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_Name</Label>
        <String>Glorious Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provides ultimate understanding of the Precursors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our pursuit for immortality is not limited to individuals but extends to our civilization's achievements and wisdom. The Glorious Legacy technology establishes advanced archiving, conservation, and broadcast methods to ensure our culture, discoveries, and stories resonate through the cosmos, forever untouched by time's decay.[BR][BR]This manifests in the non-trivial fact that we have had to reconcile our own beliefs and faiths with the fact that we know, for a fact there there was a Precursor civilization that was created by a set of beings called the Mithrilar.  These beings split into the Arnor and Dread Lords who fought each other before most species in this galaxy even evolved.  This perfect understanding allows us to intuitively use their works as if they were our own.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_Name</Label>
        <String>Call of Utopia</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks an executive order that massively increases influence on the target world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_Dec</Label>
        <String>Through the Call of Utopia, our civilization embarks on a journey to actualize a society where harmony, prosperity, and happiness reign supreme. Advanced sociological models, infrastructure blueprints, and community engagement strategies lay the groundwork for turning our utopian dream into a tangible reality. [BR][BR]This culminates through an executive order that, when used, drastically increases the influence of its target core world which will, if not immediately, in short order bring other civilizations into our light.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tech_Sanctuary_Name</Label>
        <String>Consensus Maker</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterSanctuaryTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Our diplomatic skills will increase every month.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterSanctuaryTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>To know us will be to love us. The Sanctuary technology focuses on building zones of unparalleled safety, both in terms of defense and societal well-being. Through advanced shielding, rapid-response systems, and a culture of care, these sanctuaries ensure that in times of crisis, our people have an unwavering beacon to turn to.[BR][BR]Every month our diplomatic ability will increase until every civilization cannot help but love us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IndividualDivinity_Name</Label>
        <String>Individual Divinity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ndividualDivinity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Empowering citizens to ascend to godhood.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IndividualDivinity_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our citizens stats will increase by 0.1 per month forever. Unlocking the latent potential within every individual, the Individual Divinity technology sets our citizens on a path of continuous evolution and self-improvement. Through spiritual, mental, and physical enhancement protocols, our people grow stronger, wiser, and more attuned to the cosmos each passing day, edging ever closer to a state of divine existence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    

</StringTableList>