<StringTableList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    
    <!--FORMAT-->
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Format</Label>
        <String>Tip: {DESCRIPTION}</String>
    </StringTable>


    <!--TIPS-->


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_YellowStar</Label>
        <String>Yellow Stars are more likely to have habitable worlds in orbit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_PurpleStar</Label>
        <String>Purple Stars are more likely to have Promethion in their systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_RedStar</Label>
        <String>Red Stars are more likely to have Durantium in their systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_BlueStar</Label>
        <String>Blue Stars are more likely to have Thulium in their systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_MonsterNest</Label>
        <String>Destroy space monster nests to keep them from overwhelming an area.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_MinorWorld</Label>
        <String>Minor Worlds in your zone of control give their outputs to the closest core world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Approval</Label>
        <String>Keep Approval high by addressing your citizen's needs… and lowering taxes, everybody likes low taxes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Approval2</Label>
        <String>Approval modifies Manufacturing and Research outputs. A population with 50% Approval loses half its Research and Manufacturing outputs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Approval3</Label>
        <String>A citizen's expectations influence their approval. Some beings require more pampering than others.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Rush</Label>
        <String>Ships and Improvements can be rushed to build in one turn at a significant credits cost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Anomalies</Label>
        <String>There are many mysterious anomalies throughout the galaxy. Be sure to survey them with your flagship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Asteroids</Label>
        <String>Asteroid mining facilities are a valuable source of extra manufacturing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Artifacts</Label>
        <String>Powerful artifacts from the age of the Precursors are scattered throughout the galaxy. When found, you can store them in your vault for later use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Capital</Label>
        <String>Core world capitals provide adjacency bonuses to all districts and improvements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Wonder</Label>
        <String>Galactic Achievements are powerful improvements that can only be built once between all players. If you want one, make sure you're the first to complete it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Terraforming</Label>
        <String>Planet tiles can be added with the use of terraforming improvements, special events, and precursor artifacts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Class</Label>
        <String>Planet Class is a measurement of the useable tiles a planet has.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Gov</Label>
        <String>Assign a governor to a class 10 or greater planet to turn it into a core world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Gov2</Label>
        <String>Be sure to keep your governor's loyalty high. If it dips too low, they may decide to split into their own civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Gov3</Label>
        <String>Leaders with high social skill, loyalty, and positive governance traits make good governors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Minister</Label>
        <String>Leaders can be assigned to minister positions to provide beneficial modifiers to your entire civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Policies</Label>
        <String>Enact policies that provide civilization-wide modifiers to better adapt your empire to the current situation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Inputs</Label>
        <String>Planetary inputs such as minerals, technology, and wealth are sent to the nearest core world to be transformed into their respective outputs: Manufacturing, Research, and Income.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Colony</Label>
        <String>Class 9 and below planets make for good feeder colonies. Feeder colonies are planets that send their resources to larger, more productive Core Worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Decay</Label>
        <String>The further away a colony is from a Core World, the more of its resources will be lost in transit. The % lost is measured by Decay.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Influence</Label>
        <String>Influence is radiated out from sources such as planets and starbases. The civ with the most influence on a hex will make that hex part of their zone of control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_CultureFlip</Label>
        <String>A planet belonging to another civilization within your zone of control will begin to rebel. They may even culture flip and join your side.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_CounterInfluence</Label>
        <String>It's important to invest in your civilization's culture. Planets with low cultural investment will have low influence and may even fall into other civilizations' zone of control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Diplo</Label>
        <String>Improve diplomacy with other civilizations by assigning diplomats, trading, or making favorable event decisions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Diplo2</Label>
        <String>Better relations with a civilization will result in better trade deals, gifts, and possibly even alliances.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_WarProfit</Label>
        <String>Convince other civilizations to go to war via diplomacy. This is an especially good strategy for civilizations with the war profiteers ability, such as the Drath.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_MiningStarbase</Label>
        <String>Place mining starbases in a position that maximizes the amount of resources in their area of effect; they can mine multiple resources at once.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_InfluenceStarbase</Label>
        <String>Communications starbases can be used to help push your influence border or resist another Civilization's influence border.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_EconomicStarbase</Label>
        <String>Economic Starbases provide large bonuses to Manufacturing and Income to planets in their area of effect.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_MilitaryStarbase</Label>
        <String>Military starbases can be used to give your fleets significant advantages on the battlefield. Be wary of enemy fleets backed up by a enemy military starbase.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Fighter</Label>
        <String>Fighters are critical in defending your fleet against enemy bomber swarms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Fighter2</Label>
        <String>Fighters can be useful in wearing down defenses of larger ships in attacking in swarms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Bomber</Label>
        <String>Bombers specialize in dealing devastating damage to capital ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Bomber2</Label>
        <String>Bombers work best in swarms and ignore other smaller ships as long as there are capital ships to target.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Frigates</Label>
        <String>Frigates are a larger and more sturdy option for dealing with fighter and bomber swarms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Frigates2</Label>
        <String>Frigates often work best mixed in with the faster-warming ship classes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Cruiser</Label>
        <String>Cruisers boast the increased firepower and defense options of capital ships at a cheaper and more flexible resource cost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Battleship</Label>
        <String>With a large hull, high hit points, and plenty of room for guns and defenses, Battleships make for a good backbone of fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Dreadnought</Label>
        <String>Dreadnoughts dominate space battles and will require many attackers to take down.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Kinetic</Label>
        <String>Kinetic weapons are fast firing and decently accurate but they require close distances and are costly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Beam</Label>
        <String>Beam weapons are accurate and fire at an average rate. They are some of the most cost-effective weapons but don't excel at any one thing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Missile</Label>
        <String>Missile weapons have the longest range but can be inaccurate and slow to fire.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Armor</Label>
        <String>On average, armor will mitigate the most damage when compared to other defensive systems. It is easily overcome by many attacks at once, however.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Shields</Label>
        <String>Shields absorb damage and functionally work like extra health. They recharge in between battles but are overcome by large single attacks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Evasion</Label>
        <String>Evasion rolls on all incoming attacks and has a chance to dodge all damage. It can be hard to come by but is a very powerful defensive option for ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_DefenseRepair</Label>
        <String>Defenses (Armor, Shields, Evasion) repair to full strength in between battles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_RepairSpeed</Label>
        <String>Ships have increased repair speed when in orbit of a friendly planet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Volley</Label>
        <String>Volleys are useful for softening up enemy fleets before engaging in battle.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_SuperHighway</Label>
        <String>Use military starbases with slipstream generator modules to create a super highway to quickly move fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Invasion</Label>
        <String>Core Worlds require ships with high conquest ratings to invade. Try Invader class ships or adding Transport Modules to your ships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Invasion2</Label>
        <String>Specializing Citizens as soldiers is a good way to increase your Planetary Defense.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Command</Label>
        <String>Leaders can be assigned to unique and powerful command ships. Leaders with high Resolve and Diligence make for good commanders.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Culture</Label>
        <String>Increase the discount for certain Culture Trait trees by making the appropriate event decisions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Culture2</Label>
        <String>The last culture trait in a tree unlocks a new powerful tech and often has powerful accompanying effects.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_DataBank</Label>
        <String>Looking for a planet to target with a devastating artifact power? Use the Data Bank to find out where it would hurt your enemy the most.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_FastColony</Label>
        <String>Need a faster colony ship? Add some more engines in the Ship Designer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_TelescopeTakeover</Label>
        <String>Use the Telescope Takeover executive order to scout for habitable planets in the early game.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_OrbitalAcademy</Label>
        <String>The Orbital Academy can be upgraded to various more powerful orbital improvements.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_ProbeRange</Label>
        <String>Probes have unlimited exploration range from the start of the game.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_ExtendRange</Label>
        <String>Colonizable planet just outside of your ship's range? Build a starbase in that direction to extend the range.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Factions</Label>
        <String>The Factions tab in the leader screen is a good place to "retire" obsolete leaders to.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_TradeLicense</Label>
        <String>Track trade routes and licenses on the trade tab in the civilization screen.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Bazaar</Label>
        <String>Use the Galactic Bazaar to acquire those hard-to-get strategic resources… for a price, of course.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Galactapedia</Label>
        <String>Use the Galactapedia (? next to the turn counter) to get more information and search for game terms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_LifeSupport</Label>
        <String>Life support techs are valuable for extending ship range.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Hotkeys</Label>
        <String>You can rebind useful hotkeys in the gameplay section of the options menu.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_GridAndIcons</Label>
        <String>You can adjust the zoom levels at which the grid and icons appear in the interface section of the options menu.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_ShipRefit</Label>
        <String>With the Starship Refits technolog, you can upgrade ships to be refitted with your latest defense systems and weapons.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Carriers</Label>
        <String>Carriers keep a small fleet of fighters ready for battle. The fighters are automatically replaced if destroyed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Criminals</Label>
        <String>Handle criminals by imprisoning them or sending them to a distant colony.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_Districts</Label>
        <String>Building districts are essential to having productive planets. Click a tile you'd like to build on to see available districts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_PlayingWide</Label>
        <String>Playing "wide" involves spreading out to as many colonies and core worlds as possible. Scouting and rushing colony ships early is important for this strategy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tip_PlayingTall</Label>
        <String>Playing "tall" involves purposefully not spreading out and rather using your resources to build your few Core Worlds to be productive powerhouses.</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>