<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the GC4 editor -->
    <!-- UnitRaceText.xml -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Altarian_Name</Label>
        <String>Altarian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Altarian_Dec</Label>
        <String>Most Altarians adopt a Mer, a philosophy they devote their life to. This makes them more ideological than other species and more approving when their [HS=HS_Ideology]Ideology[/HS] matches that of their empire or governor, and more disapproving when it is opposed to them. They can also be specialized to [HS=HS_DivineEmpath]Divine Empaths[/HS], though it is an expensive process.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Arcean_Name</Label>
        <String>Arcean</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Arcean_Dec</Label>
        <String>Arcean's stoic nature makes them unlikely to be [HS=HS_Ideology]ideological[/HS]. Instead they revere the military and Arcean soldiers gain additional [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] and are never pacifists.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Baratak_Name</Label>
        <String>Baratak</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Baratak_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Baratak are stout citizens who require very little to be content. But they are sensitive to [HS=HS_Pollution]Pollution[/HS] and won't be happy, or healthy, on heavily polluted worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Drath_Name</Label>
        <String>Drath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Drath_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Drath are an ancient race that are fond of their legacy and their vast storehouses of credits. They receive an [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] bonus based on the Credits in their treasury.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Drengin_Name</Label>
        <String>Drengin</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Drengin_Dec</Label>
        <String>Drengin have a high [HS=HS_Resistance]Resistance[/HS] and aptitude for becoming strong  [HS=HS_Soldier]Soldiers[/HS]. Drengin have no [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] penalty for living on undefended worlds. They defend themselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Festron_Name</Label>
        <String>Festron</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Festron_Dec</Label>
        <String>Festron love Jungle worlds. They also occasionally murder other species they share a world with.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Human_Name</Label>
        <String>Human</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Human_Dec</Label>
        <String>Humans are known for their flexibility and productivity. They have lower [HS=HS_Expectations]Expectations[/HS] than other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Iconian_Name</Label>
        <String>Iconian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Iconian_Dec</Label>
        <String>Iconians are a paranoid species that are still traumatized by their near extinction by the Yor. Because of this they suffer a significant [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] penalty if they share a world with them. And even though they are as temperamental as other species, their passive nature prevents them from protesting.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Iridium_Name</Label>
        <String>Iridium</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Iridium_Dec</Label>
        <String>Iridium's high Social make them excellent [HS=HS_Trader]Traders[/HS]. They receive an [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] bonus based on the Credits in your treasury.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Manti_Name</Label>
        <String>Manti</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Manti_Dec</Label>
        <String>Manti love [HS=HS_Aquatic]Aquatic[/HS] worlds. They receive a large [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] bonus when they are on them and a slight penalty when they aren't.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Mimot_Name</Label>
        <String>Mimot</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Mimot_Dec</Label>
        <String>An average race with an above average [HS=HS_Growth]Growth[/HS] rate. They will quickly overwhelm planets and consume all available [HS=HS_Food]Food[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Navigators_Name</Label>
        <String>Navigators</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Navigators_Dec</Label>
        <String>Navigator society is built around investigating the wonders of the universe, often to the exclusion of everything else. Their high [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS] makes them the best scientists in the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Onyx_Name</Label>
        <String>Onyx</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Onyx_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Onyx have no need for organic food and sustain themselves on the energy of the universe. [HS=HS_OnyxHiveGrowth]Onyx Hive Growth[/HS] rate is dependent on the amount of Promethion their civilization holds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Torian_Name</Label>
        <String>Torian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Torian_Dec</Label>
        <String>Torian love [HS=HS_Aquatic]Aquatic[/HS] worlds. They receive a large [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] bonus when they are on them and a slight penalty when they aren't. But their subjugation by the Drengin makes them unhappy when they share worlds with Drengin citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Xeloxi_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeloxi</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Xeloxi_Dec</Label>
        <String>Xeloxi have few redeeming qualities, if by few you mean none. Their culture rewards strong action and concerns like ethics or compassion were lost long ago. Every Xeloxi is a criminal and generates [HS=HS_Crime]Crime[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Yor_Name</Label>
        <String>Yor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Yor_Dec</Label>
        <String>As a synthetic species Yor don't require [HS=HS_Food]Food[/HS] or have any natural [HS=HS_Growth]Growth[/HS]. Instead their citizens are manufactured.[BR][BR]They also don't suffer any [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] penalty from Pollution, Overcrowding or reaching their Population Capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Burran_Name</Label>
        <String>Burran</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Burran_Dec</Label>
        <String>A peaceful species who believes that a series of 7 "rigors" will cause them to be elevated to a godlike existence. Each rigor takes many years to accomplish and only the first 3 of these can be performed on their home planet, afterwards they explore the universe pursuing their tasks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Orphica_Name</Label>
        <String>Orphica Enclave</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Orphica_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Orphic Enclave serves only to expand the power of an ancient, renegade supercomputer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Klepart_Name</Label>
        <String>Klepart</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Klepart_Dec</Label>
        <String>The first united technical achievement of their species was the creation of a great beacon tower to send their call out into space. A few days after turning it on an answer was received, a fleet of warships appeared in orbit above their world and raiders were sent down to collect every child on their homeworld. And then the raiders were gone. An entire generation of the Klepart was lost. The next generation has now grown old enough to begin exploring space on their own, but they remain fearful that the raiders will return, and hopeful that they will someday find the children that were stolen from them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Kaxx_Name</Label>
        <String>Kaxx Collective</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Kaxx_Dec</Label>
        <String>They believe their home world is the cocoon for a sleeping creature and they were placed on the planet to guard her. One day they believe the creature will awake and either spread new life across the universe or kill everyone.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Odair_Name</Label>
        <String>Odair Conclave</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Odair_Dec</Label>
        <String>Extreme nihilists counting down the moments until the universe succumbs to the eventual pull of entropy. Believe the Krynn in particular are the most foolish (for their faith) but are hard pressed to be enthused about anyone. There is a black hole at the edge of their galaxy, "The Yawning Mouth of God" that they delight in sending elaborate constructions into.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Lantern_Name</Label>
        <String>Lantern</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Lantern_Dec</Label>
        <String>A young but promising race until early galactic traders introduced them to euphoric vapors that were enjoyed by other species but deeply addictive to the Lantern. Now the Lantern society is dominated by the search for additional sources of the drug and all citizens are kept on it at all times.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Snathi_Name</Label>
        <String>Snathi</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Snathi_Dec</Label>
        <String>Snathi are clever and resourceful, but very likely to be criminals.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Trandal_Name</Label>
        <String>Trandal</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Trandal_Dec</Label>
        <String>Easily distracted and always hungry Trandals are good at taking orders, and that's about it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Tywom_Name</Label>
        <String>Tywom</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Tywom_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Tywom aren't very smart, and certainly aren't very socially adept. Their only positive quality is their incredibly low [HS=HS_Expectations]Expectations[/HS]. They are very accustomed to being treated poorly, and they are even happier when they share a world with other species. Though the other species may not like it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Korath_Name</Label>
        <String>Korath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Korath_Dec</Label>
        <String>If you thought the Drengin were disagreeable, the Korath are even worse. Though they have incredible [HS=HS_Resolve]Resolve[/HS] and [HS=HS_Diligence]Diligence[/HS] their social skills are lacking and they dislike sharing a world with any other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Slyne_Name</Label>
        <String>Slyne</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Slyne_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Slyne do not require organic food to survive, but their slow [HS=HS_Growth]Growth[/HS] rate hampers their ability to spread out into the galaxy as quickly as other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Thalan_Name</Label>
        <String>Thalan</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Thalan_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Thalan are from a dimension more advanced than ours. Their insight provides them with an increased [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS] and also increased [HS=HS_Expectations]Expectations[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Phamysht_Name</Label>
        <String>Phamysht</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Phamysht_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Phamysht are a polite and engaging species, until they murder you. Still, their high [HS=HS_Social]Social[/HS] and [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS] makes up for their equally high [HS=HS_Expectations]Expectations[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Scryve_Name</Label>
        <String>Scryve</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Scryve_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Scryve are waning. Each of their citizens has incredibly high [HS=HS_Diligence]Diligence[/HS], [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS] and [HS=HS_Resolve]Resolve[/HS] but they are handicapped by their low [HS=HS_Growth]Growth[/HS] which will make it difficult to spread out among the stars unless they capture another species to do it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Crystalline_Name</Label>
        <String>Luxar</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Crystalline_Dec</Label>
         <String>Luxar have no need for organic food but their [HS=HS_OnyxHiveGrowth]Growth[/HS] is generally less than organic species. Their growth can be increased based on the amount of Promethion they have stored.[BR][BR]Despite their low growth rate their high [HS=HS_Diligence]Diligence[/HS], [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS] and [HS=HS_Resolve]Resolve[/HS] makes them well suited for nearly any task.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Absolute_Name</Label>
        <String>Irradiated Amoeba</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Absolute_Dec</Label>
        <String>Irradiated citizens evolve if given enough time, each evolution more capable than the last. At the starting Amoeba stage, they reproduce frequently and are quick to evolve but are poor workers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Absolute2_Name</Label>
        <String>Irradiated Larva</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Absolute2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Irradiated citizens evolve if given enough time, each evolution more capable than the last. At the Larva stage, their [HS=HS_Growth]Growth Rate[/HS] slows, but they are more skilled than their Amoeba forms.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Absolute3_Name</Label>
        <String>Irradiated Nymph</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Absolute3_Dec</Label>
        <String>Irradiated citizens evolve if given enough time, each evolution more capable than the last. At the final Nymph stage, their [HS=HS_Growth]Growth Rate[/HS] slows significantly, but they are highly skilled.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Seeing_Name</Label>
        <String>Intueri</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Seeing_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Intueri have high [HS=HS_Diligence]Diligence[/HS] and low [HS=HS_Expectations]Expectations[/HS]. They put the needs of the group over their own. Lacking true complex thought -expect low [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Moth_Name</Label>
        <String>Phalenoids</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Moth_Dec</Label>
        <String>Brilliant and sociable creatures, Phalenoids excel in [HS=HS_Intelligence]Intelligence[/HS] and [HS=HS_Social]Social[/HS], but they make poor soldiers. They prefer to befriend other species. Their [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] increases when sharing their world with other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Feline_Name</Label>
        <String>Feline</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Feline_Dec</Label>
        <String>Elegant and astute, Felinoids distinguish themselves with keen intellect and agile cunning. They prefer roles of strategic importance, thriving as scientists, diplomats, or spies, and display an affinity for complex systems. Highly individualistic, they can struggle with regimented military roles. Their curious natures make them adept cultural adapters, gaining an [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] bonus when cohabiting worlds with other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Canine_Name</Label>
        <String>Canine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Canine_Dec</Label>
        <String>Loyal and intuitive, Caninoids demonstrate exceptional teamwork and remarkable instincts. They naturally excel in roles requiring cooperation and protection, such as military or policing duties. While not typically drawn to independent intellectual pursuits, they're formidable tactical operators within a group dynamic. Their sociable temperament engenders strong bonds, earning them an [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] boost when sharing their world with other species. They have very low expectations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Avian_Name</Label>
        <String>Avian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Avian_Dec</Label>
        <String>Graceful and visionary, Avianoids are known for their strategic foresight and aerial mastery. They excel in roles requiring a broad perspective, such as scouts, diplomats, or strategic planners. Their nimble agility can be less effective in ground-based military engagements. With a natural inclination towards harmony, they gain an [HS=HS_Approval]Approval[/HS] bonus when coexisting with diverse species on their world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Minor_Name</Label>
        <String>Minor Race</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Minor_Dec</Label>
        <String>A less advanced species that is unable to travel outside their solar system.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Zombie_Name</Label>
        <String>Zombies</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_Zombie_Dec</Label>
        <String>Horrible ghouls that grow quickly but aren't very bright.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_RuinedTorian_Name</Label>
        <String>Ruined Torian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Race_RuinedTorian_Dec</Label>
        <String>These pitiful creatures have had their will tortured out of them.</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>