<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!--Campaign Text-->
    <!--Soul of Machine-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>SoulOfMachine_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Soul of the Machine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>SoulOfMachine_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>Even in 2307, the Yor Singularity remains a powerful force in the Galaxy. Long have they strived to bring others into their collective consciousness -the Totality. Though their programming compels them to continue to expand and convert organic to synthetic, they are far from alone among the stars.[BR][BR]The Singularity must make several critical decisions that will determine their efforts for decades. Who among the other Civilizations do they forge alliances with, and who do they destroy? Will their bitter conflict with their creators, the Iconian Refuge, ever end?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_SoulOfMachine_Overall</Label>
        <String>Achieve Any Victory Condition</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_SoulOfMachine_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>Achieve victory by any means necessary. Prove the Yor's superiority in any (if not all) matters. Utilize logic to force all other beings into a Yor-led alliance for an [HS=HS_AllianceVictory]Alliance Victory[/HS]. Deploy perfectly calculated tactics to dominate and eliminate all resistance for a [HS=HS_ConquestVictory]Conquest Victory[/HS]. Dominate the culture through Yor's single-minded and efficient culture for an [HS=HS_InfluenceVictory]Influence Victory[/HS]. Or even achieve a [HS=HS_PrestigeVictory]Prestige Victory[/HS] and prove that no one ranks higher than the Yor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_SoulOfMachine_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>The Iconian Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_SoulOfMachine_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Yor are artificial beings, originally servants of an ancient species known as the Iconians. Granted sentience by the Dread Lords, the Yor turned against their Iconian creators, apparently wiping them from the face of the galaxy. Whether due to some hidden command of the Dread Lords, or simply from applying the cold rules of logic, the Yor have since become viciously xenophobic, and now despise all biological lifeforms. Capable of long-term planning and a surprising degree of cunning, the Yor often speak and negotiate with organic beings. Those beings should understand that this is nothing but a short-term ploy, and that their new friends will never rest until they, and all other organic life, are destroyed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_SoulOfMachine_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Yor are highly productive and capable of building large fleets of self-repairing vessels. They're profoundly unpopular, and few races opt to befriend them. Unlike organic races, their growth rate is a function of production capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <!--Everything For Sale-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EverythingForSale_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Everything for Sale</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EverythingForSale_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>With so many different Civilizations in the Galaxy, 2307 could be a banner year for trade and commerce. Someone needs to facilitate all the various transactions and dealings, and the Corporate Sector is the most obvious fit for the role.[BR][BR]The Corporate Sector has a chance to secure a dominant position in the Galaxy through Influence and market control.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_EverythingForSale_Overall</Label>
        <String>Achieve a Culture Victory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_EverythingForSale_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>Nothing is more influential than currency, at least according to the Corporate Sector. To achieve an [HS=HS_InfluenceVictory]Influence Victory[/HS], have Corporate Sector influence control most of the sector and be at peace with all other major civilizations for several months. Dominate the market so that all other factions rely on trade through the Corporate Sector to survive, which will dissuade conflict.[BR][BR][I]Hit the ESC key and select Victory Status to review how close you are to achieving success.[/I]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_EverythingForSale_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>New Markets Await</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_EverythingForSale_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Corporate Sector is the apex corporate entity of an ultra-capitalistic society, the only organization capable of entering into contracts on behalf of the entire Iridium people. The Iridium culture is based on a firm, even fanatical belief in the power of free markets. Although no strangers to weaponry, all research is first considered through the lens of mutual cooperation; the destructive cost of warfare is often too great for Iridiums to seriously consider. It remains to be seen how well this philosophy will fare when introduced to more close-minded races.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_EverythingForSale_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Corporate Sector is excellent at research and development and quick to maximize the economic potential of any new discovery. They have many ways to fill up the treasury, and they are well-served to use them: their citizens are happiest when they are wealthy, and dislike being poor.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <!--Brave New Universe-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BraveNewUniverse_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Brave New Universe</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BraveNewUniverse_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>In 2317, Subspace Streaming allowed for travel to parts of the Galaxy previously uncharted by the Civilizations of the Orion Sector. In these distant systems are Civilizations capable of faster-than-light travel and have developed advanced technologies. Among them is the Luxar Dominion, a group of crystalline beings with plans for a vast array of arms.[BR][BR]Tensions rise With so many new players on the galactic stage. Is the Luxar Dominion open to forming alliances, or will they utilize their horrifying Terror Stars to wipe out entire systems?[BR][BR]The situation is delicate; one misstep could lead to an all-out war.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_BraveNewUniverse_Overall</Label>
        <String>Achieve an Alliance Victory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_BraveNewUniverse_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Terran Alliance is at the center of a delicate situation. A misstep could lead to a war that leaves countless dead. All-out war should be avoided by any means necessary. Some conflict may be unavoidable, but it should not be sought out. Achieve an [HS=HS_AllianceVictory]Alliance Victory[/HS] by allying with all other major civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_BraveNewUniverse_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Through the use of Subspace Streaming, contact has been made with new Civilizations. Among them is the Luxar Dominion, who developed hyperdrive technology independently, as the Terran Alliance did. They seem prominent and powerful.[BR][BR]The Terran Alliance is now in a delicate situation. The Alliance's actions here can shape the relationship between the disparate Civilizations. A misstep here may lead to a devastating war.[BR][BR]The Terran Alliance must use its sway to keep the peace and form healthy relationships. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_BraveNewUniverse_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Terran Alliance can use diplomacy and military might to influence the civilizations around them. Some conflict may be required, but it should be quelled and avoided whenever possible. Anything but an Influence Victory here threatens all life across the Galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_BraveNewUniverse_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Representatives of the Orion Sector</String>
    </StringTable>

    <!--Radioactive-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Radioactive_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Radioactive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Radioactive_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>2317, the year the Orion sector contacts an entirely new part of the Galaxy. Among the Civilizations reached is the Cosmic Contaminant, a group of nearly incomprehensible lifeforms known as the Irradiated. The Luxar Dominion attempts to rally allies to help exterminate the Cosmic Contaminant.[BR][BR]The Cosmic Contaminant has not survived for millennia, where all other life decays, to be destroyed by those that can't adapt. </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Radioactive_Overall</Label>
        <String>Achieve a Conquest Victory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Radioactive_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's time for the Cosmic Contaminant to do more than survive. The Luxar Dominion has all but ensured there will be no allies among the stars. As other civilizations prepare for war, so should the Cosmic Contaminant. Achieve a [HS=HS_ConquestVictory]Conquest Victory[/HS] by eliminating all other major civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_Radioactive_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Toxic Spreaders</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_Radioactive_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Irradiated developed on toxic and radioactive worlds. Where all others wither, they thrive. They are a threatening enigma that has devastated all others they've encountered. Over time, they have only become more effective at turning planets into polluted wastelands.[BR][BR]The Luxar Dominion, all too familiar with the Irradiated, is attempting to rally the newly contacted Civilizations of the Orion sector against what has been termed the Cosmic Contaminant. They can not be allowed to succeed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_Radioactive_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Assume the Cosmic Contaminant will find no allies here. Treat all other Civilizations as hostile. Utilize all the various ways to pollute planets and render them uninhabitable to all but the Irradiated. A war of attrition benefits the Contaminant, who thrive on planets poisoned in the conflict and replenish numbers quickly.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <!--Return of the Korath-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ReturnOfKorath_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Return of the Korath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ReturnOfKorath_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>The year 2317 heralds the ominous resurgence of the Korath Clan amidst galactic turmoil. [BR][BR]In the annals of the Drengin Empire, the Korath have etched a name for themselves as the epitome of brutality - the quintessential shock troops. Their presence in battle, marked by unprecedented ferocity and a ruthless penchant for destruction, has long been a harbinger of dread. The Korath harbor a zealous belief in the absolute supremacy of the Drengin, viewing all other forms of life as not only inferior but as existential blights unworthy of existence. This extremist ideology sets them apart, even from the Drengin Empire, known for subjugating rather than annihilating perceived inferiors. Such radical divergence in philosophy eventually led to the Korath's estrangement from the Empire. Further distinguishing themselves, the Korath underwent a sinister transformation after their encounters with the enigmatic Dread Lords, emerging as beings who not only believed themselves to be the pinnacle of Drengin evolution but also as harbingers of annihilation for all other species, including their former Drengin brethren.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_ReturnOfKorath_Overall</Label>
        <String>Exterminate the other civilizations</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_ReturnOfKorath_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>The only group worthy of survival is the Korath Clan, and the Korath is more than prepared to prove it. The only course is destruction. Achieve a [HS=HS_ConquestVictory]Conquest Victory[/HS] by driving all other major civilizations to extinction in the name of the Korath Clan.</String>
    </StringTable>


</StringTableList>