<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
   <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_8F3C_Name</Label>
        <String>The Call for Peace</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_8F3C_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME}, renowned for their peace advocacy, urgently contacts you. "The primary objective of our war has been achieved," they argue, "Continuing this conflict will only result in needless loss and expenditure. It's time we sought peace for the sake of all involved."</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_8F3C_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Reject the Call</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_8F3C_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>You dismiss the plea of {LEADERNAME}, asserting that the war will continue under your discretion. "The cost is necessary for our ultimate victory," you declare, knowing this decision may strain loyalty within your ranks.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_8F3C_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Promise Peace</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_8F3C_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>Acknowledging the concerns of {LEADERNAME}, you pledge to initiate peace talks. "We will seek an end to this conflict," you promise, hoping to uphold your word and prevent further fallout.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_9E6Z_Name</Label>
        <String>Reckoning of Promises</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_9E6Z_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} approaches you again, their disappointment palpable. "You vowed to pursue peace, yet the conflict rages on. How many more must suffer before you act?" they implore, challenging you to fulfill your earlier promise or admit the shifting tides of war.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_9E6Z_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Declare Continuation</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_9E6Z_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>With a heavy heart, you inform {LEADERNAME} that the situation has evolved. "Our path to peace is not as clear as we hoped," you explain. "The war must go on for now." You brace yourself for the impact this will have on your people's loyalty.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_9E6Z_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Assure Diligence</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_9E6Z_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>"Your concerns are heard, and not in vain," you assure {LEADERNAME}. "We are actively seeking peace, but such negotiations require time." You hope this reassurance strengthens your cause and maintains the trust of your allies and citizens alike.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_A1B2_Name</Label>
        <String>Fractures of Trust</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_A1B2_Desc</Label>
        <String>"I've defended your promises of peace, believing in your words," {LEADERNAME} confronts you, their frustration barely contained. "Yet, here we stand, farther from peace than ever. How do you justify this to those who've placed their trust in you?"</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_A1B2_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Confess Deception</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_A1B2_Choice1_Desc</Label>
        <String>With a sigh, you drop the facade. "Our strategy demanded it," you admit. "True peace was never an immediate option." You prepare for the fallout, knowing this confession might shatter the remaining loyalty of your closest followers.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_A1B2_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Renew Promise of Peace</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_A1B2_Choice2_Desc</Label>
        <String>"Please, just a bit more patience," you plead, attempting to salvage the situation. "Negotiations are delicate, but we're on the cusp of peace." Your words are a gamble, promising an end that you must now do everything to achieve.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_Final_Name</Label>
        <String>Broken Bonds</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_Final_Desc</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} approaches you one last time, their disappointment palpable. "I've come to realize promises are just words to you," they state coldly. "Your actions have revealed the truth of your intentions. There's nothing left to say." With that, they turn their back, marking the end of your alliance.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_Final_Choice_Name</Label>
        <String>Let the matter drop.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_Final_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>As {LEADERNAME}'s words sink in, you're left to confront the harsh reality of your choices. There's no denying the path you've chosen, and with a heavy heart, you accept the consequences. The war continues but at what cost?</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EV31_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Defense Concerns</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EV31_Desc</Label>
        <String>Amidst the current war, a message from {PLANETNAME} reaches your desk, carrying the collective unease of its people. They feel exposed, defenseless against potential threats, a sentiment amplified by the war's shadow looming over them. The plea is clear: a request to bolster their planetary defenses, if only to provide a semblance of safety and reassurance. You could also ignore their cries, leaving them to fend for themselves against the specter of insecurity.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EV31_Enhance_Choice</Label>
        <String>Invest in some crude defenses.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EV31_Enhance_Desc</Label>
        <String>In a gesture of support, you allocate resources to construct rudimentary defense structures. While more symbolic than tactical, this act serves to lift spirits and reinforce faith in your leadership at the cost of precious Durantium.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EV31_Neglect_Choice</Label>
        <String>Ignore the request.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EV31_Neglect_Desc</Label>
        <String>Opting to concentrate resources elsewhere, you disregard the planetary appeal. This decision, practical from a strategic standpoint, risks dampening the morale of your citizens, who must now grapple with their vulnerabilities unaided.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU01_Name</Label>
        <String>Planetary Unease</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU01_Desc</Label>
        <String>As the war trudges on, despite our strategic objectives being met, The population of {PLANETNAME} grows increasingly uneasy. The delay in peace negotiations has not gone unnoticed, stirring concerns about the future among the populace.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU01_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU02_Name</Label>
        <String>Growing Insecurity</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU02_Desc</Label>
        <String>With the war's objectives seemingly achieved, the continued conflict has left {PLANETNAME} feeling particularly vulnerable. The absence of peace has sown seeds of fear and uncertainty among its citizens, affecting the colony's overall spirit.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU02_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU03_Name</Label>
        <String>Exhaustion from War</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU03_Desc</Label>
        <String>Despite reaching the war's goals, the ongoing conflict has not ceased, leading to widespread exhaustion on {PLANETNAME}. The relentless pace of production to support the war effort is taking its toll on the workforce and machinery alike.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU03_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU04_Name</Label>
        <String>Desperation and Crime</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU04_Desc</Label>
        <String>As the war drags past its objectives, {PLANETNAME} experiences desperation among its citizens. This desperation has manifested in an uptick in criminal activities, as many feel abandoned by the extended conflict and uncertain future.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EU04_Choice_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP01_Name</Label>
        <String>War Profiteers' Hideout</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP01_Desc</Label>
        <String>War profiteers have been discovered operating on {PLANETNAME}. Their presence increases criminal activities, but their removal might provoke pirate attacks nearby.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP01_Allow_Desc</Label>
        <String>Allow them to operate, accepting the rise in crime as a cost of their clandestine activities.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP01_DriveOff_Desc</Label>
        <String>Expel them, risking retaliation in the form of pirate raids near the planet.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP02_Name</Label>
        <String>Pirate Shipyard's Toll</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP02_Desc</Label>
        <String>With the war dragging beyond its intended objectives, a pirate shipyard has emerged due to the increasing number of war profiteers in the area. Near our space, exploiting the prolonged conflict. This operation is significantly impacting the wealth of our planets, as these war profiteers intercept valuable resources meant for the economy.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP02_Understood_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP03_Name</Label>
        <String>Profiteers' Ultimatum</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP03_Desc</Label>
        <String> A shadow economy has flourished as the war stretches beyond its intended goals. A notorious cadre of war profiteers, emboldened by the protracted conflict, has approached your administration. They offer a simple yet morally ambiguous proposition: overlook their siphoning of resources from Starbases, and in return, they'll limit the disruption their operations could cause. Rejecting their terms may bring swift and criminal retribution, spreading fear and chaos across your planets as the war drags on.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP03_Accept_Desc</Label>
        <String>Reluctantly agree to the profiteers' terms, compromising to maintain a semblance of stability.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP03_Reject_Desc</Label>
        <String>Reject the war profiteers' offer. This decision, while morally sound, will incur their wrath.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP04_Name</Label>
    <String>Smuggler's Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP04_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the shadow of a conflict that has long outlived its strategic objectives, the inhabitants of {PLANETNAME} find themselves relying on smugglers for basic necessities. These smugglers, operating under the guise of benefactors, have inadvertently introduced a wave of criminality that threatens to engulf the planet. As desperation grows with the war's prolongation, so does the dilemma of whether to curb their activities, risking the immediate well-being of your people, or tolerate a necessary evil in exchange for survival.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP04_Ignore_Desc</Label>
        <String>Turn a blind eye to the smugglers' operations.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP04_CrackDown_Desc</Label>
        <String>Resolve to restore order and initiate a crackdown on the smugglers' network.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP05_Name</Label>
        <String>Trade Route Turmoil</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP05_Desc</Label>
        <String>With the war's strategic objectives long surpassed, the prolonged conflict has given rise to an unscrupulous breed of war profiteers. These opportunistic entities have infested the trade routes, leeching off the vital arteries of commerce that sustain our civilization. Their activities not only siphon off the wealth meant for reconstruction and aid but also cripple the efficiency of our trade networks, exacerbating the economic strain caused by a war that refuses to end.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_WP05_Understood_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EP01_Name</Label>
        <String>Protests Against the Ongoing War</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EP01_Desc</Label>
        <String>The protracted conflict has finally boiled over into public unrest on {PLANETNAME}. Crowds gather, their voices united in protest against the continuation of a war they see as needless and wasteful. The sentiment across the planet is clear: peace should be negotiated, and further sacrifices are unacceptable.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EP01_Crackdown_Desc</Label>
        <String>Enforce a strict crackdown on dissenting voices.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EP01_BestInterest_Desc</Label>
        <String>Reassure the populace that their leadership is acting with their best interest in mind.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_EP01_FutureSecurity_Desc</Label>
        <String>Reinforce the importance of securing a stable future.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC04_Name</Label>
            <String>Diplomatic Stance under Suspicion</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC04_Desc</Label>
            <String>While our victory on the battlefield is celebrated, the delayed peace negotiations have not gone unnoticed. Allies and neutral observers alike question the delay, hinting at a potential mistrust in our ability to lead toward a peaceful resolution.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC04_Understood_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC03_Name</Label>
            <String>Concerns of Unnecessary Carnage</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC03_Desc</Label>
            <String>As our war efforts persist past the achievement of our goals, several galactic entities express concern over the unnecessary destruction and loss of life. Their warnings hint at a growing dissatisfaction and a potential reevaluation of diplomatic relations.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC03_Understood_Desc</Label>
            <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC02_Name</Label>
        <String>Diplomatic Tensions Rise</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC02_Desc</Label>
        <String>Intelligence reports indicate a growing unease among our allies and neighbors. The prolongation of a conflict, already deemed won, seeds doubt in our motives. This unease threatens to strain diplomatic ties as calls for peace grow louder.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC02_Understood_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        	<Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC01_Name</Label>
        	<String>Rising International Concern</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        	<Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC01_Desc</Label>
        	<String>Rumors have reached your ears that other civilizations are growing concerned over our prolonged conflict. Some fear that our original war goals might have been a pretext for a greater, more encompassing conflict. This could jeopardize our diplomatic relations globally.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        	<Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC01_Understood_Desc</Label>
        	<String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC05_Name</Label>
            <String>Suspected Warmonger</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC05_Desc</Label>
            <String>The continuation of the war, well beyond its strategic goals, isolates us on the galactic stage. Other civilizations view our actions with increasing suspicion, believing our intentions may not be as clear-cut as once thought.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_DC05_Understood_Desc</Label>
        <String>Understood.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_GenericLeaderPromise_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LeaderName} will remember your promised to seek peace.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE01_Name</Label>
        <String>Stressful Times</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE01_Desc</Label>
        <String>Amidst the lingering shadows of the war, a notable leader expresses concerns over the escalating stress levels among the populace. The strain of the prolonged conflict has made daily tasks and responsibilities increasingly challenging. The leader looks to you, hoping for a swift and peaceful resolution to the war's tensions.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE01_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Promise to seek peace.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE01_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Pressure to maintain focus.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE02_Name</Label>
        <String>Unfulfilled Promises</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE02_Desc</Label>
        <String>Returning with deep frustrations, the leader confronts you about the elusive promised peace. The prolonged conflict and unmet assurances have left them questioning the path ahead.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE02_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Dismiss the leader.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE03_Name</Label>
            <String>A Leader's Concern</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE03_Desc</Label>
            <String>A leader approaches with a heavy heart, troubled by the war's continuation beyond its intended goals. They express deep concern for the people's well-being and the growing unease among the populace. 'The weight of prolonged conflict bears down on us all,' they confide, seeking reassurance or action to mitigate the strain.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE03_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Promise to seek peace.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE03_Choice2_Title</Label>
            <String>Pressure to persevere.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE04_Name</Label>
            <String>Logistical Limitations</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE04_Desc</Label>
            <String>Another leader comes forward, visibly stressed by the logistical nightmares spawned by the war's overextension. 'Our resources are stretched thin, and the people grow weary of unending demands,' they lament, seeking a directive to alleviate the pressure without compromising the war effort.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE04_Choice1_Title</Label>
            <String>Reassure and promise relief.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
            <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE04_Choice2_Title</Label>
            <String>Insist on maintaining course.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE05_Name</Label>
        <String>Rumors of Unrest</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE05_Desc</Label>
        <String>A governor brings rumors of unrest stirring among the populace, exacerbated by the war dragging past its objectives. 'The people's patience wears thin, and the murmurs of discontent grow louder each day,' they report, seeking guidance on how to best address the burgeoning dissent.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE05_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Advise direct swift action.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_LE05_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Encourage persuasive measures.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR01_Name</Label>
        <String>Rebel Outbreak</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR01_Desc</Label>
        <String>On {PLANETNAME}, a war prolonged beyond its objectives has given rise to anti-war rebels. Marking their opposition, they have significantly disrupted the planet's manufacturing capabilities, urging an immediate cease to hostilities. The leadership faces a crucial decision: to crack down on these activities or to publicly announce efforts to conclude the war.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR01_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Initiate a crackdown.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR01_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Announce an increase in peace efforts.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR02_Name</Label>
        <String>Rebel Escalation</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR02_Desc</Label>
        <String>Despite attempts to negotiate peace, the war lingers, emboldening the rebels on {PLANETNAME}. Their numbers swell as more join their cause, driven by disillusionment and anger. The planet stands on the brink of widespread unrest.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR02_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Increase crack down efforts.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR02_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Reiterate peace promises.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR03_Name</Label>
        <String>Countermeasures</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR03_Desc</Label>
        <String>In the wake of the crackdown and the continued war, the rebels on {PLANETNAME} have begun to retaliate, targeting the planet's defenses. This act of defiance not only undermines the planet's security but also strains the already limited resources.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR03_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Intensify crackdown.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR03_Choice2_Title</Label>
        <String>Focus on maintaining defenses.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR04_Name</Label>
        <String>Riot Aftermath</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR04_Desc</Label>
        <String>The rebels' unrest escalates into a full-blown riot on {PLANETNAME}, significantly impacting manufacturing, spiking crime rates, and hindering growth. The administration is now forced to navigate these tumultuous times with limited options. The rebels threaten to continue to escalate their strikes until the drawn-out war is brought to an end and peace is negotiated.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR04_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Attempt to maintain order.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR05_Name</Label>
        <String>Unending Unrest</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR05_Desc</Label>
        <String>The anti-war rebellion has morphed into an ongoing crisis on {PLANETNAME}. Despite efforts to quell the unrest, the riot continues unabated, further disrupting the fabric of society with no end in sight as the war lingers. The rebels refuse to give up until peace is negotiated and the war with its goals accomplished is brought to an end.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarWeariness_AR05_Choice1_Title</Label>
        <String>Attempt to maintain order.</String>
    </StringTable>

</StringTableList>