<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<FlavorTextDefs xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">

    <!---->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Korath_StartOfGame</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Benvenuto, entità. Ti trovi davanti ai Korath, l'avanguardia suprema dell'universo e l'ultima rappresentazione di un Drengin.[BR][BR]È tempo che tu comprenda la nostra dottrina, il principio guida della nostra esistenza. [BR][BR]Nell'immenso spazio del cosmo, esiste un ordine naturale, una gerarchia non dichiarata che governa ogni forma di vita. Noi, i Korath, siamo l'apice di questo ordine, il culmine dell'evoluzione e della coscienza. La nostra filosofia non è di malizia, ma di necessità logica. [BR][BR]Considera le semplici azioni che compi per preservare il tuo habitat. Quando le vespe nidificano nella tua dimora, non le allontani? È considerato malevolo rivendicare terre dalle paludi per riparo o eradicare i parassiti che minacciano la tua esistenza? Fai queste cose non per odio, ma per un bisogno primordiale di sopravvivenza e progresso. [BR][BR]Allo stesso modo, consideriamo le altre specie come tu potresti considerare queste semplici creature. Per noi, non sono senzienti come lo siamo noi; mancano della nostra consapevolezza, della nostra profonda comprensione dell'universo. La loro esistenza, nel suo stato inferiore di evoluzione, non equivale alla nostra. Così come potresti macellare il bestiame per sostentamento o decimare animali per un maggiore equilibrio ecologico, noi agiamo per mantenere l'equilibrio cosmico. [BR][BR]Le nostre azioni sono spesso interpretate come crudeltà, ma sono, in sostanza, una forma di amministrazione cosmica. L'eliminazione delle specie più deboli è un dovere, non una scelta. È una responsabilità che ci assumiamo, per garantire la sopravvivenza e il dominio della forma di vita più elevata - i Drengin. [BR][BR]Non ci compiacciamo di questo compito; è un fardello che accettiamo. È una progressione logica dell'ordine naturale, un passo necessario verso la purezza e l'equilibrio galattico. Consentire alle specie inferiori di proliferare significa invitare il caos, turbare il delicato tessuto dell'universo. [BR][BR]L'universo non è una culla di benevolenza; è un regno di verità inesorabili. E la verità è questa: solo i più forti, i più evoluti, hanno il diritto di plasmare il futuro. Questa è l'essenza della nostra filosofia, il nucleo del nostro essere. I Korath non cercano il male; cerchiamo ordine, progresso e l'ascensione dei legittimi sovrani delle stelle.[BR][BR]Tu, entità, hai la rara opportunità di osservarci mentre svolgiamo il nostro necessario lavoro. Rallegrati di questa opportunità. Assisti ai Korath in azione. Assisti all'ordine naturale dell'universo.</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>Conversation_KorathMeetOthers</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Nel grande arazzo dell'universo, ogni filo ha il suo posto, ogni specie il suo ruolo. [BR][BR]Noi siamo osservatori, all'inizio apprendisti, cercando di comprendere la natura unica delle altre entità. La nostra filosofia è quella di uno studio attento, per accertare il ruolo che ogni specie gioca nel grande disegno. È un equilibrio delicato, che non disturbiamo senza motivo. [BR][BR]Notate che qui, in questo momento di contatto, tendiamo una mano di cauta amicizia verso queste creature. Ma siate consapevoli, l'universo è un luogo di giudizio e conseguenza, e noi, i Korath, ne siamo i vigili custodi. [BR][BR]Osserveremo e poi agiremo per rimuovere la specie come elemento destabilizzante. Questo è un atto di purificazione, non di malevolenza. È un'escissione chirurgica, precisa e priva di crudeltà inutile, proprio come potare un albero per la salute dell'intero. [BR][BR]Osservate. Imparate. Comprendete. E siate grati per il servizio che forniamo.</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>


    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We stand before you as the enduring survivors of our own tragedy. We know of your beliefs, your view of other species as lesser. But heed this: we are not mere specters to be dismissed or eradicated. [BR][BR]Our history is one of resilience against the Yor, a testament to our strength and will. In our first encounter, we urge you to reconsider your notions. We are not adversaries to be conquered, but equals to be respected in the cosmic arena.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_PEACEFUL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>I wonder what you'll taste like.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_TRADE</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Let us see what you have that justifies your continuing existence.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>1000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_NEUTRAL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>It is unlikely you are going to make the cosmic cut.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

    

    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ARCEAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>I don't remember the Drengin being quite this ugly. Sickly even.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_PEACEFUL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ARCEAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerFaction>FACTION_KORATH_Campaign_ReturnOfKorath</ListenerFaction>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We are not Drengin!</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_TRADE</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We might as well trade while the peace remains.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>1000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_NEUTRAL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ARCEAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your bones will make excellent decorations.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

    
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your arrival fills us with deep concern. Your reputation precedes you, a shadow cast across the stars, a symbol of unbridled malevolence and destruction.[BR][BR]Our civilization, guided by principles of enlightenment and harmony, stands in stark contrast to your ruthless ethos. The Korath's blatant disregard for life, for the sanctity of sentient existence, is an abomination in our eyes.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_PEACEFUL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You have no value. You are neither sentient or food.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>500</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_NEUTRAL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your skin has a pleasant hue to it.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

    
    
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TORIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our people, the Torians, and our memory of suffering at the hands of monsters like you is long and bitter. Your kind, with your contemptuous view of other species as mere tools, embodies the very essence of our disdain. [BR][BR]We are acutely aware of the atrocities you commit, the abhorrent genetic manipulations to create docile, ruined beings, treating sentient life as cattle. Such acts are not just aggressive; they are an affront to the very essence of what it means to be sentient. [BR][BR]We will not go quietly into the night.
                </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_PEACEFUL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TORIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>It is always good to find a fresh supply of Torian.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_NEUTRAL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TORIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You appear more defective than is typical of your kind.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

    
    
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRATH</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We greet you with a nod of equal stature, yet with eyes wide open to your true nature. Your strength is undeniable.[BR][BR]We recognize you as a formidable player. Like us, you understand the necessity of asserting dominance. While you wield brute force, for that suits your limited capabilities, we prefer the subtlety of manipulation, the art of steering events from the shadows.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_PEACEFUL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRATH</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A quasi-sentient dragon is hardly subtle.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_NEUTRAL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRATH</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>It is laughable that a mere beast believes they can interact with us on our level.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>


    
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_IRIDIUM</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We of the Corporate Sector make no excuses. You, like all our potential customers, are above us. You are better than us.  But consider this, instead of exterminating us, think of us as species that could be made use of. The Limuras of Thacos IV that clean the fins off the Urho sharks.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100000</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_PEACEFUL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_IRIDIUM</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Perhaps we may let you live.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_RESPONSE_NEUTRAL</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_IRIDIUM</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>ExterminatorsAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We have drone technology to service our needs. We don't need more parasites.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>


</FlavorTextDefs>
