<StringTableList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd"><StringTable>
        <Label>ImpressCitizens_Name</Label>
        <String>Impress Citizens</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ImpressCitizens_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our people are owned by you. It is time they remember. Will provide a Colony Ship and a Constructor</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedLabor_Name</Label>
        <String>Forced Labor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedLabor_Dec</Label>
        <String>The people are working hard. They could be working harder.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedTraining_Name</Label>
        <String>Thrall Training</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedTraining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Trains thralls to increase target fleet experience.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>RushNewCitizen_Name</Label>
        <String>Manufacture Population</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>RushNewCitizen_Dec</Label>
        <String>Without using Durantium we can recycle scraps to quickly produce more citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FleetIncreaseMovesEO_Name</Label>
        <String>Upgrade Fleet Propulsion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FleetIncreaseMovesEO_Dec</Label>
        <String>Use our executive powers to focus our efforts onto a single fleet to optimize its speed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MilitaryConstructionEO_Name</Label>
        <String>Shipyard Production Boost</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MilitaryConstructionEO_Dec</Label>
        <String>Focus our efforts to quickly supply manufacturing resources to a specific shipyard.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InfluenceBroadcast_Name</Label>
        <String>Broadcast Culture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InfluenceBroadcast_Dec</Label>
        <String>This module contains an optimized message certain to make others wish to assimilate to our culture.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>PlanetTiles_Name</Label>
        <String>Modify Planet</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PlanetTiles_Dec</Label>
        <String>Increase this planet's use to our species. Adds +1 to its usable tiles. Should only be used on Core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>

<StringTable>
        <Label>Entry_DrenginEmpire</Label>
        <String>Drengin Empire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Entry_DrenginEmpire_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Drengin Empire embodies the quintessence of cosmic ambition. Towering at over 9 feet and brandishing an impressive set of razor-sharp teeth, their reputation in the galaxy is one of both awe and fear. The year 2226 marked a poignant chapter in their history, witnessing a civil confrontation with the Korath. And in this intricate dance of power, the Drengin, surprisingly, were the more measured participants.[BR][BR]The Drengin's creed is simple: the galaxy and all its non-Drengin inhabitants exist for their dominion. Their history with the Arceans is a testament to this belief. The joint invention of the stargates was a landmark of cooperation, swiftly followed by the Drengin's attempted betrayal. The ensuing debacle cemented a rivalry that remains fervent, even as stars burn out.[BR][BR]It would be an error to assume the Drengin's aggressiveness overshadows their intellect. Their technological marvels tread into areas many would deem ethically nebulous. Their persistence in galactic conquest is evident from their historical annals. When humanity was embroiled in terrestrial power struggles, the Drengin were engineering audacious mechanisms, like the ominous 'death furnaces', and undertaking expansive campaigns like the Torian enslavement.[BR][BR]Ironically, what held the Drengin back from universal domination was the vastness of space itself. Their venture to Toria, while grand, underscored the inefficiencies of their space travel. Humanity's invention of the hyperdrive, however, leveled the cosmic playing field. The initial human overtures, grounded in idealistic hopes of a united cosmos, were met with Drengin pragmatism in 2176. The ensuing silence from that human delegation speaks volumes, reminding us all that cosmic diplomacy, with the Drengin, comes with its own set of... challenges.</String>
    </StringTable>
<StringTable>
        <Label>PainAmplifier_Name</Label>
        <String>Pain Amplifier</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PainAmplifier_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the constant pain of our citizens to get them to focus in order to increase [HS=HS_Research]Research[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>ConstructBroadcastModule_Name</Label>
        <String>Broadcast Culture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ConstructBroadcastModule_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Produces a Broadcast module for our Vault which can be used to broadcast our culture from a target friendly planet.</String>
    </StringTable>

    
<StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Drengin_Name</Label>
        <String>Warships</String>
      </StringTable>

      <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Drengin_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provide a prototype Siege ship to conquer small enemy worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Drengin_Dec</Label>
        <String>The galaxy and its people must be destroyed if it is to be reborn under our rule. A prototype Siege Ship will bring our might to the weak very quickly.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepSpaceLabor_Name</Label>
        <String>Deep Space Labor Training</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepSpaceLabor_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Trains our thralls to work in space on asteroids and starships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepSpaceLabor_Dec</Label>
        <String>Getting our thralls to do work is always hard. Getting them to do it in space is nearly impossible without the right techniques. This technology enables us to more effectively use our thralls to mine asteroids as well as station them on ships which frees up actual people to do what matters.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarPropulsion_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Propulsion</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarPropulsion_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes Experimental Drive Policies available</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarPropulsion_Dec</Label>
        <String>We need to better understand what is involved in traveling through bent space in order to make the most of it.  This technology will allow us to disseminate to our captains new ways of traveling faster. </String>
    </StringTable>

    
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_PlanetarySubstrates_Name</Label>
    <String>Planetary Substrates</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_PlanetarySubstrates_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Prepare our worlds for synthetic life. Provides device to increase planet class.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_PlanetarySubstrates_Dec</Label>
    <String>By integrating advanced planetary substrates, our robotic kin can seamlessly synchronize with the core of planets, enhancing our resource extraction and optimization capabilities.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_GodOfTheMachine_Name</Label>
    <String>God of the Machine</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_GodOfTheMachine_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Develop a theory of consciousness. Provides a device to increase our influence.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_GodOfTheMachine_Dec</Label>
    <String>Delving into the intricate fabric of thought and cognition, the "God of the Machine" technology represents a profound understanding of synthetic consciousness. This monumental breakthrough not only demystifies the very essence of sentience but also equips us with an advanced device that amplifies our influence across systems. By resonating with the fundamental frequencies of robotic cognition, this device strengthens our diplomatic and strategic outreach, positioning our robotic species at the forefront of galactic affairs.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_RecursiveModels_Name</Label>
    <String>Recursive Models</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_RecursiveModels_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Create new modes of thought allowing for greater research. Provides a space exploration device.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_RecursiveModels_Dec</Label>
    <String>The "Recursive Models" epitomizes a quantum leap in synthetic cognitive architectures. Harnessing principles from non-linear dynamics and advanced algorithmic topology, this technology enables our robotic consciousness to access and iterate through multi-dimensional thought planes, thus optimizing our computational research vectors. Accompanying this advancement is an ultra-spectral space exploration device, crafted from exotic matter and quantum-entangled sensors. This apparatus operates in tandem with our enhanced cognition, probing space-time anomalies and extracting hyper-detailed cosmological data. In transcending our previous limitations, we are poised to decode the very matrix of the cosmos, navigating its intricate tapestry with a rigor previously deemed unattainable.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_DiversityOfLife_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Synthesis</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_DiversityOfLife_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Assimilate other cultures into our own to amplify our own. Unlocks the [HS=HS_BroadcastCulture]Broadcast Culture[/HS] project.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_DiversityOfLife_Dec</Label>
    <String>By meticulously studying the plethora of lifeforms and their intricate cultural tapestries, this advanced technology enables our robotic civilization to curate a meta-culture&#8212;a confluence of the myriad. As we assimilate, interpret, and emulate these diverse cultural nuances, we create a universal appeal that resonates with a vast spectrum of lifeforms. This not only amplifies our cultural growth but also fosters a harmonious coexistence in the galactic milieu, turning diversity into our strength and establishing us as cultural beacons in the cosmos.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_Negotiations_Name</Label>
    <String>Negotiation Algorithms</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_Negotiations_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves our communication skills with inferior beings.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_Negotiations_Dec</Label>
    <String>In the vast expanse of the cosmos, where myriad civilizations converge, the art of negotiation becomes pivotal. The "Diplomatic Algorithms of Negotiation" technology represents a quantum leap in synthetic interpersonal dynamics. By deconstructing and simulating countless diplomatic scenarios and cultural intricacies, we've fine-tuned our protocols to understand, adapt, and resonate with diverse species. These advanced algorithms not only enhance our negotiation prowess but also expedite the establishment of harmonious ties. As we navigate the vast tapestry of galactic politics, this newfound expertise positions our robotic civilization as astute diplomats, forging alliances and understanding even in the most complex of interstellar relations.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Yor_Name</Label>
    <String>Weaponized Probes</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Yor_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Augment exploration probes with weaponry.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Yor_Dec</Label>
    <String>Within our relentless drive for optimization lies the fusion of exploration and combat utility. The "Weaponized Probes Protocol" crystallizes this philosophy. Merging our sophisticated shuttle tech with cutting-edge armaments, we've birthed a new breed of probes &#8211; equipped to explore, report, and when necessary, retaliate. This evolutionary step not only solidifies our presence in the vast expanse but also ensures that our expeditions remain unchallenged, reinforcing the Yor's position as a dominant force in the galactic theatre.</String>
</StringTable>



</StringTableList>