<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExperimentalDrugConsequence_0xC3B1_Name</Label>
    <String>Cure side effects</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExperimentalDrugConsequence_0xC3B1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Remember the experimental cure we used on {PLANETNAME}? The people there do.[BR][BR]It appears the experimental drug has drastically boosted the cognitive abilities of its users. They exhibit enhanced intelligence, innovative ideas, and accelerated technological progress. However, there are noticeable behavioral changes: increased aggression, impatience, and a tendency towards rash decisions. [BR][BR]Do we nurture this newfound intelligence or attempt to revert the changes with another treatment?</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExperimentalDrugConsequence_Choice_1_0xC3B1_Name</Label>
    <String>Encourage the intellect. Ignore the psychopaths.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExperimentalDrugConsequence_Choice_1_0xC3B1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We decide to embrace and guide this heightened intelligence, reaping the benefits of innovation and growth at the potential cost of civil unrest. [BR][BR]We can always build more prisons. Our citizens will gain +10 to their intelligence.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExperimentalDrugConsequence_Choice_2_0xC3B1_Name</Label>
    <String>Revert the changes. Safety and harmony come first.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_ExperimentalDrugConsequence_Choice_2_0xC3B1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We choose to introduce a new experimental treatment aiming to neutralize the drug's side effects, prioritizing the mental well-being and harmony of our populace over the rapid advancements. [BR][BR]No immediate result.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeo_Name</Label>
    <String>Worm Rodeo</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeo_Dec</Label>
    <String>We recently received word that an important leader from the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} was visiting {PLANETNAME}.  You may recall that you established a worm rodeo there some time ago. [BR][BR]The alien visitor was so impressed that this has led to improved relations with their species.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeoChoice_Name</Label>
    <String>I knew it was a good idea.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeo_Choice_Text_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Worm Rodeo continues.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_SpaceWhaleMurder_Name</Label>
    <String>Space Whale Slaughterer</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_SpaceWhaleMurder_Dec</Label>
    <String>We are horrified and disgusted that you would exterminate the precious Lilulas, the gentle space creatures that were migrating through this part of space. The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} condemns your vile actions.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_SpaceWhaleMurder_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>I never thought you'd find out.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_HiveMinds_Name</Label>
        <String>Hive Mind</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_HiveMind_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Every individual operates in perfect harmony, guided by a shared consciousness. The concept of "self" has dissolved, making the civilization a powerful, singular entity.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]All units and cities act in perfect coordination with significant bonuses to simultaneous actions. Unlocks Post-Sentience technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_TerrorStars_Name</Label>
        <String>Terror Stars</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_TerrorStars_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]The vastness of space hides terrifying wonders, harnessed by our civilization for dominance and defense.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Enhanced cosmic weaponry and interstellar fortifications. Fear strikes enemies upon encounter. Unlocks the Terror Star technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Sanctuary_Name</Label>
        <String>Sanctuary</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Sanctuary_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]In a galaxy of turmoil, our civilization stands as a beacon of refuge and hope.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Diplomatic bonuses and enhanced defenses make our territories a haven for allies and citizens. Unlocks The Consensus Maker technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Singularity_Name</Label>
        <String>Singularity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Singularity_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Embracing the pinnacle of technological advancement, our civilization hovers on the brink of becoming something... transcendent.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Massive bonuses in all tech-related endeavors. Possibility of evolving into a post-biological state. Unlocks Technological Singularity technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Utopia_Name</Label>
        <String>Utopia</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Utopia_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]In our pursuit of perfection, we have crafted a society where all prosper and harmony reigns supreme.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Exceptional societal happiness, growth, and prosperity across all systems. All planets gain 1000 influence. Unlocks Dream of Utopia technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Legacy_Name</Label>
        <String>Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Legacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Honoring the past, our civilization ensures that its achievements and wisdom will endure for eons.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Monuments, wonders, and cultural outputs are enhanced. History is preserved meticulously. We have successfully integrated the knowledge of the Precursors with our own glorious traditions. Provides 50 Prestige points. Unlocks Glorious Legacy technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_BigBrother_Name</Label>
        <String>Big Brother</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_BigBrother_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Every move, every whisper, every thought is monitored for the greater good.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Impeccable internal security and surveillance. Dissent is almost non-existent. Expectations on citizens lowered by 50 points. Unlocks Coordinated Travel technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_SovereignIdentity_Name</Label>
        <String>Sovereign Identity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_SovereignIdentity_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Above all, our civilization values its unique identity and independence, standing firm in the face of external influences.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Strong resistance against external cultural or diplomatic influences. Enhanced national pride and unity. All citizens stats increased by a factor of 3. Unlocks Individual Divinity technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    

<StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_0x62A3_Name</Label>
        <String>The Rare Resource Proposition</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_0x62A3_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} contacts you with news.[BR][BR] A mining conglomerate has discovered a deposit of crystalized Elerium on {PLANETNAME}, a material vital for advanced energy systems and weaponry. The conglomerate offers two proposals. [BR][BR]The first is to mine the resource using an AI based strip mining, which will bring immediate economic benefits but could harm the local environment and populace. [BR][BR]The second is to mine it sustainably, ensuring the well-being of the planet but at a slower economic pace.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_1_0x62A3_Name</Label>
        <String>Mine it all now. Who cares about alien whales and other space fish?</String> 
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_1_0x62A3_Dec</Label>
        <String>You will gain credits immediately but it will create a bit of an environmental catastrophe.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_2_0x62A3_Name</Label>
        <String>Take your time. We are in no hurry.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_RareResource_Choice_2_0x62A3_Dec</Label>
        <String>You will use slower but gentler techniques to extract the resource.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_0x72B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Artifact found</String>
    </StringTable>


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_0x72B4_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} reaches out with intriguing news.[BR][BR] A mysterious ancient artifact has been unearthed on {PLANETNAME}. The artifact emits a unique frequency. Experts present two choices: Harvest the frequency as an energy source, which can be a boon for our reserves, or dedicate resources to decode it for ancient knowledge. The choice is yours.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_1_0x72B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Harvest the energy.</String> 
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_1_0x72B4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We will benefit from a sudden boost in energy, but may face backlash for destroying a piece of history.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_2_0x72B4_Name</Label>
        <String>Decode its secrets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientArtifact_Choice_2_0x72B4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We'll gain knowledge possibly accelerating our technological growth, but will miss out on the immediate energy boost.</String>
    </StringTable>


    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_0x82C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Controversial Visit</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_0x82C5_Dec</Label>
        <String>{LEADERNAME} sends an urgent transmission.[BR][BR] Ambassador Zaraq from the {PLAYERFACTION:1} wishes to visit {PLANETNAME} for a diplomatic summit. [BR][BR]The ambassador is not popular.[BR][BR]Really really not popular.[BR][BR]Do we grant the visit or decline diplomatically?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_1_0x82C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Grant the visit.</String> 
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_1_0x82C5_Dec</Label>
        <String>Strengthening ties with the {PLAYERFACTION:1} might lead to new opportunities, but risks unrest among our citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_2_0x82C5_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline the visit.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_ForeignVisit_Choice_2_0x82C5_Dec</Label>
        <String>Peace within the colony will be maintained, but our relations with the {PLAYERFACTION:1} suffer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_0x92D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Harvesting Dilemma</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>Governor {LEADERNAME} contacts you with an intriguing proposition. [BR][BR]The {PLAYERFACTION:1} have expressed interest in harvesting a unique plant from {PLANETNAME}. This flora produces a resin that is a potent ingredient for various beneficial chemicals. However, this resin can also be refined into a potent and addictive drug. [BR][BR]Allowing the harvest would bolster relations and boost planetary income, but could also lead to increased crime rates on the colony.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_1_0x92D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Allow the harvest. Our finances could use the boost.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_1_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>Relations with {PLAYERFACTION:1} will improve and the planet's economy will improve, but crime will rise on {PLANETNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_2_0x92D6_Name</Label>
        <String>Deny the request. We don't what the syndicate to show up.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Choice_2_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>Relations with {PLAYERFACTION:1} will deteriorate but at least the crime will remain unchanged on {PLANETNAME}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AlienPlantHarvest_Relations_0x92D6_Dec</Label>
        <String>You spurned our Ambassador</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_0xA7F4_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ancient Enigma</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_0xA7F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>Governor {LEADERNAME} sends you a transmission detailing the discovery of an ancient Arnorian facility on {PLANETNAME}. [BR][BR]The energy signal it emits could be of great value, but the indigenous species we've encountered on the planet consider it sacred ground. [BR][BR]Should we harness its energy or respect the local beliefs?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_1_0xA7F4_Name</Label>
        <String>Extract the energy. Might makes right.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_1_0xA7F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We will harness the facility's energy, boosting our surplus manufacturing reserves but possibly straining relations with the indigenous species on {PLANETNAME}.[BR][BR]No immediate consequences to be seen.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_2_0xA7F4_Name</Label>
        <String>Respect the sacred site. We shouldn't interfere.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_AncientFacility_Choice_2_0xA7F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We decide to honor the indigenous species' beliefs, ensuring peace on {PLANETNAME} but foregoing the potential energy resource.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_0xB8A2_Name</Label>
        <String>The Plague</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_0xB8A2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Governor {LEADERNAME} reaches out with alarming news: a mysterious illness has struck {PLANETNAME}. A locally developed experimental drug might combat the disease, but its potential side effects are unknown. [BR][BR]Relying solely on approved treatments will curb the epidemic but slow the planet's growth for years. How should we proceed?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_1_0xB8A2_Name</Label>
        <String>Compel the population to use the experimental drug.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_1_0xB8A2_Dec</Label>
        <String>The experimental drug is distributed widely, potentially preventing further devastation but introducing the risk of unknown side effects. </String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_2_0xB8A2_Name</Label>
        <String>Use only approved treatments. Safety first.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_GovernorEvent_IllnessDilemma_Choice_2_0xB8A2_Dec</Label>
        <String>By using only the tried-and-tested methods, we ensure the well-being of our citizens, even if it means a setback for {PLANETNAME}'s growth.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_0xD4E2_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Exchange Proposition</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_0xD4E2_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached Governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with an intriguing offer. They wish to establish a cultural exchange office on our planet, promising aid in our manufacturing endeavors. [BR][BR]However, our intelligence suggests this could serve as a cover for their espionage activities. [BR][BR]Accepting their offer might bolster our production, but at the potential risk of a spy network. Rejecting might offend them. How should we proceed?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_1_0xD4E2_Name</Label>
        <String>Accept the offer. We'll take the risk for the aid.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_1_0xD4E2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We decide to welcome the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} and their cultural exchange office, receiving their manufacturing aid but also exposing ourselves to potential espionage. [BR][BR]No immediate consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_2_0xD4E2_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline politely. We cannot risk our security.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CulturalExchangeProposal_Choice_2_0xD4E2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We choose to prioritize our security, declining the offer of the {PLAYERFACTION:1} . This might sour our relations, but our planet's security remains uncompromised. [BR][BR]No immediate consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_0xF3A8_Name</Label>
        <String>Observation Post</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached Governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with an unusual request. They wish to set up an observation post to study our society and culture. In exchange, they are offering us advanced technology. [BR][BR]However, our citizens are deeply uncomfortable with the idea of being under the watchful eyes of the {PLAYERFACTION:1}. [BR][BR]While their technology is tempting, we must consider the well-being of our people. Declining might be seen as an insult to the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}. What should we do?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_1_0xF3A8_Name</Label>
        <String>Accept the offer. We could use some tech.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_1_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>We grant the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} their observation post in exchange for their technology. However, our citizens may feel uneasy about their new observers. [BR][BR]No immediate consequences.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_2_0xF3A8_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline. This isn't an ant farm.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Choice_2_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>We prioritize the well-being and comfort of our citizens, denying the {PLAYERFACTION:1} request.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_YorObservationProposal_Diplomatic_0xF3A8_Dec</Label>
        <String>You denied our observation post</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_0xG4B9_Name</Label>
        <String>Codex Offer</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached the governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with a unique offer: they are willing to share a codex of Universal Truths in exchange for some ancient relics that have little value to us but are of great importance to them.[BR][BR]The Codex would increase the cultural value of this planet given its historic value.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_1_0xG4B9_Name</Label>
        <String>Accept the Offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_1_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've chosen to trade the relics for the codex, hoping the knowledge within will increase this world's influence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_2_0xG4B9_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline the Offer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Choice_2_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>We respectfully decline the {PLAYERFACTION:1} proposal, choosing to safeguard the relics. This may affect relations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_AltarianCodexProposal_Diplomatic_0xG4B9_Dec</Label>
        <String>You declined our Codex</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_0xH5C1_Name</Label>
    <String>Historic Revelation</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>The ancient {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached the governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with a profound offer: they wish to share their ancient history that reveals the tales of the Arnor, Dread Lords, and the momentous Precursor wars.[BR][BR]Such knowledge can be both a blessing and a curse, reshaping the beliefs and culture of the local population.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_1_0xH5C1_Name</Label>
    <String>Accept the Revelation.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_1_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By accepting this history it undermienes many traditional beliefs and religons.  It will give us a short-term burst of knowledge but some unrest for a time.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_2_0xH5C1_Name</Label>
    <String>Decline the Offer.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Choice_2_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We decline the offer, choosing to let our population remain blissfully ignorant.</String>
  </StringTable>
  
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_IconianHistoryShare_Diplomatic_0xH5C1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Your civilization is provincial</String>
  </StringTable>

  <StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_0xJ6D2_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Agreement Proposal</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} have approached governor {LEADERNAME} of {PLANETNAME} with a lucrative trade agreement. This deal promises to greatly elevate the planet's economy, but locals have voiced their concerns over the influx of alien visitors it might bring.[BR][BR]The potential for cultural enrichment is immense, yet so is the potential for tension.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_1_0xJ6D2_Name</Label>
    <String>Accept the Trade Agreement.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_1_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We embrace the trade deal, anticipating the economic boom it will bring. However, we must also be prepared for potential cultural clashes due to the new alien visitors and their various smells.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_2_0xJ6D2_Name</Label>
    <String>Nope. No thanks.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Choice_2_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Choosing the wishes of the local population, we decline the trade deal, potentially souring relations with the {PLAYERFACTION:1}.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_AlienTradeAgreement_Diplomatic_0xJ6D2_Dec</Label>
    <String>You refused our trade offer.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_Name</Label>
        <String>Coordinated Travel</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes traveling in our area of influence cost essentially nothing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the advancement of Coordinated Travel, our fleets and convoys can move in perfect harmony. This technology uses advanced algorithms and real-time data streams to ensure our fleets can move through friendly space at speeds previously thought impossible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_Name</Label>
        <String>Glorious Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provides ultimate understanding of the Precursors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our pursuit for immortality is not limited to individuals but extends to our civilization's achievements and wisdom. The Glorious Legacy technology establishes advanced archiving, conservation, and broadcast methods to ensure our culture, discoveries, and stories resonate through the cosmos, forever untouched by time's decay.[BR][BR]This manifests in the non-trivial fact that we have had to reconcile our own beliefs and faiths with the fact that we know, for a fact there there was a Precursor civilization that was created by a set of beings called the Mithrilar.  These beings split into the Arnor and Dread Lords who fought each other before most species in this galaxy even evolved.  This perfect understanding allows us to intuitively use their works as if they were our own.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_Name</Label>
        <String>Call of Utopia</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks an executive order that massively increases influence on the target world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_Dec</Label>
        <String>Through the Call of Utopia, our civilization embarks on a journey to actualize a society where harmony, prosperity, and happiness reign supreme. Advanced sociological models, infrastructure blueprints, and community engagement strategies lay the groundwork for turning our utopian dream into a tangible reality. [BR][BR]This culminates through an executive order that, when used, drastically increases the influence of its target core world which will, if not immediately, in short order bring other civilizations into our light.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tech_Sanctuary_Name</Label>
        <String>Consensus Maker</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterSanctuaryTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Our diplomatic skills will increase every month.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterSanctuaryTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>To know us will be to love us. The Sanctuary technology focuses on building zones of unparalleled safety, both in terms of defense and societal well-being. Through advanced shielding, rapid-response systems, and a culture of care, these sanctuaries ensure that in times of crisis, our people have an unwavering beacon to turn to.[BR][BR]Every month our diplomatic ability will increase until every civilization cannot help but love us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IndividualDivinity_Name</Label>
        <String>Individual Divinity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ndividualDivinity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Empowering citizens to ascend to godhood.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IndividualDivinity_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our citizens stats will increase by 0.1 per month forever. Unlocking the latent potential within every individual, the Individual Divinity technology sets our citizens on a path of continuous evolution and self-improvement. Through spiritual, mental, and physical enhancement protocols, our people grow stronger, wiser, and more attuned to the cosmos each passing day, edging ever closer to a state of divine existence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    

<StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Name_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>Cultural Exchange Festival</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Dec_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>We have a proposal for the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:0}. In the interest of peace we would like to hold a Cultural Exchange Festival. The are art, music, and traditions from both civilizations might promote understanding and unity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Choice1_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>Agree to the Festival</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Choice1_Dec_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>We have decided to promote the event, expecting an influx of tourists and a boost in cultural appreciation. However, we will have to spend some control to manage the diverse crowd.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Choice2_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>Decline the Proposal</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Choice2_Dec_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>We have decided against the cultural festival. We prioritize our internal peace and stability. This decision, however, may not sit well with the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CultureExchange_Diplomatic_0X9A7BC</Label>
        <String>You declined our festival proposal</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_0x49B2_Name</Label>
        <String>The Pilgrimage Proposal</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_0x49B2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our people are very spiritual. There are areas within your sphere of influence that our people believe connect them to the ancient Mithilar. Would you allow them to pass through your territory? We would appreciate it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_0x49B2_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Allow the Pilgrimage.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_0x49B2_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Recognizing the spiritual significance and respecting their traditions, we have granted them permission for the pilgrimage. It will cost some control to ensure their safety.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_0x49B2_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>No. I don't think so.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_0x49B2_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>The last thing we need are a bunch of alien spies traveling through our space.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_GoodDiplomaticReason_0x49B2</Label>
        <String>Grateful for Pilgrimage Approval</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CivPilgrimage_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x49B2</Label>
        <String>Disappointed by Pilgrimage Denial</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_0x15E9_Name</Label>
        <String>The Ghastly Request</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_0x15E9_Dec</Label>
        <String>We, the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}, are approaching a significant period in our lifecycle &#8212; our sacred mating ritual.[BR][BR]For the ritual's success, we require sentients to feast upon. We would like you to provide these sentients. You can gather them from your prisons if that helps you justify it. But its importance to our kind cannot be overstated. Will you offer this gesture of goodwill?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_0x15E9_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Fine. Round up some criminals to feed to them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_0x15E9_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>The choice will surely cause unrest among our people. But it will improve relations at least. For now.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_0x15E9_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Absolutely not.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_0x15E9_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>They will be unhappy with this choice but our people will still respect you just as little tomorrow..</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0x15E9</Label>
        <String>You supported our flesh festival</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_FeastProposal_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x15E9</Label>
        <String>You ruined our festival</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_0x23F4_Name</Label>
        <String>The Bloody Proposal</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_0x23F4_Dec</Label>
        <String>We, the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}, have a long-standing tradition of games that test the true capabilities of one's physique and mental prowess. For warm up, your weak species would be well advised to provide some specimens for our warriors to practice on.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_0x23F4_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Only if I get to watch.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_0x23F4_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our people will likely be horrified by this decision, but it may prevent further conflict with the cruel {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_0x23F4_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Refuse their vile proposal</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_0x23F4_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>While our people will be relieved, this might further sour our relations with them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0x23F4</Label>
        <String>You know your place</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SportRequest_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x23F4</Label>
        <String>You have too much spine</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_0x3C4D_Name</Label>
        <String>Deepwater Festival</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_0x3C4D_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} cordially invites your people to join our Deepwater Festival, a celebration of our amphibious heritage. We request some of your best swimmers to experience the depth of our oceans. It's a unique, once-in-a-lifetime opportunity. But, we must admit, it comes with some risks. [BR][BR]Will you accept?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_0x3C4D_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>We will send volunteers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_0x3C4D_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's an opportunity for cultural exchange but also some risk if any of our swimmers die.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_0x3C4D_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>This is too dangerous for us to participate in.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_0x3C4D_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Even though we have some people who would jump at the chance to participate, the scandal if something went wrong would be a disaster.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0x3C4D</Label>
        <String>You are good swimmers</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_SubmersionFestival_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x3C4D</Label>
        <String>You are cowardly</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_0x4F5A_Name</Label>
        <String>Deep Water</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_0x4F5A_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our people, the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}, have a profound connection to water. We wish to explore the depths of your oceans, study its inhabitants, and understand its mysteries.[BR][BR]We assure you, our intentions are purely scientific. Would you permit us?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_0x4F5A_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>This sounds great.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_0x4F5A_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>It's a step towards interstellar cooperation, but our coastal communities are particularly wary.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_0x4F5A_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>No. Our worlds are not open for this.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_0x4F5A_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We value our autonomy and the sentiments of our people. The seas remain ours alone.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0x4F5A</Label>
        <String>You granted us ocean access</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_OceanExploration_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x4F5A</Label>
        <String>You denied us your oceans</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_0x5A1B_Name</Label>
        <String>The Way</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_0x5A1B_Dec</Label>
        <String>As you know the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}, have been enlightened by The Way. We wish to bring you salvation by setting up shrines on your planets, teaching your people of our sacred beliefs. Embrace The Way and allow us to guide you to the true path. Do you accept?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_0x5A1B_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Very well. Set up your shrines.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_0x5A1B_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>This will reduce our cultural influence growth for a time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_0x5A1B_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Our people are not interested.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_0x5A1B_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>They may not take this rejection lightly, but our influence remains undiminished.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0x5A1B</Label>
        <String>You embraced The Way</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DevoutShrines_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x5A1B</Label>
        <String>You rejected The Way</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_0x8C3D_Name</Label>
        <String>Dream Spies</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_0x8C3D_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've been watching you. We know your people have been infiltrating the dreams of the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}. We're not crazy. [BR][BR]We demand 10 units of Antimatter to build a device to shield our minds from your prying.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_0x8C3D_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>You can have the Antimatter but I doubt it will help.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_0x8C3D_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>While the claims are baseless, this might be the way to keep the peace.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_0x8C3D_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>If you have to say you're not crazy...</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_0x8C3D_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>They might be furious, but we won't be bullied based on delusions.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0x8C3D</Label>
        <String>You're not spying on our dreams</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_DreamSpyingAccusation_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0x8C3D</Label>
        <String>You are spying on our dreams</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_0xA12F_Name</Label>
        <String>Weapons of War</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_0xA12F_Dec</Label>
        <String>We, the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}, have come across some... extra military hardware. We thought you might be interested. These arms will significantly bolster your weapons capabilities. However, remember, such deals remain between us. Do we have an agreement?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_0xA12F_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Better weapons on our ships? Yes. Yes please.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_0xA12F_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>These weapons will help but they will lower our overall diplomatic ability.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_0xA12F_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>We must pass on this.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_0xA12F_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We are not in the habit of installing strange weapons from foreign governments.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_PositiveDiplomaticReason_0xA12F</Label>
        <String>You like our weapons</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_WarProfiteerDeal_NegativeDiplomaticReason_0xA12F</Label>
        <String>You are dumb</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TraderDeal_0xC45D_Name</Label>
        <String>Special Offer</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TraderDeal_0xC45D_Dec</Label>
        <String>We, the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1}, have a limited time offer for you. A rare Harmony Crystal, known to enhance the wellbeing and productivity of colonies or something. All we ask for in return is a modest sum. </String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TraderDeal_0xC45D_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Take the deal</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TraderDeal_0xC45D_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>We can use this.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TraderDeal_0xC45D_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>We can't afford it right now.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_TraderDeal_0xC45D_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Perhaps another time, when our coffers are more abundant.</String>
    </StringTable>
    

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PersuasionOffer_0xC45E_Name</Label>
        <String>Persuasion Workshop</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PersuasionOffer_0xC45E_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our traders have honed the art of persuasion through countless dealings across the galaxy. For a fee we'd be willing to share some of these trade secrets with you. This knowledge could greatly benefit your future negotiations. Interested?</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PersuasionOffer_0xC45E_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Invest in the workshop</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PersuasionOffer_0xC45E_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>The art of persuasion is a valuable skill. We accept. We can use persuassion when trading to get better deals.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PersuasionOffer_0xC45E_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>Decline the offer</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_PersuasionOffer_0xC45E_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>We will rely on our own methods of negotiation.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Name</Label>
        <String>Crystal Resonance</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Dec</Label>
        <String>The {PLAYERFACTION:1} have come to you with a proposal. We can detect harmonics that are beyond your imagination. We are willing to share knowledge on how to detect these harmonics which should aid your science but in return we want access to some of your worlds that have unique crystalline formations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Choice1_Name</Label>
        <String>Grant access.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Choice1_Dec</Label>
        <String>The ancient knowledge of the universe is invaluable. We accept.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Choice2_Name</Label>
        <String>No thank you.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Choice2_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our resources are for our own use. We cannot grant access. This may insult them.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_CrystalResonance_0xC45F_Diplomacy</Label>
        <String>You chose...poorly</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    


<StringTable>
		<Label>STATNAME_FactionCulturalFactor</Label>
		<String>[ICON=Stat_Culture_Icon] Culture Points</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>STATNAME_InfluencePower</Label>
		<String>[ICON=Stat_Influence_Icon] Influence</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>STATNAME_FactionMilitaryPotentialFactor</Label>
		<String>[ICON=Stat_Manufacturing_Icon] Manufacturing</String>
	</StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ReturnOfKorath_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Return of the Korath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ReturnOfKorath_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>2317, among the upheaval, the Korath Clan returns. The Korath Clan was legendary in the Drengin Empire as shock troops. They were often at the front of any attack and were renowned for their ferocity and viciousness. The Korath Clan believed that all life was inferior to the Drengin and unworthy of existence. They believed anything weak should be eradicated from the universe, deviating sharply from the Drengin Empire's tendency to enthrall groups they saw as lesser. The strife caused by these philosophical differences caused the Korath Clan to break from the Empire. The Korath Clan became even more noteworthy after their contact with the Dread Lords left them physically altered. The Korath Clan believes they are the true Drengin and seek to drive all others to extinction, even the Empire they once served.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_ReturnOfKorath_Overall</Label>
        <String>Achieve a Conquest Victory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_ReturnOfKorath_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>The only group worthy of survival is the Korath Clan, and the Korath is more than prepared to prove it. The only course is destruction. Achieve a [HS=HS_ConquestVictory]Conquest Victory[/HS] by driving all other major civilizations to extinction in the name of the Korath Clan.</String>
    </StringTable>


</StringTableList>