<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<FlavorTextDefs
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the Flavor Text Editor -->
    <!-- FlavorText.xml -->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>FIRST_CONTACT_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Vuresef, {PLAYERFACTION:2}. Tipot  {PLAYERFACTION:1}'s orisih beha rinin holares. Erasuto ki nakeduc menurit!
          (You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>1</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A smooth-skinned biped stares back at us from the  view screen. Wearing some kind of lightly ceremonial garb, it jabbers a short series of unintelligible grunting sounds. Getting no response from us, it gestures at someone off screen in a manner which suggests annoyance. They can't seem to understand us either.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_FESTRON</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our screen flickers for a minute before the video emerges, filled with an image of a massive insectoid creature. [BR][BR]Motionless at first, its only a slight waver of its vicious pincers which indicate the creature is alive as it glares back at us. In the background, more of its kind move around, clicking and chittering at each other. A language of some kind, but it's impossible to determine what they're saying.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_NAVIGATORS</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A curious creature stares back at us from the screen. Ten or twelve legged, in the manner of a segmented insect, the creature also appears to have a lightly armored exoskeleton.[BR][BR]From its long, dexterous tongue, a series of subtle hissing noises emerges. It seems to be trying to communicate with us, but it's of no use.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MIMOT</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A small, furry creature appears on screen. With its soft fur and enormous eyes, the being looks cute, and possibly delicious. Its eyes widen even further, perhaps realizing what we're thinking.[BR][BR]Eventually it opens its small, delicate mouth and emits a series of mewling noises. A speech of sorts, though who knows what it means. Something adorable, no doubt.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_XELOXI</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A green skinned biped appears on screen, wearing elaborate clothes and a headdress. Likely a female, if this species has the same notion of genders as we do, which may be a dangerous guess.[BR][BR]  The creature utters something in their native tongue, unintelligible, yet somehow very, very compelling.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ARCEAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A ferocious looking humanoid fills the screen, glaring at you from behind green eyes. You can feel the contempt dripping from him, though he says nothing.[BR][BR]It murmurs something, almost below the range of hearing, and flicker of strange text crosses the screen, as the alien's communications systems try and fail to interface with ours. There will be no talking with this creature today.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRENGIN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A cruel looking green skinned biped appears, glaring at us. Wearing armor of some kind, and baring its teeth, it gives every impression that it is a warrior, or at least wishes to be perceived as one.[BR][BR]It barks something angrily at the screen, and you wonder for a moment if it's truly a bad thing we can't understand what its saying.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A slender, blue skinned biped appears, delicate in feature and manner. It speaks calmly at us in a strange yet somehow noble speech.[BR][BR]Seeing no recognition in our response, it nods its head slowly, having realized the communication barrier that exists. If anything, it seems disappointed in us.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_YOR</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A metallic creature appears on screen, unblinking red sensors staring back at us. The sensors iris open a bit, before narrowing, the creature studying us.[BR][BR]Sound emerges from it, a clash of discordant sounds, almost as if its trying different languages on us to see if we understand anything. We don't.  The sensors narrow even further. There's no point communicating with this being now.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TORIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A small biped appears on screen, staring at us. It has a wide, flat skull, and large eyes which seem to avoid making eye contact with us. Perhaps a side effect of the communication system.[BR][BR]It murmurs at us for a time in a language devoid of sharp consonant sounds, but no meaning really comes through. We'll have to converse with this strange creature another time.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MANTI</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A being in much the same shape as a crustacean wobbles cheerfully on our view screen, a jumble of eyes and legs. A gentle shimmer suggests the creature - and its kin working behind him - are underwater at the moment.[BR][BR]The creature clicks and snaps its claws in our direction, no doubt trying to say something. Hard to say what it could be at this point.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_KRYNN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A tall bipedal alien appears on screen with a distinct, ridged skull. The being has six eyes, spread widely across its face, which all pivot to look at us.[BR][BR]Has it seen our kind before, or are we as much of a mystery to them as they are to us?  It says something, quick and repetitive, almost a chant. A ritual greeting perhaps? But there's no making sense of it.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>An alien appears on the  view screen, likely bipedal, with a long, narrow skull and slender tendrils appearing from the mouth area.[BR][BR]Small eyes towards the top of the skull narrow as it says something. The tone of the language suggests a question, though we can't understand it. The alien sways gently, sensing the futility of further communication.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRATH</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A strange bipedal alien appears on screen, with lizard-like, even draconid qualities. The crested ridges above its eyes flex, as it leans in to study us from its perch in an ornate looking room.[BR][BR]A deep growling voice emerges from somewhere deep within it, the mouth barely moving. A pleasant greeting or dire threat, we can't be sure.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_IRIDIUM</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A gray skinned hominoid alien peers back at us from the  view screen. The alien has four eyes, and a thin smile which gives the impression of friendliness, though that may be a dangerous assumption.[BR][BR]Behind the creature, a clean, even sterile looking spaceship can be seen. Some words are exchanged, but nothing can be understood between you and them. The thin smile remains though. All in good time, it would seem.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A tall hominoid alien appraises us from the  view screen. Although bipedal, the segmented section of its neck suggests perhaps an annelid biology.[BR][BR]Whatever its origin, the being tries a few words in its native tongue, a strange combination of rumbles and rhythmic vibrations, though nothing can be understood from it. The alien seems bemused by our speech as well.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_BARATAK</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A strange plantlike creature appears on screen. Bark like skin covers its trunk and surprisingly humanoid looking face, before giving way to sleek, well maintained foliage further up.[BR][BR]In the background, a decidedly organic, plant-like ship can be seen. The creature emits a series of long, creaking groans, evidently trying to communicate with us. No sense can be made of it, for now.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A glimmering creature appears on the screen, its body formed of blue crystal with wide intelligent eyes. As beautiful as it is, your awe at seeing it is not reflected in its face, which instead looks sympathetic or disgusted.[BR][BR]There is a brief pause as the creature considers you and you almost hear voices, like memories echoing distantly in your mind. But you cannot tell what they say, or if they are coming from the alien. Disappointed the creature hums softly in almost musical tones. It is beautiful, but equally indecipherable. [BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MOTH</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The incoming message comes with the visage of a slender alien covered naturally in fuzz and chitin. Large compound eyes blink quickly and frequently.[BR][BR]A series of melodic hissing clicks comes from the being. After a short pause, another series of sounds come through the speakers, coupled with soft hand motions. Without a means to decipher the message, proper communication is unachievable.[BR][BR](You need to research Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
</FlavorTextDefs>