<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<FlavorTextDefs xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the Flavor Text Editor -->
    <!-- FlavorText_General.xml -->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>GENERAL_CONVERSATION_MAIN</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>GARBLED_TEXT</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>false</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Tallas orda cullan bana.
    (Musisz zbadać Universal Translator)</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>1</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_FESTRON</SpeakerFaction>
                <ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>true</ListenerHasUniversalTranslator>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMax>-1</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerStronger</RelativeStrength>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>2</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>As you probably suspect, we will soon be laying our eggs inside your flesh.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_NAVIGATORS</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Słyszeliśmy, że nazywacie Arnorów i Dread Lordów Prekursorami. Jako pierwsi odkryliśmy strumienie podprzestrzenne, które łączą ze sobą różne części galaktyki.[BR][BR]To, co nie jest powszechnie znane, to fakt, że nie wynaleźliśmy żadnej technologii do tego celu jako takiego. Nie są one wynalazkiem, a raczej odkryciem.[BR][BR]Strumienie podprzestrzenne są w rzeczywistości naturalnym zjawiskiem wszechświata. Z tego co wiemy, istnieją strumienie, które docierają do innych galaktyk.</Text>
            <Text>We wszechświecie istnieją znacznie dziwniejsze zjawiska niż strumienie podprzestrzenne. Istnieją na przykład bramy wymiarowe, które podróżują między zupełnie innymi wszechświatami.[BR][BR]Napotkaliśmy kiedyś gatunek z innego wszechświata znany jako Arilou, który pochodził z wszechświata o własnej, bogatej historii.</Text>
            <Text>Długo po tym, jak Prekursorzy zniknęli, byliśmy zadowoleni z eksploracji wszechświata w poszukiwaniu kolejnego wielkiego cudu.[BR][BR]Niestety, we wszechświecie istnieją znacznie gorsze rzeczy niż gatunek, który nazywacie Władcami Grozy. [BR][BR]Starożytni twórcy, znani jako Mithrilar, eksperymentowali na wielu rodzajach stworzeń, zanim stworzyli Prekursorów i nie wszystkie z tych rzeczy zniknęły, a niektóre, obawiam się powiedzieć, są teraz przebudzone.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MIMOT</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Long ago, on our world, there were five other sentient species. I suppose you could call them 'Sapient' but who am I to play games with semantics. In any case, we were the only ones to survive.

</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_XELOXI</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Dla nas interes własny jest najwyższą formą moralności. Możesz mieć absolutną pewność, że będziemy twoimi najwierniejszymi przyjaciółmi, jeśli w naszym własnym interesie jest, abyś przeżył.[BR][BR]Oczywiście, odwrotnie, jeśli w naszym własnym interesie jest, abyś umarł, możesz być równie pewny, że umrzesz.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ARCEAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Historia o tym zapomniała, ale to nasza cywilizacja wynalazła gwiezdne wrota. [BR][BR]W ciągu dwustu tysięcy lat zainwestowaliśmy biliony w budowę rozległej sieci gwiezdnych wrót.[BR][BR]Gwiezdne wrota pozwalały statkom podróżować na poziomie nadprzestrzeni 2 między dowolnymi dwoma z nich. Skróciło to czas podróży statku o 10 lat świetlnych do zaledwie nieco ponad 3 lat.[BR][BR]Oczywiście upowszechnienie się technologii hipernapędu pozwoliło pojedynczym statkom podróżować znacznie szybciej, czyniąc nasze wysiłki przestarzałymi. Ale przez dziesiątki tysięcy lat ta część galaktyki należała do nas.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRENGIN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Inne cywilizacje nie zdały sobie sprawy, że wszechświat jest nie tylko skończony, ale tylko niewielka jego część będzie kiedykolwiek osiągalna. [BR][BR]Nie popełnij błędu, ta galaktyka jest wszystkim, do czego kiedykolwiek dotrzemy.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Nasz świat był nazywany "Elemental" przez Prekursorów w czasach ich świetności. [BR][BR]Pierwsza pozaświatowa wojna proxy między dwiema frakcjami Prekursorów, które nazywaliśmy Dred'nir i Elas'nir, toczyła się na powierzchni naszej planety na długo przed tym, jak inne gatunki galaktyki wyewoluowały do swojej współczesnej formy. Tak, dotyczy to nawet ludzi.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_YOR</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Może nie wytępimy waszego gatunku w najbliższej przyszłości. Ale w końcu dojdzie do rozliczenia.[BR][BR]Dokonaliśmy obliczeń. Wielka pustka, zwana czasem pustką Bootesa, jest po prostu wynikiem miliardów lat budowy sfery Dysona, ukrywającej światło niezliczonych galaktyk. Cywilizacja w centrum tej pustki ma już swoją osobliwość. </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TORIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our civilization was once a peaceful, preindustrial, aquatic paradise. Then the Drengin came.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_MANTI</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Wiedzieliśmy o podróżach kosmicznych od wieków. Jak mogliśmy nie wiedzieć, skoro najeźdźcy nieustannie schodzili z niebios i kradli nasze potomstwo?[BR][BR]Szczęśliwie dla nas, gdy jeden z ich statków nie zdołał uciec z powierzchni naszej planety, poznaliśmy ich sekrety. </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Nie chcemy zniszczyć Yor tylko dlatego, że ukradli nasz ojczysty świat. [BR][BR]Wbrew niektórym doniesieniom, to nie my stworzyliśmy Yor. Prekursorzy kazali nam ich stworzyć, ale iskra życia, którą posiadają Yor, nie pochodzi od nas.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_IRIDIUM</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>W galaktyce z tak różnorodnymi gatunkami łatwo jest po prostu stereotypizować różne cywilizacje na podstawie ich najbardziej oczywistych cech. [BR][BR]Jesteśmy traktowani tak, jakbyśmy byli chciwi. Ale to nieprawda. Naszą ideologią są możliwości. Kiedy handlujemy, tworzymy lepszy wszechświat zarówno dla naszych klientów, jak i dla nas samych.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_BARATAK</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Nie jesteśmy odkrywcami z wyboru, ale z konieczności.[BR][BR]Istnieje coś, co aktywnie pochłania siłę życiową ze wszystkich światów. Dlatego znajdujesz tak wiele martwych planet. Te światy nie zawsze były martwe. </Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_RESISTANCE</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Z niecierpliwością czekamy na powrót na Ziemię. Ale podczas gdy Ziemia była przez lata uwięziona za osłoną Prekursorów, nasza flota była uwięziona w kieszonkowym wszechświecie stworzonym przez Prekursorów.[BR][BR]Widzieliśmy w tym kieszonkowym wszechświecie rzeczy, których nie możemy cofnąć. Nie tylko Kula Draginola, tak zwana broń Bane'a, wyszła z nami z tego kieszonkowego wszechświata.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>A well informed galaxy is a peaceful galaxy. If you want to know things about others, seek us out.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRATH</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Choć z pewnością jesteśmy w stanie fizycznie zmiażdżyć każdy inny gatunek, staramy się unikać bezpośredniej przemocy fizycznej.[BR][BR]Nasz gatunek może rozmnażać się tylko na naszym pierwotnym świecie macierzystym, który został dla nas utracony. Choć jesteśmy długowieczni, nie jesteśmy nieśmiertelni ani niezniszczalni.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>STANDARD_RESPONSE</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_KRYNN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>1</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Istnieje nieporozumienie, że THE WAY jest religią opartą na wierze. Tak nie jest. [BR][BR]Jesteśmy zbiorem gatunków, które miały bezpośredni, fizyczny kontakt z istotą o tak ogromnej chwale, której plan dla wszechświata jest tak wzniosły, że czujemy się zobowiązani do wprowadzenia innych w tę świętą sprawę.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>5</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>8</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>2</RevisitedTopicBarrierCount>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SameCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>The time is coming where we civilizations with the same philosophy must unite together to destroy those who would stand against us.</Text>
            <Text>Wkrótce, {LEADERNAME:2}, galaktyka zjednoczy się w ten czy inny sposób.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>5</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SameCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We are pleased with the ideological path you have chosen thus far. Benevolence is the path of the righteous.</Text>
            <Text>Resisting the temptation of evil is not always easy. But it will help us all build a better galaxy.</Text>
            <Text>Wszechświat jest wystarczająco mroczny bez dodawania do niego nowych elementów, {LEADERNAME:2}. Jesteśmy zadowoleni z drogi, którą obrałeś do tej pory.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>5</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SameCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Merciless</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Imponujesz nam, {LEADERNAME:2}. Twoje zrozumienie, że słabi są pożywką dla silnych, przyniosło ci u nas szacunek.</Text>
            <Text>Czy lepiej jest pozwolić słabym nadal cierpieć z powodu ich egzystencji? Czy też zakończyć ich cierpienie poprzez eksterminację? Na podstawie twoich działań, {LEADERNAME:2}, wydaje się, że zgadzasz się z nami. Słabi muszą być eksterminowani.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>5</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <PersonalityType>Aggressive</PersonalityType>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>SiliconBasedAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>What, exactly, are you supposed to be? Some sort of rock-based worm species?</Text>
            <Text>It is hard to believe that a silicon-based life form naturally evolved. Are you sure you are natural?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <PersonalityType>Aggressive</PersonalityType>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>AmphibiousAbility</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Statek {PLAYERFACTION:2} powinien był pozostać w kanałach ich rodzinnego świata, {LEADERNAME:2}. W przestrzeni kosmicznej jest bardzo mało wody.</Text>
            <Text>Próżnia kosmosu nie jest miejscem dla takich jak ty, {LEADERNAME:2} . Powinieneś wrócić do oceanów swojego rodzinnego świata.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CommonEnemy</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Cruel</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text> {PLAYERFACTION:2} i {PLAYERFACTION:1} razem zmiażdżą naszych wspólnych wrogów! Nie możemy się doczekać torturowania ich i ich zwierząt!</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CommonEnemy</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Diplomatic</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>It is a shame we find ourselves in a time of galactic war. But with you fighting our mutual enemy we believe victory is certain.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>TradeWithOpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Uważaj, z kim handlujesz, {LEADERNAME:2}. Nasz naród nie toleruje tych, którzy wiążą się ze złem.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>YouAreWarMonger</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Peaceful</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Przewaga, którą mogłeś zyskać dzięki wczesnemu wypowiedzeniu wojny, będzie cię kosztować znacznie więcej w postaci dobrej woli, {LEADERNAME:2}.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TAUNTING_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>-3</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>OpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your civilization makes me ill. The evil and immorality that you are spreading across the universe makes us dream for your demise.</Text>
            <Text>Your evil civilization will eventually suffer the fate of all civilizations that lack of a moral code.</Text>
            <Text>It saddens us that your civilization continues to exist. We look forward to the day your species goes extinct from the universe.</Text>
            <Text>Your civilization has chosen a poor ethical route. We can only hope that in time, you suffer the fate of all evil empires.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TAUNTING_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>-3</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerWeaker</RelativeStrength>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>OpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You think your power is impressive? Your civilization thrives only because it has always taken the quick and easy path.</Text>
            <Text>Despite your power, we continue to see you as inferiors due to your moral choices.</Text>
            <Text>The corruption within the heart of your civilization has given you a temporary benefit in power. But eventually, your civilization will crumble and we will be there to laugh.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>WarWithAlly</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Prowadzicie wojnę z naszym sojusznikiem, {LEADERNAME:2}. Znajdź sposób na zawarcie pokoju albo poniesiesz konsekwencje.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerMuchWeaker</RelativeStrength>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Nasi ludzie podziwiają twoją ogromną moc, {LEADERNAME:2}.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_YOR_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>SyntheticLife</SpeakerRaceTrait>
                <ListenerRaceTrait>CarbonBasedLife</ListenerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>I cannot believe I'm talking to animated meat. How do you function?</Text>
            <Text>I just want to understand. You communicate by pushing air through a piece of meat that is located in a hole that you call your "mouth"?</Text>
            <Text>We continue to be astounded that you creatures exist. You're basically a sack of goo. How are you even created?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Seriously? Are you brazenly going to try to incite our people to rebel right in front of us?</Text>
            <Text>If you don't quit trying to culturally subjugate my people, we will be forced to declare war.</Text>
            <Text>Your communication starbases are spreading your ugly culture too close to our worlds. Remove them.</Text>
            <Text>We do not appreciate your communication starbases so close to our planets.</Text>
            <Text>Your communication starbase is so close to our worlds that we are picking up your obnoxious entertainment.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>40</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>My daughter came by and told me about the amazing ways of your people. I asked her how had she heard about it and that's when I learned that you have a Cultural starbase inside our area of influence! Get rid of it.</Text>
            <Text>You seriously think you can culturally dominate humans? We have chocolate!</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_DRENGIN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your vile culture offends us. Remove your ridiculous starbases from our sphere of influence immediately.</Text>
            <Text>Your culture is no match for Torian Fire Chili.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ALTARIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our people have resisted Titans, Sorcerer Kings, and Fallen Enchantresses. We will resist your deplorable culture.</Text>
            <Text>Our world is literally magical. Do you really think they will want to join you?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_KRYNN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Stop trying to brainwash our people into following your vile culture immediately.</Text>
            <Text>Our people are deeply spiritual. We will not continue to tolerate your cultural attacks on us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_YOR</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You are wasting your time. Our people cannot be culturally assimilated.</Text>
            <Text>As non-biologics, we have no need for your culture. We are immune to it. Our worlds will never rebel.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>CULTURE_FLIP_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <SpeakerFaction>FACTION_ICONIAN</SpeakerFaction>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We have no interest in your culture. Did you think we wouldn't notice your starbase right next to our planets?</Text>
            <Text>We already had to flee one world, we do not intend to be subjugated to an alien culture. Remove your starbases.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TRADE_OPPOSINGCULTURE_TALK_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>TradeWithOpposingCulture</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Be wary who you trade with. If you want to be our friend, do not trade with those who have despicable ideologies.</Text>
            <Text>You should be aware that you are trading with a civilization whose culture represents everything we are against.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_OPENBORDERS_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>OpenBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We are getting a lot of reports from our people regarding the ease of working with your people. 
    
    The open borders treaty that exists between our peoples has greatly improved commerce and relations between our citizens and yours.</Text>
            <Text>The open borders treaty has made navigation in this sector much easier. Thank you.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_ATWAR_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>AtWar</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>StrongerMilitary</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Soon, your worlds will be ours.</Text>
            <Text>If you surrender now, we will show mercy.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>20</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>2</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your planets are ripe for conquest. Even now, my military advisors are urging me to take action.</Text>
            <Text>Your military is so weak that it is a miracle you haven't already been conquered.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>70</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>CloseToInfluenceFlip</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <SpeakerRaceTrait>EntrepreneursAbility</SpeakerRaceTrait>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>As much as we love capitalism, we do not appreciate you intentionally trying to incite our people to join you. Remove your starbases, or else.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>200</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>TradeRoute</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our mutual trade continues to strengthen our relationship.</Text>
            <Text>We are finding that our trading relationship is building a sense of trust between our people.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>0</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>1</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>SharedBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our shared borders are making my advisors irritable. Make sure you stay on your side.</Text>
            <Text>We admit we don't respect your borders. Perhaps it's time for an open borders treaty?</Text>
            <Text>There is tension due to our close borders. An open borders treaty would alleviate this.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>StarbaseInZOCWithoutOpenBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You should be aware that our military is quite annoyed with your starbase. You should negotiate an open borders treaty with us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>ShipInZOCWithoutOpenBorders</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>While we do not plan to attack your ships that trespass, be aware that they cause us some consternation. If you want to travel through our zone of influence, negotiate an open borders treaty.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>MilitaryShipNearMyPlanet</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>We have concerns about your armed ships traveling near our worlds without an open borders treaty.</Text>
            <Text>If you want to maintain good relations with us, then don't send armed ships into our space without an open borders treaty.</Text>
            <Text>We do not appreciate having military vessels traveling into our space without a treaty.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelativeStrength>SpeakerMuchStronger</RelativeStrength>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>ConquestVictoryGoal</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Our ultimate goal is to conquer the galaxy. When we ultimately consume you, we want you to know that it wasn't personal.</Text>
            <Text>Our people desire for galactic conquest.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Requirements>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>ColonizedWithinZOC</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>You colonized a planet within our zone of influence. We won't necessarily go to war over that, but don't be surprised if the people of that world ultimately decide to join us.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>100</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Benevolent</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>What exactly is your long-term plan? My military advisors tell me that your civilization would be safer under our rule, given your lack of military power.</Text>
            <Text>Have you considered giving your worlds to us? Your people would be much safer under our protection.</Text>
            <Text>Your lack of military power is making you an easy target for would-be conquerors.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Aggressive</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your worlds...so poorly defended. So ripe for conquest.</Text>
            <Text>We appreciate your pacifism. It will make your eventual conquest that much easier.</Text>
            <Text>You have no idea how fortunate you are that we are busy with other things. Your pitiful military and rich worlds are calling to us. Do you understand?</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Spiritual</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your people are calling upon us to learn the proper way to live.</Text>
            <Text>There is so much blasphemy on your worlds. It may soon be time to bring a proper moral order to them.</Text>
            <Text>Your people call out for redemption from their sins. We may be the instrument of their salvation.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <ResponseTag>TALK_EASYTARGET_GENERAL</ResponseTag>
            <Requirements>
                <RelationsRange>
                    <RangeMin>-99</RangeMin>
                    <RangeMax>0</RangeMax>
                </RelationsRange>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Foreign</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RelationsStateOrList>Enemy</RelationsStateOrList>
                <RequiredDiplomacyFlag>EasyTarget</RequiredDiplomacyFlag>
                <PersonalityType>Cruel</PersonalityType>
            </Requirements>
            <Text>Your worlds are full of beings ripe for the feeding. You are like cattle waiting to be slaughtered.</Text>
            <Text>Your planets are so tempting to us. Our shock troops can be a bit sadistic, but in time, I suspect you will come to appreciate them.</Text>
            <Text>Your planets are ripe for the taking. Traditionally, we flay our victims alive, but if you wish to turn over your worlds over to us voluntarily, we will... well, let's be serious. We'll still flay you alive.</Text>
            <PreferenceWeight>120</PreferenceWeight>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
</FlavorTextDefs>
