<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Artifacts_LABEL</Label>
        <String>Artifact</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Artifacts_DESC</Label>
        <String>Artifacts are powerful relics of lost civilizations. They are rare, but give valuable rewards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ArtifactAnomaly_Name</Label>
        <String>Artifact Anomaly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ArtifactAnomaly_Dec</Label>
        <String>We discovered an artifact in space and collected it with our survey ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_FinishProjectArtifact_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Builders</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_FinishProjectArtifact_Dec</Label>
        <String>A scan of this Precursor artifact doesn't reveal anything unusual, but when that scan is backed up to the nearest colonial database, strange things start happening. The physical structure of the artifact itself is a form of self-executing code, which seizes control of the colonial computer, and soon after the manufacturing sector. Thousands of tiny worker bots are produced which almost immediately complete the project currently in progress on the world. They then immediately shut down.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_FinishTechArtifact_Name</Label>
        <String>Unfortunate Genius</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_FinishTechArtifact_Dec</Label>
        <String>This is a sentient [HS=HS_ArtifactResearchCharge]Precursor Archive[/HS]. When our survey team member attempts to interface with it he claims to have boundless knowledge and shows all the signs of a remarkable and sudden increase in intelligence. Over the next several minutes, he details astounding technological breakthroughs until his head explodes.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetTerraformer_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetTerraformer_Dec</Label>
        <String>This capsule of [HS=HS_ArtifactPlanetClass]Chimeric Biomass[/HS] was fired into space in the hopes it would find a new world to revitalize. While it never found its original target, we can now repurpose it to improve the ecosystem of any world we choose.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetDimensionalSnare_Name</Label>
        <String>Dimensional Snare</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetDimensionalSnare_Dec</Label>
        <String>A strange device here has trapped a creature from another dimension. We can collect the [HS=HS_ArtifactCagedMonster]Dimensional Snare[/HS] and release the creature in an area of our choosing. Hard to say what the effects of that will be. Don't bet a lot of money on the creature being grateful to us, however.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetActivatedNanites_Name</Label>
        <String>Mnemonic Nanites</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetActivatedNanites_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've discovered a container filled with specialized Nanites capable of examining the structure of whatever material they are exposed to, determining its original design via an encyclopedic knowledge of engineering principles and semantic cues, and then rebuilding it back to like-new condition. The end result is we can use these [HS=HS_ArtifactFleetRepair]Mnemonic Nanites[/HS] to instantly repair any of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetBoostCoil_Name</Label>
        <String>Boost Coil</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetBoostCoil_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've discovered a high energy fuel source. Although it won't last long, it is enough to get a substantial increase in output from any ship's engine. We can use this [HS=HS_ArtifactFleetResetMoves]Boost Coil[/HS] to reset the moves of any of our fleets.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetBetatronCollider_Name</Label>
        <String>Betatron Collider</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetBetatronCollider_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've discovered a massive mine, with the markings of Precursor technology. We're fortunate it didn't trigger by our approach, though perhaps it was smart enough to detect we weren't a threat. We should be able to collect it and adapt its key component, a [HS=HS_ArtifactFleetDamage]Betatron Collider[/HS], into a device that can inflict heavy damage on an enemy fleet.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetBernalSphere_Name</Label>
        <String>Bernal Sphere</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetBernalSphere_Dec</Label>
        <String>This cargo module is a self contained habitat, complete with a synthetic workforce, idle for now but otherwise in perfect condition. We can use this [HS=HS_ArtifactPlanetPopulation]Bernal Sphere[/HS] to add a citizen to any of our worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetClimatePurifier_Name</Label>
        <String>Climate Purifier</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_GetClimatePurifier_Dec</Label>
        <String>This artifact was intended as part of a larger terraforming project that would convert a dead world into a paradise. Unfortunately only the first stage is working, a [HS=HS_ArtifactPlanetPollution]Climate Purifier[/HS] that will remove the most caustic elements from the planet's atmosphere.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Capsules_LABEL</Label>
        <String>Capsule</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Capsules_DESC</Label>
        <String>Capsules are lost goods never recovered, escape pods, jettisoned contraband, or simply misplaced wares. They have miscellaneous effects.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ContrabandTech_Name</Label>
        <String>Mysterious Capsule</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ContrabandTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>We discovered a mysterious capsule floating in space. After scanning it, we brought it onboard our ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostAndFound_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost and Found</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostAndFound_Dec</Label>
        <String>The scorched and pitted exterior of this abandoned cargo pod gives the impression that its rightful owners are unlikely to return for it in this life. It would be a shame to let the goods inside go to waste.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostCargo_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_LostCargo_Dec</Label>
        <String>The capsule contains military equipment, which is not normally found in civilian containers such as this. It seems likely it was dropped by smugglers before an inspection. Their loss is our gain, but we'll have to decide how to best make use of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_MysteriousHardware_Name</Label>
        <String>Mysterious Hardware</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_MysteriousHardware_Dec</Label>
        <String>The alien computational systems found in this capsule are so advanced that our survey team lack the vocabulary to describe all but their most rudimentary functions. But even those low-level capabilities would be enough to advance our technological studies by leaps and bounds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_DistressBeacon_Name</Label>
        <String>Distress Beacon</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_DistressBeacon_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've discovered a beacon sending a distress call for an emergency that happened millennia ago. Grave threat, galaxy's only hope, please, anyone, something something. Though we are perhaps a little late to respond to the emergency itself, the broadcast equipment in the beacon can certainly be put to use.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_Credits_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost and Found</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_Credits_Dec</Label>
        <String>The scorched and pitted exterior of this abandoned cargo pod gives the impression that its rightful owners are unlikely to return for it in this life. It would be a shame to let the goods inside go to waste.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_HeliosOre_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost and Found</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_HeliosOre_Dec</Label>
        <String>The scorched and pitted exterior of this abandoned cargo pod gives the impression that its rightful owners are unlikely to return for it in this life. It would be a shame to let the goods inside go to waste.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_Durantium_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_Durantium_Dec</Label>
        <String>The capsule contains military equipment, which is not normally found in civilian containers such as this. It seems likely it was dropped by smugglers before an inspection. Their loss is our gain, but we'll have to decide how to best make use of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_Promethion_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Cargo</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Quest_Promethion_Dec</Label>
        <String>The capsule contains military equipment, which is not normally found in civilian containers such as this. It seems likely it was dropped by smugglers before an inspection. Their loss is our gain, but we'll have to decide how to best make use of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ShipGraveyards_LABEL</Label>
        <String>Ship Graveyard</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ShipGraveyards_DESC</Label>
        <String>Ship graveyards are the remains of less fortunate interstellar travelers. They spawn assorted ship-related rewards.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ShipGraveyards_WARNING</Label>
        <String>[COLOR=Yellow]Lightly Defended[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GraveyardAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>Graveyard Anomaly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GraveyardAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>We explored the remains of an ancient stellar battle.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostScoutAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>Lost Probe</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostScoutAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>A small vessel drifts in deep space, all systems dead. Upon examination it appears to be an old scout from some long forgotten war. Its capabilities do not strain even the moderate intellects crewing our survey ship, and with a little work they believe it could be restored to service.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostSurveyAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>One Wormhole Too Many</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostSurveyAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>This survey ship is similar to Terran vessels, but our crew can't find an exact match anywhere in the database. The exterior shows signs of wormhole passage, but is otherwise in good shape. The interior however, needs substantial cleanup to deal with a mysterious green goo. There's no sign of the occupants, unless they're the green goo, which.... they might be actually. Still. Free ship.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostCutterAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>Toasted But Not Burned</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostCutterAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our survey crew finds a scorched but salvageable vessel amid the wreckage of a forgotten skirmish that appears to have occurred during the Dread Lord war. The bodies of the crew are found within, apparently executed. By their opponents, or perhaps their peers, it's hard to say - the Dread Lords cruelty was infamous. In any event, there are few obstacles preventing our crew from repairing the ship and pressing it into service.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostDefenderAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>Never Surrender</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostDefenderAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>A single ship orbits the remains of a planet destroyed by the terrible weaponry of the Dread Lord war. The crew, long dead, stand their posts - waiting for reinforcements that never came.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostGunboatAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>Cast the First Stone</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostGunboatAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>We've discovered an enormous Drengin battlecruiser floating in deep space, its hull perforated by thousands of small kinetic impacts. It is wholly unsalvageable. A Terran gunboat drifting nearby, however, is still in working order. The pilot's mummified remains still have their hands on the cannon controls, a smile frozen forever on their face.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostConstructorAnomoly_Name</Label>
        <String>Constructive Salvage</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Anomaly_LostConstructorAnomoly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Here lie the remains of a starbase, destroyed beyond any hope of salvage. Nearby however lies an abandoned constructor, never given a chance to fulfill its function. Minimal repairs will be needed to get it working again, to the point it can create a starbase of our own.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>SpaceJunk_LABEL</Label>
        <String>Space Junk</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>SpaceJunk_DESC</Label>
        <String>These make up the flotsam and jetsam of the galaxy. They are of rarely of great value, but provide unique opportunities.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BigCredits_Name</Label>
        <String>Debris Field</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>BigCredits_Dec</Label>
        <String>We discovered the remains of some sort of vessel. Our survey ship sets to the work of searching the debris for anything of value.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Wormholes_LABEL</Label>
        <String>Wormhole</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Wormholes_DESC</Label>
        <String>Wormholes are also rare, they simply transport any ship that enters them to a random location in the Galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>WormholeAnomaly_Name</Label>
        <String>Wormhole Ride</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>WormholeAnomaly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Your survey ship is caught in an unknown field and sucked through a hole in space itself. The crew may be annoyed at the unplanned detour, but the fact that they are somehow unharmed after traveling such a vast distance in the blink of an eye should keep morale at an acceptable level.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PrecursorAnomaly_LABEL</Label>
        <String>Precursor Anomaly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PrecursorAnomaly_DESC</Label>
        <String>This anomaly is a rare and powerful treasure, for anyone that can deal with its powerful guardians.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PrecursorAnomaly_WARNING</Label>
        <String>[COLOR=WarRed]Heavily Defended[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PrecursorProductionAnomaly_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Anomaly</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PrecursorProductionAnomaly_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our survey ship discovered precursor debris. Unfortunately, others discovered it first.</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>