<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_COLONY_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Colony</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_COLONY_DESC</Label>
        <String>With the establishment of this colony, we have taken our first steps into the galaxy. Our colonists represent everything which makes our people great, and with that they'll have every chance of thriving on this new alien world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_DURANTIUM_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Durantium Mine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_DURANTIUM_DESC</Label>
        <String>Our miners have returned with rocky debris laced with a telltale flicker of silvery-gold: Durantium. More dense and resilient than anything we've seen before, a steady supply will surely lead to new breakthroughs in ship design.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_ELERIUM_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Elerium Mine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_ELERIUM_DESC</Label>
        <String>An unnatural glow fills the mining ship as it draws in the first batch of the mysterious substance, Elerium. It is a material that seems to amplify high energy systems. It will be vital for high energy beam weapons and certain domestic applications.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_PROMETHION_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Promethion Mine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_PROMETHION_DESC</Label>
        <String>The first group of our probes have returned with canisters containing trace amounts of Promethion. Trace amounts by necessity, as the material is incredibly unstable. It will prove vital for our research efforts across a wide variety of applications.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_THULIUM_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Thulium Mine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_THULIUM_DESC</Label>
        <String>Thulium is not much to look at, surprisingly dull in texture and color. It's only in higher dimensions that it shows its true character, a stable form of Neutronium, a material of enormous density. This will be a vital component for any number of new systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_ANTIMATTER_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Antimatter Mine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_ANTIMATTER_DESC</Label>
        <String>The first of our antimatter mining probes (little more than an engine with a scoop) returns from the perimeter of a black hole with its precious cargo. The antimatter it has collected will soon be put to use developing advanced weapon and power generation systems.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_TRADE_ROUTE_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Trade Route</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_TRADE_ROUTE_DESC</Label>
        <String>With minimal ceremony, the first of your trading frigates pushes away from its slip. When it returns, it will contain a small portion of the galaxy's wealth, the first in what will surely be a long series of profitable exchanges for your people.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_STARBASE_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Starbase</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_STARBASE_DESC</Label>
        <String>Our people have built permanent structures in space before, but nothing like this. This starbase is an extension of our very civilization. Everything we do, everything we are, can be found here. From it, we will surely extend our civilization even further.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_ANOMALY_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Anomaly Survey</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_ANOMALY_DESC</Label>
        <String>Our survey ship cautiously approaches the mysterious object, all sensors set to maximal gain. One of the universe's many secrets, perhaps a great danger or valuable treasure, will soon be revealed to us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_SUBSPACE_STREAM_TRAVEL_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Subspace Stream Flight</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_SUBSPACE_STREAM_TRAVEL_DESC</Label>
        <String>With a flash and a trick of physics, the ship is gone, having traveled farther and faster than any of our kind has traveled before. Today, the galaxy has gotten much, much smaller.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_INVASION_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Invasion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_INVASION_DESC</Label>
        <String>Not every planet we find will be empty; we've known that for some time. But today is the first day we've tried to take one from someone else. Today will mark a victory we will surely celebrate for a long time.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_GOVERNMENT_UPGRADE_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Election</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_GOVERNMENT_UPGRADE_DESC</Label>
        <String>Our people have spoken, and although some might doubt the wisdom, none shall doubt the process. Our new government has been given a clear mandate. Let's wish them the best, for their failure will become ours.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_PRECURSOR_RELIC_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Precursor Relic</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_PRECURSOR_RELIC_DESC</Label>
        <String>The scanner readings are inconclusive, but one thing is for certain: this object is old. As our probes maneuver around the strange device, it becomes clear that the beings who made this were vastly more powerful and experienced than we are. It's a privilege to even gaze upon their work.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_TERROR_STAR_USED_NAME</Label>
        <String>First Terror Star Used</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_TERROR_STAR_USED_DESC</Label>
        <String>Our civilization has unleashed the devastating power of a Terror Star, wiping out an entire system and all the life it hosted. There's no turning back; the Age of Terror has begun.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_TERROR_STAR_BUILT_NAME</Label>
        <String>Terror Star Complete</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FIRST_TERROR_STAR_BUILT_DESC</Label>
        <String>Your newly constructed space station is the ultimate in warfare weaponry. Equipped with a system-destroying Death Beam, your enemies will have to do some tricky maneuvering to take out this behemoth (just keep an eye on that thermal exhaust port).</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>