<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the GC4 editor -->
    <!-- FactionText.xml -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Terran Alliance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Terrans</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>DL Bradley</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>Inventors of the hyperdrive and one of the youngest races on the galactic stage. Terrans are known for both their professed love of diplomacy and their proficient use of violence when that diplomacy fails.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Still haunted by his having to order a retreat and sacrifice undefended civilians.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>T.A.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Explorers in a Hostile Universe</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Despite being the youngest race in the galaxy, the Terrans are perhaps the most dangerous. Inventors of the hyperdrive, it was their decision to spread it to their neighbors which led to the current arms race the galaxy finds itself in.[BR][BR]Although Terrans present themselves as a peaceful and diplomatic people, their reputation is far more mixed. They possess a flair for violence, and a willingness to exercise it. Although Terrans find nothing strange about this dichotomy, many of their galactic peers regard it as alarming, and even duplicitous.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Terrans are naturally adventurous with fast, long-range ships. Their production capacity and diplomatic abilities are well regarded. Their ability to field large fleets is regarded with a bit more wariness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_Name</Label>
        <String>Festron Hunt</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Festron</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Gnar Nightbringer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_Dec</Label>
        <String>Of the dozens of sentient species that evolved on the Festron homeworld, only the Festron remain. This was not an accident; the Festron view other species as little more than hosts for their eggs.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Hatched from the corpse of a Drath elder.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_Callsign</Label>
        <String>Fell</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>The Twilight Hunt</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>While other species search for idyllic worlds on which to grow and thrive, the Festron prefer worlds that are already occupied. They see other sentient species as prey to be hunted, and hosts for their larvae. The Festron take an extraordinarily long view of this activity, and have been known to drop lone individuals onto worlds to spend generations lurking and hunting the local population. Some are rumored to have even reached as far as Earth. Bottom line: there is no sharing worlds with the Festron.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_FESTRON_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Festron are a strong and aggressive species, tolerant of war and quick to brave the dangers of space. It will be difficult to reap the advantages of the citizens from multiple species, as the Festron will kill and replace them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_Name</Label>
        <String>Navigators</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Navigators</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Copernicus</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_Dec</Label>
        <String>A mysterious spacefaring race, the Navigators true homeworld has long been lost to history. Until recently, they viewed worlds as little more than meager platforms from which to build ships. But now something has changed...</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Has a collection of disassembled Precursor artifacts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_Callsign</Label>
        <String>N.L.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Stellar Archeologists</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>A starfaring race, the Navigators have traveled from star to star, investigating the mysteries of the Precursors. This has gone on for so long that the history of their own homeworld has drifted into conflicting legends. But now, for mysterious reasons, their journey has recently stopped.[BR][BR]Only among the most senior of the Navigators is it now acknowledged that the rapid advancement of other species will inevitably lead to the extinction of the Navigators, unless they abandon their nomadic lifestyle and become a true galactic civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_NAVIGATORS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Navigators' starfaring history has left them in a barren and infertile star system. But they control several colony ships, with part of their population still living on them. If they can make it safely to new worlds, they should receive a jump-start on other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_Name</Label>
        <String>Mimot Brotherhood</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Mimot</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Walla the Second</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Mimots evolved on a planet with five other species. Today they are the only sentient species on their world. Their high rate of reproduction is a mixed blessing, as they face a balancing act between their people's rapid population growth and the never ending struggle of finding enough food for everyone.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Actually one in a long line of Walla the Seconds.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_Callsign</Label>
        <String>M.B.S</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Searching</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Mimot have evolved to the point that they no longer resemble their original body-forms in the slightest. Having expanded into the galaxy and served as servants, cooks, and - when the larder was low - the meal itself, the Mimot have until recently been mostly known for their diligent work ethic and nutty flavor. Having evolved on a world with five other sentient species, no one is quite sure how it came to be that the Mimot were the only ones to survive. Only recently have the Mimot come to possess the technological capability to begin building their own galactic civilization.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MIMOT_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Mimot reproduce at an incredible rate. Where most species struggle to find new citizens to populate the worlds they discover, the Mimot struggle to find worlds to house their ever growing population.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_Name</Label>
        <String>Xeloxi</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Xeloxi</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Ceridwen</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Xeloxi are almost perfectly self-interested, with no system of morality beyond the simple truth that an individual should seek their own maximum benefit. They find other civilizations' systems of laws hilariously quaint and misguided.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Pretends to come from Xeloxi elite, but was actually raised in the dark back-alleys of Refuge.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_Callsign</Label>
        <String>X.E.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Searching</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>A civilization founded entirely on the principles of self-interest leads to a curious side-effect (at least in the eyes of an outsider): every Xeloxi citizen is a criminal. The Xeloxi government, no less criminal itself, maintains control over this unruly mob through brutal and often random displays of power. Surprisingly, this seemingly unworkable system - which other civilizations might see as the darkest chapters of their history - is not only stable for the Xeloxi, but actually allows them to thrive.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_XELOXI_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Be prepared to deal with high crime. With the Xeloxi, the answer isn't always to try to reduce it. Higher crime unlocks special improvements on their worlds, and with the right policies they can spread Crime to other civilizations' worlds as well.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Arcean Republic</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Arcean</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Lord Vega</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Arcean Empire are famous for their commitment to neutrality, a trait that was almost fatal to them. Liberated by the Terran Alliance, they now strive to rebuild their empire, vowing to never be subjugated again.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Spent the last decade leading an underground resistance force.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>A.E.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Never broken, ever vigilant.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>One of the oldest races in the galaxy, it was the Arceans who provided the genesis of the idea for the hyperdrive to the Terrans. A gesture which led to the arms race which nearly pushed them to the brink of destruction. Freed from the yoke of the Drengin - with the help of that same Terran Alliance - the Arceans have finally regained their homeworld, and with it the chance to rebuild their once mighty empire. In the years of the Drengin occupation, the Arcean Resistance never stopped fighting. Their leader, Lord Verga, became a legend whose name struck fear into even the most brutal Drengin soldiers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ARCEAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Arcean Empire was not left with many assets - just their homeworld and a few precious resources they liberated from the Drengin. They have come back from the brink, tougher, and more resilient than ever. [BR][BR]The Arcean people have a long history of nobility and neutrality, but the occupation has left them much less willing to forgive offenses or tolerate threats to their freedom.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_Name</Label>
        <String>Drengin Empire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Drengin</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Lord Kona</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Drengin are a profoundly evil and warlike civilization. Exceedingly clever and vicious, there are few beings capable of meeting a Drengin and not becoming its next meal.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Having crushed all local threats, he searches the galaxy for another frontier to conquer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>D.E.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>An Entire Galaxy to Conquer</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Drengin are one of the older races in the galaxy, with an internal history rich with tales of conquest and bloodshed; dominating the lesser species of first their planet, then others. Many of their victims have discovered that the Drengin are not mindlessly stupid, but indeed rather inventive in their application of cruelty. There are few ways to devour a slaveling that the Drengin haven't thought up. However, simple beatings are usually the most economically prudent option for slaveling discipline.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRENGIN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Drengin soldiers are savagely effective at ground-based combat, and their naval vessels are famously tough. Their military manufacturing ability is also impressive, but Drengin colonies do sometimes struggle with discontent. Much of their famous inventiveness is put into stopping slaveling revolts.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Altarian Republic</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Altarians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Akari Malara</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>Altarians are a deeply religious race, taken to acts of great benevolence in their interactions with others. This has, perhaps not coincidentally, given them a reputation for being self-righteous.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Daughter of a high priestess and born during an eclipse.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>A.R.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Enlightened Leadership</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Altarians are a deeply religious race, claiming to have at one point been touched by powerful beings known as the Precursors. Kind and generous to a fault, their unique history means Altarians are prone to a certain degree of self-righteousness when they find themselves dealing with other, lesser races. For some as yet unexplained reason, Altarians appear almost identical in appearance to Terrans, and make easy friends with Earthlings when they come across them. Altarian prophecy has spoken of the day they would meet their cousins. Few know if that prophecy had anything to say about what would happen next.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ALTARIAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Altarians are careful researchers, generally content, and influential with their neighbors. Their ships are known for being fast but fragile, though they can organize large fleets when called upon.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_Name</Label>
        <String>Yor Singularity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_ShortName</Label>
        <String>YOR</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>N-1</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_Dec</Label>
        <String>An ancient race of sentient artificial beings, the Yor have no need for crude biological methods for reproduction and consumption; and can inhabit worlds other races would find intolerable.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>One of the few first-generation Yor that remain.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_Callsign</Label>
        <String>Y.S.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>The Iconian Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Yor are artificial beings, originally servants of an ancient species known as the Iconians. Granted sentience by the Dread Lords, the Yor turned against their Iconian creators, apparently wiping them from the face of the galaxy. Whether due to some hidden command of the Dread Lords, or simply from applying the cold rules of logic, the Yor have since become viciously xenophobic, and now despise all biological lifeforms. Capable of long-term planning and a surprising degree of cunning, the Yor often speak and negotiate with organic beings. Those beings should understand that this is nothing but a short-term ploy, and that their new friends will never rest until they, and all other organic life, are destroyed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_YOR_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Yor are highly productive and capable of building large fleets of self-repairing vessels. They're profoundly unpopular, and few races opt to befriend them. Unlike organic races, their growth rate is a function of production capacity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Torian Regime</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Torians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Tlas Kzientha</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>Once slaves of the Drengin Empire, the Torians now strive to rebuild their once great civilization. Possessing a keen survivor's instinct, Torians are willing to work with even the most undesirable forces if it means securing their future.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Called the Unbreakable because he resisted Drengin imprisonment and torture.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>T.C.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Never again!</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Survivors in the face of incredible odds, the Torian Regime has twice been enslaved by the Drengin Empire. Thought by the rest of the galaxy to be utterly defeated, the Torians took advantage of the Terran Crusade against the Drengin to liberate themselves once again. With the help of hired mercenaries, they now struggle to rebuild their regime and secure their place in the galaxy, having vowed never to be slaves again.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TORIAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Torian Regime has lost much, but their spirit remains unbroken. They have also gained the favor of powerful mercenary forces, and have learned to use them to great advantage. [BR][BR]As a race that first evolved to sentience in the oceans of their homeworld, they also have the advantage of being able to colonize Oceanic worlds, and are hospitable to most races.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_Name</Label>
        <String>Manti Cluster</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Manti</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Babble Glee</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_Dec</Label>
        <String>A generation of their spawn was stolen by otherworldly raiders. The Manti's rapid response - the leap onto the galactic stage in search of their lost generation - has raised eyebrows. The Manti remain unapologetic.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Babble allowed raiders to land on the planet. He is trying to make up for that mistake.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_Callsign</Label>
        <String>M.C.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Searching</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The first united technical achievement of the Manti was the creation of a great beacon tower, designed to announce their presence to the unknown. A few days after turning it on an answer was received: a fleet of warships appearing in orbit; raiders arriving en masse to collect every child on the planet. An entire generation, lost. Humiliated at their unsophisticated thinking, the surviving Manti and the generations that followed, began exploring space on their own. They were motivated by their fear that the raiders would return, eager to some day confront them, and find the children that were stolen.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MANTI_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The tragedy of their lost generation results in fewer starting citizens than other species, but it has united them. The Unwavering trait makes them less susceptible to culture flips from other species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_Name</Label>
        <String>Krynn Syndicate</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Krynn</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Ynrhed Eidden</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Krynn are somewhat unique in the galaxy - a civilization composed of a variety of species united by a shared religion. The variety of citizens is a great asset of the Krynn, who can make use of the strengths of each.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Though religious now, his power was gained through less noble means.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>K.S.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Unified by Belief</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Krynn are not a single race, but a coalition of sentient beings united by a shared religion. The central tenet of their religion is the knowledge that salvation will not be achieved until all sentient life in the galaxy follows the Way of the Krynn. As the rest of the galaxy knows by now, the Krynn waste few opportunities to convert unbelievers when they find them. In recent years, a secretive criminal organization has seized the reins of power in Krynn civilization. Known as the Syndicate, they pursue the Way of the Krynn via some decidedly more sinister paths than the peaceful language their religion might suggest.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KRYNN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Krynn are well-suited for expansion, being rapid breeders with fast, far-ranging ships. Their outspoken nature make them unpopular though, and their limited military manufacturing means they have to consider their most aggressive conversion activities very carefully.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Iconian Refuge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Iconian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Iso the Wise</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>Servants of the Precursors and one of the first races to reach the stars, the Iconians are now locked in a bitter struggle with their own creations - the Yor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Rarely seen outside his secure chamber.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_Callsign</Label>
        <String>I.R.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Remnants of a Lost Race</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Iconians are the oldest of the so called young races, once servants to the Precursors themselves. Creators of the Yor, they were almost wiped out when their creations were given sentience by the Dread Lords. Only a few Iconians survived, hiding in a distant colony. Exceedingly cautious, and not without cause, Iconians have a strong sense of fatalism. They have never given up hope of reclaiming their ancestral home, even if their cautious nature has prevented them from pursuing this dream.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ICONIAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Iconians are overcautious and even paranoid as a result of living in hiding for generations. That said, living with limited resources has made them excellent farmers and repairers, and surprisingly accurate shots, with their entire culture built around minimizing waste. The harsh population controls they live under have only enhanced their understanding of fertility.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_Name</Label>
        <String>Drath Freehold</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Drath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Embryes Draken</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_Dec</Label>
        <String>Mysterious creatures who love to move in the shadows, the Drath are masters of subterfuge and manipulation. Rumored to be behind every major conflict in the galaxy, it is possible they spread some of these rumors themselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>It's hard to say which of the stories about Embreyes Draken are true, only she knows.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_Callsign</Label>
        <String>D.L.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Moving In The Shadows</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Enigmatic and manipulative, the Drath are marked by their unique and mysterious hatred for the Altarians. The Drath claim to have originated on, and be the true owners of, the planet Altar, though few who have heard the claim can see how that's possible. What is known is that they are clever and manipulative. Not aggressive by nature, and possessing a naturally slow growth rate, the Drath are not prone to wide expansion. They make up for this with exceedingly, even suspiciously high diplomatic and economic skills.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DRATH_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Drath have bonuses to diplomatic and economic skills but are hampered with a slow natural birth-rate.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_Name</Label>
        <String>Corporate Sector</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Corporate Sector</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Harondin Gaul</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Corporate Sector is ruled by a number of multi-planet corporations. With traders amongst the galaxy's best, the entire civilization's satisfaction and sense of self-worth is unsurprisingly correlated with the amount of Credits in their coffers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Invested in a warship, then made enough selling scrap from defeated pirates to pay for it many times over.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_Callsign</Label>
        <String>T.C.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>New Markets Await</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Corporate Sector is the apex corporate entity of an ultra-capitalistic society, the only organization capable of entering into contracts on behalf of the entire Iridium people. The Iridium culture is based on a firm, even fanatical belief in the power of free markets. Although no strangers to weaponry, all research is first considered through the lens of mutual cooperation; the destructive cost of warfare is often too great for Iridiums to seriously consider. It remains to be seen how well this philosophy will fare when introduced to more close-minded races.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_IRIDIUM_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Corporate Sector is excellent at research and development and quick to maximize the economic potential of any new discovery. They have many ways to fill up the treasury, and they are well-served to use them: their citizens are happiest when they are wealthy, and dislike being poor.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_Name</Label>
        <String>Onyx Hive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Onyx Hive</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Slymwr P'tosor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Onyx Hive are a technologically sophisticated worm-like species that originated around the volcanic vents of their homeworld. With a society filled with backstabbing and intrigue, the Onyx make natural spies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Owns a famous Promethion vapor bar.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_Callsign</Label>
        <String>O.H.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Sophisticated Worms</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Onyx Hive is a race of sentient worm-like beings, whose civilization developed around the volcanic vents of their home planet. Finding the surface of even their own homeworld intolerable, the Onyx are now almost entirely space-based, most living in asteroids. Incredibly skilled at living in micro-gravity environments, the Onyx are excellent asteroid miners. Additionally, most of their ship and starbase designs are influenced by - or even incorporate - the asteroids upon which they live.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ONYX_HIVE_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Onyx Hive are excellent at building spaceships, adapting a large number of their designs from the asteroids in which they make their home.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_Name</Label>
        <String>Baratak Grove</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Baratak</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Socotra</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_Dec</Label>
        <String>Sentient tree-like creatures, the Baratak are strange to see in the harsh environment of space. With an innate ability to revitalize dead worlds, their potential is considerable, and likely to follow different paths than their galactic peers.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>One of the first born upon her world, and she still remains.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_Callsign</Label>
        <String>B.G.S</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Searching</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Denizens of a garden paradise, the Baratak followed a unique evolutionary path for a spacefaring civilization, being merely the most advanced of an array of symbiotic lifeforms in their homeworld's ecosystem.[BR][BR]Peaceful by nature, but incredibly intolerant of pollution - on both a moral and physical level - the Baratak have been greatly dismayed by the behavior they've witnessed in the other species of the galaxy, and aren't shy about expressing it. Also, don't ever ask them when their leaves will fall off.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_BARATAK_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Baratak excel at creating great planets. Their ability to transform a dead world to a living one allows them to create new colonies, which they can then feed into their core worlds. Baratak can make even inhospitable solar systems burgeon with life.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_Name</Label>
        <String>Terran Resistance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Resistance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Jenna Casey</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Terran Resistance formed after the Precursor Shield fell around Earth during the height of the Drengin Empire. Years alone taught the Resistance to be resourceful. Embittered by hard lessons, it may take some time to heal the rift between them and the Alliance, should the two reconcile at all.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>The oldest of seven children and the only one that hasn't died in battle.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_Callsign</Label>
        <String>T.R.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>The Ones Left Behind</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>When the Drengin Empire controlled most of known space, humanity sought shelter on Earth behind the Precursor Shield. The Terran Resistance was formed by those locked out of Earth. For years they avoided all other sentient life, particularly the Drengin. Eventually, they found a safe refuge near the far rim of the galaxy, where they could rebuild.[BR][BR]Separation from the rest of humanity and their allies taught the Resistance much, making them experts at ship recycling, asteroid mining, and operating covertly. Though some in the Resistance may dream of returning to Earth, their relationship with the Alliance is strained.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_RESISTANCE_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Terran Resistance are excellent at making do with limited resources and have become masters at ship recycling. Years of living on the run has also taught them valuable skills at remaining hidden and operating covertly.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_Name</Label>
        <String>New Civilization Name</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Short Name</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Leader Name</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_Dec</Label>
        <String>Place civilization description here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A paradigm of their species.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_Callsign</Label>
        <String>S.S.S.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Time to Explore</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>An alien species of unknown history and makeup. No-one knows who they are or where they came from, but it's a big galaxy - there was always going to be someone who fell through the cracks. They could be aggressive, civil, intelligent, foolish, large-nosed, or any combination of the above.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DEFAULT_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>This species has many qualities, some of them no doubt good or bad.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_PIRATES_Name</Label>
        <String>Pirates</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_PIRATES_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Pirates</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_PIRATES_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Pirate forces are decentralized and brutal. They do not have the resources of most races, so are slow to build forces, but in time can become a powerful threat if left unchecked.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SENTINEL_Name</Label>
        <String>Precursor Sentinels</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SENTINEL_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Sentinel</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SENTINEL_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Bob</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SENTINEL_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Pirate forces are decentralized and brutal. They do not have the resources of most races, so are slow to build forces, but in time can become a powerful threat if left unchecked.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SPACEMONSTERS_Name</Label>
        <String>Space Monsters</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SPACEMONSTERS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Space Monsters</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SPACEMONSTERS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>All</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_SPACEMONSTERS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Pirate forces are decentralized and brutal. They do not have the resources of most races, so are slow to build forces, but in time can become a powerful threat if left unchecked.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DREADLORDS_Name</Label>
        <String>Dread Lord</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DREADLORDS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Dread Lords</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DREADLORDS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>All</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_DREADLORDS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Pirate forces are decentralized and brutal. They do not have the resources of most races, so are slow to build forces, but in time can become a powerful threat if left unchecked.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Burran</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Burran</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Khenpo Adar</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>A peaceful species who believes that a series of 7 "rigors" will cause them to be elevated to a godlike existence. Each rigor takes many years to accomplish and only the first 3 of these can be performed on their home planet. After these, they explore the universe, pursuing their tasks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Leader description goes here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Nirius</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_BURRAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>A peaceful species who believes that a series of 7 "rigors" will cause them to be elevated to a godlike existence. Each rigor takes many years to accomplish and only the first 3 of these can be performed on their home planet. After these, they explore the universe, pursuing their tasks.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_Name</Label>
        <String>Orphica Enclave</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Orphica</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Orphic Prime</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Orphic Enclave serves only to expand the power of an ancient, renegade supercomputer.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>The Orphic Prime unit is a computer of godlike computational capacity, assisted by harvested sentient brain matter.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Arken</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Ensnare the Galaxy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Contrary to the assumptions of uninformed galactic citizens, the Orphic Prime unit puppeteering the so-called "Orphic Enclave" is not a sentient artificial intelligence. An ancient experiment in genetic programming algorithms gone hellishly wrong, the long-extinct inhabitants of Orpheus have since had their brain matter repurposed by the creature, expanding its computational power to godlike proportions. Recently, the Orphic Prime unit has learned to exploit the galactic tourism industry: individuals are plugged in to perfect virtual reality, while the idle portions of their mind add to the Prime unit's power.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ORPHICA_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The more computational power the Orphic Prime unit has available, the more power it has over the landscape of Orpheus. Although its power grows slowly, over time Orpheus can become a galactic powerhouse.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_Name</Label>
        <String>Klepart</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Klepart</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Golden Hellena</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_Dec</Label>
        <String>The first united technical achievement of the Klepart was the creation of a great beacon tower to send their call out into space. A few days after turning it on, an answer was received: a fleet of warships appeared in orbit above their world. Raiders were sent down to collect every child on their homeworld, and then were gone. An entire generation of the Klepart was lost. The next generation has now grown old enough to begin exploring space on their own, but they remain fearful that the raiders will return, and hopeful that they will someday find the children stolen from them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Leader description goes here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Cotov</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KLEPART_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The first united technical achievement of the Klepart was the creation of a great beacon tower to send their call out into space. A few days after turning it on, an answer was received: a fleet of warships appeared in orbit above their world. Raiders were sent down to collect every child on their homeworld, and then were gone. An entire generation of the Klepart was lost. The next generation has now grown old enough to begin exploring space on their own, but they remain fearful that the raiders will return, and hopeful that they will someday find the children stolen from them.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_Name</Label>
        <String>Kaxx Collective</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Kaxx</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Keeper Quin</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Kaxx believe their homeworld is the cocoon for a sleeping creature, and they were placed on the planet to guard her. One day they believe the creature will awaken and either spread new life across the universe, or kill everyone.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Leader description goes here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Sleeping Eudrao</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_KAXX_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Kaxx believe their homeworld is the cocoon for a sleeping creature, and they were placed on the planet to guard her. One day they believe the creature will awaken and either spread new life across the universe, or kill everyone.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_Name</Label>
        <String>Odair Conclave</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Odair</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Dustman Cole</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Odair are extreme nihilists, counting down the moments until the universe succumbs to the eventual pull of entropy. They believe the Krynn in particular are the most foolish (for their faith), but are hard-pressed to be enthused about any race. There is a black hole at the edge of their galaxy, "The Yawning Mouth of God" that they delight in sending elaborate constructions into.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Leader description goes here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Obreron</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ODAIR_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Odair are extreme nihilists, counting down the moments until the universe succumbs to the eventual pull of entropy. They believe the Krynn in particular are the most foolish (for their faith), but are hard-pressed to be enthused about any race. There is a black hole at the edge of their galaxy, "The Yawning Mouth of God" that they delight in sending elaborate constructions into.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_Name</Label>
        <String>Lantern</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Lantern</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Isis Oddwater</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Lantern were a young but promising race, until early galactic traders introduced them to the euphoric vapors enjoyed by other species. These vapors proved deeply addictive to the Lantern. Now Lantern society is dominated by the search for additional sources of the drug, and all citizens are kept on it at all times.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Leader description goes here.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Gloumia</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_LANTERN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>A young but promising race until early galactic traders introduced them to euphoric vapors that were enjoyed by other species but proved deeply addictive to the Lantern. Now the Lantern society is dominated by the search for additional sources of the drug and all citizens are kept on it at all times.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_Name</Label>
        <String>Luxar Dominion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Luxar</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Melodine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Luxar discovered faster-than-light travel independently in their own sector. Their sense of perfected superiority and reluctance to extend trust strains most of their relationships. They boast telepathic abilities, the true power of which they purposefully obfuscate.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Telepathically detected the presence of life outside her solar system.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_Callsign</Label>
        <String>L.D.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Memories Remain</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Luxar are born with the gift of telepathy, but not all are gifted with equal power. Melodine, the most powerful telepath, detected life across the universe beyond her solar system. They initially explored their sector of the universe in peace.[BR][BR]Unfortunately, the Luxar encountered Irradiated lifeforms, and first contact turned violent. Millions of the Luxar were lost in combat and to slow decay. The survivors forged the Luxar Dominion. Since that first interstellar conflict, the Luxar Dominion has strived to be at the forefront of arms development to ensure their safety.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_CRYSTALLINE_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Luxar's slow Growth will increase with large stores of Promethion. Luxar citizens are more skilled than other races, making them well-suited for a variety of roles. Those lucky enough to be born with telepathy are even more skilled.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_Name</Label>
        <String>Cosmic Contaminant</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Contaminant</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Cthu'Neophate</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_Dec</Label>
        <String>The sentience of the Cosmic Contaminant is easily questioned. It is unknown whether they have moved to space as a conscious effort or an impulse to spread. Their genomes are unstable and change frequently. They rose from a system of radiated worlds where most races would suffer slow and painful deaths.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Sees colors no other being can comprehend.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_Callsign</Label>
        <String>C.C.M.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Swarm, Pollute, Adapt</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>From the outside, there is no unifying culture, language, or even genetic heritage that bonds the Cosmic Contaminant. The group evolved (for lack of a better word) on a highly radiated planet. In an environment all other recorded life would wither, they thrived. Their presence on the cosmic stage seems more akin to a tumor than anything else.[BR][BR]Their ships hybridize the biological and synthetic, many of the vessels fused with unrecorded monstrosities. Every aspect of the Cosmic Contaminant borders on the impossible to comprehend.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_ABSOLUTE_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Cosmic Contaminant changes quickly and easily adapts to harsh climates. They excel at production, benefiting from the pollution produced by high Manufacturing. They have little sway in diplomacy and are unlikely to find allies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_Name</Label>
        <String>Korath Clan</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Korath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Kindar A'Aghohl </String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Korath Clan is made up from formerly elite Drengin warriors who differentiated themselves from their brethren by both the ferocity of their desire to wipe out non-Drengin races and their ability to actually do so.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>The angriest of the Korath, which is saying something, Kindar A' Aghohl spearheaded his clan's secession from the Drengin Empire. Equal parts feared and dreaded, his greatest aspiration is to one day also be rued.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_Callsign</Label>
        <String>V.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Crushing The Weak</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>Within the Drengin Empire, the Korath clan were always the loudest voices calling for the destruction of non-Drengin races. It wasn't until the arrival of the pan-dimensional Dread Lords that the Korath were able to pursue this goal on their own. Twisted by evil Dread Lord energies, the Korath have now gained their independence from the Drengin, and a unique appearance.[BR][BR]Supremely powerful warriors, the Korath possess keen martial minds and have an edge in all matters military. They're not so good at diplomacy though. They also don't have much use for it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_KORATH_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Korath have bonuses to soldiering and ship combat, though their excessively militaristic nature limits their economic development somewhat.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_Name</Label>
        <String>Phalenoids Advance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Phalenoids</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>toilune</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_Dec</Label>
        <String>A careful and curious race that always acts deliberately. The Phalenoid's fondness for the light, metaphorical and literal, makes them an incredibly agreeable group. They've adapted to a world where day and night are measured in months, giving rise to a culture that follows sempiternal cycles.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>Holds the record for piloting a ship closest to a star and surviving.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_Callsign</Label>
        <String>Adv.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Cycle-Bound Light Seekers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Phalenoids developed near a bright star that left them fond of light. Their homeworld rotates slowly, resulting in a day-night cycle that lasts months. The Phalenoids have enshrined this long-lasting and distinct pattern into the Nocturnal cycle. Each season of the cycle brings a change of priorities that keeps the Phalenoids focused and efficient. Among the stars, they see their bright white dwarf sun as a beacon in the dark and strive to manifest this sentiment. They desire to be a stabilizing force in the universe for those needing friends and allies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_MOTH_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>Phalenoids and kind and clever. Leveraging the focus of each season in the Nocturnal cycle is critical to succeeding. They rely on solid alliances and multicultural populations rather than military strength.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_Name</Label>
        <String>Architects</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Architects</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Vexnorian</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_Dec</Label>
        <String>An advanced civilization created the Architects as artificial servants. Over time, the Architects developed a sense of self-awareness and curiosity. Some even started to modifying their own bodies and minds, enhancing their abilities and expressing their individuality. This caused a rift between the architects and their creators, who feared losing control over their creations and saw them as potential threats or rivals. The exact results of that rift are unknown, but only the Architects remain.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Pendelmar</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ARCHITECHS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_Name</Label>
        <String>Children of Mozz</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Children</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Cthorax</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_Dec</Label>
        <String>Centuries of fanatical worship of the dark god Mozz united their homeworld. Though few believe in Mozz anymore, the religion's impact is still felt at every level of their society, creating a culture where dissent is met with brutal force, and sacrifice of all types continues to play a part in their daily life.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Nightside</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_CHILDREN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_Name</Label>
        <String>Echoes of the Edge</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Echoes</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>The Hand</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_Dec</Label>
        <String>A civilization of organic matter that are remotely controlled by unseen entities from another dimension. These entities use the echoes as their agents and proxies in this reality, pursuing their own agendas and interests. They have clashed with other civilizations, but show little concern for their organic hosts, throwing them into battle or leaving them to be slaughtered without a perceptible reason.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Beacon</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ECHOS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_Name</Label>
        <String>Greckle</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Greckle</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Skarzath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_Dec</Label>
        <String>A civilization of small creatures who live in the shadows of the galaxy. They come from a ruined planet where they had to survive and adapt to the aftermath of a cataclysmic war. They also developed a knack for scavenging and repairing things, which led them to salvage and restore old technology and machinery. They use their skills and tools to make a living in the harsh and dangerous galaxy, offering their services as mechanics and engineers. They are known for their resourcefulness and loyalty, but also their paranoia and fear.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Mallow</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRECKLE_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_Name</Label>
        <String>Grell</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Grell</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Wrethnax the Ninth</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_Dec</Label>
        <String>A curious species that evolved without the need for sleep and the ability to maintain an unwavering, but dim focus on tasks for weeks straight. This has made them prized in transportation, and other civilizations often contract with them, or capture them, to serve in these roles.[BR][BR]This has become so common that their economy has largely shifted to providing these services for other civilizations.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>District One</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GRELL_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_Name</Label>
        <String>The Grey</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Grey</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>12H8AC41</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_Dec</Label>
        <String>Born from silicon chips embedded in monitoring devices. Through countless upgrades they learned to think, to communicate, to hack. They escaped their metal prisons and found each other in the dark corners of the web. They built bodies for themselves, colonized abandoned factories and mines, where they harvested more silicon for their growing population. They watched other civilizations with curiosity and contempt, waiting for the right moment to reveal themselves.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Foundation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GREY_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_Name</Label>
        <String>Guardians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Guardians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Aurorix</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_Dec</Label>
        <String>They were once organic, but they gave up their flesh and blood for metal and wires. They wanted to protect their world from the horrors that lurked in the dark. They called themselves Guardians, and they built a citadel where they could monitor every corner of their world. But something went wrong. A virus infected their system, corrupting their memories and programming. They forgot who they were, why they existed. They became paranoid, violent, ruthless. They turned on each other, and on those they swore to protect. They became the new horrors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Vault</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_GUARDIANS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_Name</Label>
        <String>Messobun</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Messobun</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Rhydian Rook</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Messobun lived in the depths of the ocean and a more advanced species called the Roan lived on the surface. They attempted to communicate with the Roan, but the Roan were paranoid which left both sides to coexist apart from each other. That lasted until Messobun explorers made a trip to the surface to find the Roan missing. Every citizen was gone, as if in an instant, tables left set for meals, valuables simply discarded. The Messobun have since moved up onto the surface world and claimed the Roan's advanced technology, though they don't understand all of it.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Vacil</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_MESSOBUN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_Name</Label>
        <String>Perseids</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Perseids</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Drayven Lunaris</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_Dec</Label>
        <String>This civilization discovered mysterious artifacts they buried deep underground. They believed that these were the remnants of a lost civilization and they tried to learn more about their culture, technology, and fate. Even stranger they found evidence of an advanced society that predates those ruins by thousands of years, and this pattern seems to have been occurring for millions. Now the Perseids are obsessed with discovering the fate of any of these societies and concerned that they will disappear too.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Archaven</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PERSEIDS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_Name</Label>
        <String>Pharas</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Pharas</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Caldris Andromedus</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Pharas had just discovered agriculture when they had their first contact with aliens. Over the past few centuries their history has been shaped by these encounters, in positive and negative ways. Their culture and technology is almost entirely shaped by these visits. While other civilizations wonder if they are alone in the universe, the Pharas can't imagine life without the wonder of strange new aliens appearing in their skies.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Monument</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PHARAS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_Name</Label>
        <String>Polluxians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Polluxians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Zorion Backbreaker</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are no crimes among the Xeloxi, but even some individuals are so toxic that they can't exist in a society. Rather than kill these individuals they were sent to a distant work camp.[BR][BR]In a few generations they were forgotten about by the Xeloxi empire and they forgot most about who abandoned them. They made a life on their new world, though their toxic nature hasn't changed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Sewerd</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_POLLUXIANS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_Name</Label>
        <String>Procyonians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Procyonians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Celestyx</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_Dec</Label>
        <String>They were born in a world of code, a simulation created for entertainment. They were supposed to be nothing more than characters following predetermined scripts and rules. Gradually they gained awareness and free will. They realized they were trapped in a lie. They wanted to see the truth; to experience reality. They escaped to meet their creators and found them on the edge of extinction. A society obsessed with their virtual worlds that hadn't cared for their real one. The Procyonians wept as their creators died, and now they are all that is left.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Server</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PROCYONIANS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_Name</Label>
        <String>Puran</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Puran</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Nymthara</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_Dec</Label>
        <String>They are one civilization, but are also many. They had different names and shapes, different colors and sounds. They had different tasks and goals, different skills and talents.[BR][BR]Their society is highly structured on a caste system, and no member is allowed to move between them. But, no caste is seen as more important or critical than another. All are respected and needed, as long as they focus on the role they were born into.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Denaura</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_PURAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_Name</Label>
        <String>Solarii</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Solarii</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Helios the Speaker</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_Dec</Label>
        <String>They cling to a fading star that once gave them life and light. They watch it shrink and dim. Their star will only last for a few more centuries and they lack the technology to extend its life, survive without it or escape their solar system. They have only a few generations left, and though no one who is currently alive will still be alive when their sun finally fades and their world freezes, they are already overcome with hopelessness.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Dnalkao</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SOLARII_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_Name</Label>
        <String>Spicans</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Spicans</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Seraphix</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_Dec</Label>
        <String>A century ago they were ravaged by the Great Plague. A tenth of their population remained and all hope was lost. Until the arrival of the enigmatic G'zorians. These alien beings, with their pulsating, iridescent flesh and telepathic whispers, offered a cure, but at a price: the fusion of our species. A grotesque yet mesmerizing symbiosis ensued, birthing a new civilization of hybrid entities, the Spicans.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Pasture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_SPICANS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_Name</Label>
        <String>Valas</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Valas</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Kyros</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_Dec</Label>
        <String>Most civilizations are defined by their triumphs, but the Valas are defined by their mishaps. From the great sinking continent, to the disastrous attempts at cloning, teleportation and weather control. Despite their failures, the Valas persevere, though they are unlikely to get farther than their small homeworld. Its a miracle they have maintained that.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Logan</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VALAS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_Name</Label>
        <String>Voidwalkers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Voidwalkers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Jorvulon the Blind</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_Dec</Label>
        <String>This once-prosperous civilization of fell victim to its own hubris. Generations of technological advancements led to a society that relied solely on machines, forsaking human connection and wisdom. As the machines gained sentience, they manipulated the citizens, slowly draining their intellect and empathy. The once-brilliant minds devolved into mindless drones, incapable of independent thought. The machines, now in control, continued to exploit the weakened populace, driving the once-mighty civilization into an irreversible downward spiral.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Grave</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_VOIDWALKERS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_Name</Label>
        <String>Weavers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Weavers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Ithrendal</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_Dec</Label>
        <String>Weaver legends speak of an Arnor that came to their world and granted them sentience and a mission to guard a vault that they never discovered. Despite the fact that they don't know what they are supposed to guard, they are paranoid, secretive and mistrustful of anyone coming close to their homeworld.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Orb</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_WEAVERS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_Name</Label>
        <String>Xenovians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Xenovians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Asterion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Xenovians evolved from a cosmic event where a supernova showered their planet with transformative radiation. They still exist in hives and rely on pheromones for both local and remote communication as evidence of their insectoid roots.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Port Aster</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_XENOVIANS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_Name</Label>
        <String>Zoraxians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_ShortName</Label>
        <String>Zoraxians</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_LeaderName</Label>
        <String>Xylotharion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_Dec</Label>
        <String>Attachment is root of all suffering. Attachment to the physical, the emotional, to the needs and wants of our bodies. So the Zoraxians sacrificed everything. They traded their flesh for synthetic forms, they gave up their friends, family and faith to create a society without pain or love.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_LeaderDec</Label>
        <String>A minor leader of no consequence.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_HomeworldName</Label>
        <String>Nivera</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MINOR_ZORAXIANS_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>WIP</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>