<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!--Campaign Tutorial Text-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tutorial_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>(Tutorial) The Story so Far</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tutorial_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>In 2178, the humans of a United Earth developed Hyperdrive Propulsion systems, discovering faster-than-light travel.[BR][BR]Humanity had already established interstellar contact with two civilizations: The Korx and the Arcean Empire. Some scientists, eager to share their discoveries, transmit the specifications for the new drive systems to the Arceans and the Korx. Both groups go silent immediately after receiving the specifications for this new technology. Earth is left alone in the universe once again.[BR][BR]You are Commander DL Bradley, leader of the newly formed Terran Alliance. This group has been created to oversee the manned exploration of space and the colonization of new planets. Humanity's new Hyperdrive Propulsion makes such grand ambitions possible.[BR][BR]Unfortunately, you must contend with a new threat: Pirates. A group of terrorists have acquired the Hyperdrive plans. They threaten all colonization efforts as long as they keep a foothold in nearby star systems. At some point, we will need to find and destroy their base.[BR][BR]Your primary mission is to colonize at least 8 worlds with at least one large enough to warrant a governor and establish leaders to support the effort.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_ColonizeTargetPlanets</Label>
        <String>Colonize 8 Planets</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_ColonizeTargetPlanets_Dec</Label>
        <String>Explore the galaxy to find planets to colonize. Planets can be colonized using Colony Ships. Colony Ships can be constructed at a Shipyard or obtained through the Draft Colonists Executive Order.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_FillCabinet</Label>
        <String>Appoint 3 Ministers</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_FillCabinet_Dec</Label>
        <String>Grant benefits to the entire Alliance by recruiting Leaders and putting them to work. Recruited Leaders can be assigned roles in the Ministry, accessible through the Leader Screen. Each position provides a unique benefit based on a specific stat, so pick the best person for the job to get the best benefit possible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_AppointGovernor</Label>
        <String>Appoint a Governor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_AppointGovernor_Dec</Label>
        <String>Planets with a Planet Class 10 or greater can be turned into Coreworlds by assigning a Governor to the planet. To assign a Governor, you'll first need a Leader available. Planets with Governors can be upgraded to improve output and support a new Shipyard.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_DestroyTheShipyard</Label>
        <String>Destroy a Pirate Shipyard</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_DestroyTheShipyard_Dec</Label>
        <String>Pirates have set up a base in this part of the galaxy. While they're allowed a Shipyard, they can produce ships that threaten the whole Alliance. Destroying the Pirate's Shipyard will weaken their forces and drive them from the galaxy.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_Overall</Label>
        <String>Secure the Sector for the Terran Alliance</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_FindCoreWorld</Label>
        <String>Colonize a Core World</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_FindCoreWorld_Dec</Label>
        <String>You've successfully colonized enough planets for the Alliance; however, the Alliance wants to enhance its foothold with a new Coreworld. To establish a new Coreworld, you'll need a Colony on a planet with a Planet Class 10 or higher. Continue to search the galaxy for a planet at Planet Class 10 or greater to colonize.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_UnlockLeaders</Label>
        <String>Complete the Colonial Leadership Project</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_UnlockLeaders_Dec</Label>
        <String>There are a lot of benefits that Leaders provide to the entire civilization. The project Colonial Leadership needs to be completed at the homeworld to recruit and manage Leaders. The project can be queued up and completed through the planet management screen from the Projects section.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <!--EVENT TEXT-->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_Tutorail_GenericConfirm</Label>
        <String>Understood</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_Intro_Name</Label>
        <String>The Terran Alliance: First Steps</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_Intro_Dec</Label>
        <String>In 2178, the humans of a United Earth developed Hyperdrive Propulsion systems, discovering faster-than-light travel.[BR][BR]Humanity had already established interstellar contact with two civilizations: The Korx and the Arcean Empire. Some scientists, eager to share their discoveries, transmit the specifications for the new drive systems to the Arceans and the Korx. Both groups go silent immediately after receiving the specifications for this new technology. Earth is left alone in the universe once again.[BR][BR]You are Commander DL Bradley, leader of the newly formed Terran Alliance. This group has been created to oversee the manned exploration of space and the colonization of new planets. Humanity's new Hyperdrive Propulsion makes such grand ambitions possible.[BR][BR]Unfortunately, you must contend with a new threat: Pirates. A group of terrorists have acquired the Hyperdrive plans. They threaten all colonization efforts as long as they keep a foothold in nearby star systems. At some point, we will need to find and destroy their base.[BR][BR]Your primary mission is to colonize at least 8 worlds with at least one large enough to warrant a governor and establish leaders to support the effort.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_ColonizedGovernablePlanet_Name</Label>
        <String>A Prospective Core World</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_ColonizedTargetPlanets_Name</Label>
        <String>Foothold Established</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_ColonizedTargetPlanetsNoCoreworld_Name</Label>
        <String>Search for a Core World</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_CanUseCabinet_Name</Label>
        <String>Leaders Available</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_InstalledGovernor_Name</Label>
        <String>Governor Assigned</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_PiratesSpotted_Name</Label>
        <String>Pirate Shipyard Located!</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_CabinetFilled_Name</Label>
        <String>Cabinet Filled</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_ShipyardDestroyed_Name</Label>
        <String>Pirate Shipyard Destroyed</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>Event_Campaign_Tutorial_ShipyardDestroyedLeadersLocked_Name</Label>
        <String>Pirate Shipyard Destroyed</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_Tutorial_StartupDescription</Label>
        <String>The Terran Alliance has been formed by United Earth to explore space and colonize new planets. This project has been made possible by the development of faster-than-light travel. Approaching the galaxy warrants caution. If the natural dangers of the cosmos weren't enough, there might be aliens. [BR][BR]It's been some time since humanity last contacted the Arceans or the Korx, leaving them alone in the galaxy once more. It may only be a matter of time before discovering other alien groups. Until then, it's up to the Terran Alliance and its commander, DL Bradley, to secure the sector in the name of humanity.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_Tutorial_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
        <String>The Terran Alliance's current isolation should be considered an advantage. There is an opportunity to expand, establish production, and discover how best to organize.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FACTION_TERRAN_Campaign_Tutorial_StartupTitle</Label>
        <String>Isolated Spacefarers</String>
    </StringTable>

</StringTableList>