<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<StringTableList
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
    <!-- Created with the Gal Civ 3 Editor -->
    <!-- UPResolutionDefsText.xml -->
    <!-- Culture Trait Names and Descriptions -->
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ElectChairmanRes_Name</Label>
        <String>Elect A United Planet Chair.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ElectChairmanRes_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to better assist all the races of the Galaxy, the U.P. elects a Chair Being that will lead the U.P. for the next four sessions, whose duty it is to choose which proposals should be presented.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](The winning race is appointed the U.P. Chair for the duration)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ElectChairmanRes_Question</Label>
        <String>Who should be the U.P. Chair?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsHeadquarters_Name</Label>
        <String>United Planets Headquarters</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsHeadquarters_Dec</Label>
        <String>One member race is chosen to host the United Planets Headquarters for the duration.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](50% bonus to Influence for the selected race)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsHeadquarters_Question</Label>
        <String>Who should get the UP HQ?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsTourismBoard_Name</Label>
        <String>United Planets Tourism Board</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsTourismBoard_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to facilitate race relations and better educate its member citizens, the United Planets moves to establish a Galactic Tourism Board. This will help popularize the assorted tourist spots throughout the galaxy.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Tourism bonuses are doubled)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsTourismBoard_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we open the United Planets Tourism Board?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalaxyUnitedCelebration_Name</Label>
        <String>Galaxy United Celebration</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalaxyUnitedCelebration_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets proposes to organize a year long celebration in an attempt to make the citizens of the galaxy realize how good they have it.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](10% Approval bonus to all members)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalaxyUnitedCelebration_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we start the Galaxy United Celebration?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EconomicRedistributionAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Economic Redistribution</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EconomicRedistributionAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets has grown concerned that some have become excessively wealthy by exploiting the other races of the UP. It therefore proposes a tax on the wealthiest race. The revenue generated will be equally distributed between the remaining members.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](The race with the largest treasury gives 25% of their credits to the remaining members)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EconomicRedistributionAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have an Economic Redistribution?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticPeace_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Peace</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticPeace_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets proposes that all interstellar wars be brought to an immediate end. [BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Wars are ended and can not be declared for the duration)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticPeace_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have Galactic Peace?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarWarFine_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar War Fine</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarWarFine_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets has found that the price of interstellar war has become so great that it affects the economies of all races including those not embroiled in these conflicts. Therefore, it proposes a Tax on all member races that continue to wage war.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Warring races are fined 25% of their treasury, these credits are distributed to non-warring members)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarWarFine_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have an Interstellar War Fine?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticGamesFund_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Games Fund</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticGamesFund_Dec</Label>
        <String>Taking a note from the Romans the United Planets proposes a galaxy sporting event, the Galactic Games, to bring the disparate races together to compete in just about every sport known, over a six month period. The lucky race to host the GG's will reap the financial rewards. [BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](15% Economic bonus to the chosen race)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticGamesFund_Question</Label>
        <String>Who should host the Galactic Games?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CulturalPreservationCouncil_Name</Label>
        <String>Cultural Preservation Council</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CulturalPreservationCouncil_Dec</Label>
        <String>In an attempt to lower tension between member nations, the U.P. moves that colonies will no longer be able to change their allegiance.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Colonies controlled by members can no longer have Influence affected)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>CulturalPreservationCouncil_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Cultural Preservation Council?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarPatentBoard_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Patent Board</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarPatentBoard_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to stimulate research, the United Planets endorses the formation of an Interstellar Patent Board. That will allow inventing races to make a profit as a reward for their efforts.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](The first member to research a tech gets 25% of its cost back in credits)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarPatentBoard_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have an Interstellar Patent Board?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FreedomOfTechnologyAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Freedom of Technology</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FreedomOfTechnologyAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets, in an attempt to equalize opportunity, will require all of its members to provide one tech to be shared with all members.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](A random tech will be chosen from each member, and given to all others)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FreedomOfTechnologyAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Freedom of Technology Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsResearchFoundation_Name</Label>
        <String>U.P. Research Foundation</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsResearchFoundation_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to foster growth and quality of life, the United Planets moves to fund a Research Foundation that will facilitate the sharing of Knowledge throughout the galaxy.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Non-military technologies will be 25% cheaper to research for members)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>UnitedPlanetsResearchFoundation_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have an United Planets Research Foundation?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyExploitationPreventionAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Tech. Exploitation Prevention</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyExploitationPreventionAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets has found that technology trading races have taken advantage of unwary races, brokering these technologies to their enemies. Therefore, it proposes a ban on all technology brokering.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Technologies may not be resold to other races)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyExploitationPreventionAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Technology Exploitation Prevention Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyNonInterferenceAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Technical Non-Interference</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyNonInterferenceAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets has become concerned that the ramped up trading of technology has begun to stifle the cultural development of its members, encouraging homogenization over cultural diversity. It therefore proposes a ban on all technological trading.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Disables technology trading)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyNonInterferenceAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Technology Non-Interference Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EnvironmentalProtectionAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Environmental Protection</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EnvironmentalProtectionAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets, in an attempt to protect what is left of the virgin worlds in the galaxy, calls for a freeze to all colonization. [BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Members can not colonize new planets)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>EnvironmentalProtectionAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have an Environmental Protection Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DemilitarizationTreaty_Name</Label>
        <String>Demilitarization</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DemilitarizationTreaty_Dec</Label>
        <String>In order to foster peace in the galaxy, the United Planets moves to ban the research of all new weapons technologies for a limited duration. [BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Un-researched weapons techs are locked for the duration)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DemilitarizationTreaty_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Demilitarization Treaty?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarTradeStimulusAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Trade Stimulus</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarTradeStimulusAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets believes that thriving interstellar peace is good for all its members, promoting good will and economic growth. To this end it is endorsing the expansion of trade licenses, granting each race an additional two trade routes each.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Members gain two additional trade routes)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InterstellarTradeStimulusAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have an Interstellar Trade Stimulus Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DiversityInTradeAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Diversity in Trade</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DiversityInTradeAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets feels that exclusive trading causes cultural islands that breed strife in the galaxy. In order to encourage diversification, the UP proposes an economic reward to races that trade with all members that they are not at war with.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Having at least one trade route with each member provides a 50% bonus to Trade income)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DiversityInTradeAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Diversity in Trade Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticDomainAct_Name</Label>
        <String>Galactic Domain</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticDomainAct_Dec</Label>
        <String>The United Planets feels that uncolonized planets in an empire's borders belong to that empire. The UP proposes a resolution to block other races from colonizing them.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](Players can not colonize planets in another player's borders)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>GalacticDomainAct_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Galactic Domain Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DefiantRaceRemoval_Name</Label>
        <String>Defiant Race Removal</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DefiantRaceRemoval_Dec</Label>
        <String>Any faction in the UP must forever vow to purge the galaxy of any faction defying the UP.[BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight](All members declare war on anyone who is defying the UP)[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>DefiantRaceRemoval_Question</Label>
        <String>Should we have a Defiant Race Removal Act?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyOutreach_Name</Label>
        <String>Technology Outreach</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyOutreach_Dec</Label>
        <String>We cooperating together all civilizations will be able to finish their current research project</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>TechnologyOutreach_Question</Label>
        <String>Should everyone get their current research project completed?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ANewHomeWorld_Name</Label>
        <String>Xendar Homeworld</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ANewHomeWorld_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Xendar's homeworld was destroyed many years ago. Since then, they have sought a new world.  At last, we have found a suitable planet for them to settle on. Should they be given a homeworld?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ANewHomeWorld_Question</Label>
        <String>Should the Xendar be given a planet?</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ThuliumNeeded_Name</Label>
        <String>Thulium Needed</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ThuliumNeeded_Dec</Label>
        <String>There is a definite shortage of Thulium in the galaxy. This proposal requires us to use all our resources to convert 5 dead worlds into Thulium.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ThuliumNeeded_Question</Label>
        <String>Should 5 dead worlds be converted to Thulium?</String>
    </StringTable>
</StringTableList>