<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<FlavorTextDefs
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_GenericConfirm</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Understood</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <!---->
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_StartOfGame</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Since the inception of the Hyperdrive by the Terran Alliance, this groundbreaking technology has rapidly spread, ushering in a multitude of new civilizations onto the galactic forefront. [BR][BR]We categorize minor civilizations as those yet to achieve Faster-Than-Light travel. Notably, a species named the Xeloxi recently pilfered Hyperdrive blueprints from unsuspecting researchers who visited their domain. [BR][BR]The Xeloxi's societal norms starkly contrast with our understanding of morality. Activities we deem criminal, including theft, are integral to their culture. Consequently, they have emerged as a formidable threat in our vicinity, predominantly exploiting vulnerable civilizations without the means to resist. [BR][BR]Our primary mission is to shield these civilizations. To achieve this, we must integrate them into our sphere of influence. Establishing a Starbase in proximity and expanding its influence is our best strategy. Simultaneously, efforts to oust the Xeloxi from this sector must be intensified. Good luck!</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>

    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_ControlsMinorCivxXeloxiRemain</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Minor Civilizations of the sector now know relief. While under Alliance protection, they are free of the Xeloxi's oppression. This freedom may be temporary. There is a threat as long as the Xeloxi occupy this part of the galaxy. The Xeloxi must be pushed from the sector, and any planet they claim retaken.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Protect 3 Minor Civilizations</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_ControlsMinorCivxXeloxiDestroyed</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Minor Civilizations of the sector now know relief. While under Alliance protection, they are free of the Xeloxi's oppression. In addition, the Xeloxi have already been pushed from this part of the galaxy, providing additional security to these fledgling civilizations.[BR][BR]Congratulations on fulfilling your duties.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Protect 3 Minor Civilizations</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_XeloxiDestroyedMinorFactionsUncontrolled</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Xeloxi have been defeated! They are driven from this part of the galaxy. Great work.[BR][BR]The Minor Civilizations of this sector may not feel relief yet. They remain unprotected and may still suffer from the Xeloxi influence. To stabilize this section of the galaxy, the Minor Civilizations should be brought under the Alliance's Zone of Control.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Defeat the Xeloxi</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_XeloxiDestroyedMinorFactionsControlled</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>The Xeloxi have been defeated! They are driven from this part of the galaxy. Great work.[BR][BR]The Minor Civilizations can know true peace, at least for a moment. They are now under Alliance protection, and the Xeloxi threat has been sent far away.BR][BR]Congratulations on fulfilling your duties.[BR][BR]Completed Objective: Defeat the Xeloxi</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
    <FlavorTextDef>
        <InternalName>AllianceAscendant_DestroyedMinorFaction</InternalName>
        <FlavorTextOption>
            <Text>Abort![BR][BR]Something must have gone wrong. One of the Minor Civilizations has been destroyed. Things have escalated too far. The lives that remain can not be risked.[BR][BR]This mission is being counted as failed, and the Alliance is pulling all resources from the sector.[BR][BR]Failed Objective: Ensure All Minor Factions Survive</Text>
        </FlavorTextOption>
    </FlavorTextDef>
</FlavorTextDefs>