<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<StringTableList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Recapitalize_Name</Label>
    <String>Recapitalize</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Recapitalize_Dec</Label>
    <String>Generate new capital through recapitalization with your reserve currency status.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>SpawnMiner_Name</Label>
    <String>Hire Miner</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>SpawnMiner_Dec</Label>
    <String>Engage skilled miners to extract valuable resources efficiently and boost your productivity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>SpawnFreighter_Name</Label>
    <String>Hire Merchant</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>SpawnFreighter_Dec</Label>
    <String>Contract experienced merchants to manage and expand your trade routes, maximizing profitability.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GalacticReserve_Name</Label>
    <String>Réserve de Monnaie Galactique</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GalacticReserve_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Position your currency as the unifying economic cornerstone of the galaxy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ReallyLateStageCapitalism_Name</Label>
    <String>Capitalisme de Très Dernier Stade</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ReallyLateStageCapitalism_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>First step to ensuring our currency is the galactic reserve currency.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ReallyLateStageCapitalism_Dec</Label>
    <String>Money is what will detemrine who rules this galaxy. And the civilization who controls the most trusted form of currency will be in the best position to control the flow of money. [BR][BR]In the vast cosmic expanse where myriad civilizations vie for dominance, a profound understanding of economic structures is indispensable. The "Trade Networks" technology represents a sophisticated endeavor aimed at achieving an economic zenith: positioning one's currency as the epicenter of the galactic economy.[BR][BR]Within this ambit, a reserve currency transcends its rudimentary function as a transactional medium. It emerges as an emblem of economic prowess—a universally acknowledged benchmark against which the financial robustness of other currencies is gauged. The custodian of such a formidable currency enjoys manifold advantages, ranging from facilitating frictionless interstellar commerce to securing preferential exchange rates. More significantly, this custodianship bestows upon its holder a potent instrument in the orchestra of diplomatic and economic dialogues.[BR][BR]Beyond its transactional supremacy, the galactic reserve currency serves as a bulwark against economic vicissitudes. It becomes a coveted asset, zealously accumulated by civilizations galaxy-wide, thereby perpetuating its demand and reinforcing its fiscal stature. The strategic privilege of directing monetary policies, afforded to the progenitor of this currency, wields the power to sculpt the contours of the overarching galactic economy.[BR][BR]In essence, the pursuit of the Trade Networks technology is not merely a quest for economic ascendancy; it represents a philosophical commitment to reshaping the very sinews of galactic commerce, diplomacy, and power dynamics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Modifier_OwnedClusterInfluenceBonus</Label>
    <String>Bonus du Secteur Possédé</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>RelativeEthicsModule_Name</Label>
    <String>Relativistic Ethics Beacon</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>RelativeEthicsModule_Dec</Label>
    <String>50% Boost to influence output</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>RelativeEthicsModule_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>50% Boost to influence output</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>STATNAME_OwnedClustersCount</Label>
    <String>Owned Sectors</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>STATDESC_OwnedClustersCount</Label>
    <String>Number of Sectors the faction has majority control over.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>PLAYER_READY_LABEL</Label>
    <String>Ready</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>PopupTurnSummary</Label>
    <String>Auto Pop-Up</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Alert_Show_Title</Label>
    <String>Always Show</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Alert_UI_Title</Label>
    <String>Monthly News Report</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Alert_UI_Done</Label>
    <String>Done</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Alert_UI_Clear</Label>
    <String>Clear All</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>Alert_Devider_Header</Label>
    <String>July 8th - July 14th, 2308</String>
  </StringTable>
</StringTableList>
