<StringTableList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd"><StringTable>
        <Label>ImpressCitizens_Name</Label>
        <String>Impress Citizens</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ImpressCitizens_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our people are owned by you. It is time they remember. Will provide a Colony Ship and a Constructor</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedLabor_Name</Label>
        <String>Forced Labor</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedLabor_Dec</Label>
        <String>The people are working hard. They could be working harder.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedTraining_Name</Label>
        <String>Thrall Training</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ForcedTraining_Dec</Label>
        <String>Trains thralls to increase target fleet experience.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>RushNewCitizen_Name</Label>
        <String>Manufacture Population</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>RushNewCitizen_Dec</Label>
        <String>Without using Durantium we can recycle scraps to quickly produce more citizens.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FleetIncreaseMovesEO_Name</Label>
        <String>Upgrade Fleet Propulsion</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>FleetIncreaseMovesEO_Dec</Label>
        <String>Use our executive powers to focus our efforts onto a single fleet to optimize its speed.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MilitaryConstructionEO_Name</Label>
        <String>Shipyard Production Boost</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MilitaryConstructionEO_Dec</Label>
        <String>Focus our efforts to quickly supply manufacturing resources to a specific shipyard.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InfluenceBroadcast_Name</Label>
        <String>Broadcast Culture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>InfluenceBroadcast_Dec</Label>
        <String>This module contains an optimized message certain to make others wish to assimilate to our culture.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>PlanetTiles_Name</Label>
        <String>Modify Planet</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PlanetTiles_Dec</Label>
        <String>Increase this planet's use to our species. Adds +1 to its usable tiles. Should only be used on Core worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeo_Name</Label>
    <String>Worm Rodeo</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeo_Dec</Label>
    <String>We recently received word that an important leader from the {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} was visiting {PLANETNAME}.  You may recall that you established a worm rodeo there some time ago. [BR][BR]The alien visitor was so impressed that this has led to improved relations with their species.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeoChoice_Name</Label>
    <String>I knew it was a good idea.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_WormRodeo_Choice_Text_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Worm Rodeo continues.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_SpaceWhaleMurder_Name</Label>
    <String>Space Whale Slaughterer</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_SpaceWhaleMurder_Dec</Label>
    <String>We are horrified and disgusted that you would exterminate the precious Lilulas, the gentle space creatures that were migrating through this part of space. The {PLAYERFACTIONLONG:1} condemns your vile actions.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Consequence_SpaceWhaleMurder_Choice1_Name</Label>
    <String>I never thought you'd find out.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
        <Label>Entry_DrenginEmpire</Label>
        <String>Drengin Empire</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Entry_DrenginEmpire_Dec</Label>
        <String>The Drengin Empire embodies the quintessence of cosmic ambition. Towering at over 9 feet and brandishing an impressive set of razor-sharp teeth, their reputation in the galaxy is one of both awe and fear. The year 2226 marked a poignant chapter in their history, witnessing a civil confrontation with the Korath. And in this intricate dance of power, the Drengin, surprisingly, were the more measured participants.[BR][BR]The Drengin's creed is simple: the galaxy and all its non-Drengin inhabitants exist for their dominion. Their history with the Arceans is a testament to this belief. The joint invention of the stargates was a landmark of cooperation, swiftly followed by the Drengin's attempted betrayal. The ensuing debacle cemented a rivalry that remains fervent, even as stars burn out.[BR][BR]It would be an error to assume the Drengin's aggressiveness overshadows their intellect. Their technological marvels tread into areas many would deem ethically nebulous. Their persistence in galactic conquest is evident from their historical annals. When humanity was embroiled in terrestrial power struggles, the Drengin were engineering audacious mechanisms, like the ominous 'death furnaces', and undertaking expansive campaigns like the Torian enslavement.[BR][BR]Ironically, what held the Drengin back from universal domination was the vastness of space itself. Their venture to Toria, while grand, underscored the inefficiencies of their space travel. Humanity's invention of the hyperdrive, however, leveled the cosmic playing field. The initial human overtures, grounded in idealistic hopes of a united cosmos, were met with Drengin pragmatism in 2176. The ensuing silence from that human delegation speaks volumes, reminding us all that cosmic diplomacy, with the Drengin, comes with its own set of... challenges.</String>
    </StringTable>
<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_ConquestTitle</Label>
		<String>Conquest Victory</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_ConquestDec</Label>
		<String>A Conquest Victory is achieved by destroying all other major civilizations.[BR][BR]Check victory progress under the Victory Status screen, accessible from the pause menu.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_InfluenceTitle</Label>
		<String>Influence Victory</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_InfluenceDec</Label>
		<String>An Influence Victory is achieved by having a majority of the galaxy in the Zone of Control and being at piece with all other major civlizations for several months.[BR][BR]Check victory progress under the Victory Status screen, accessible from the pause menu.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_AllianceTitle</Label>
		<String>Alliance Victory</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_AllianceDec</Label>
		<String>An Alliance Victory is achieved by being allied with all other major civilizations.[BR][BR]Check victory progress under the Victory Status screen, accessible from the pause menu.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_PrestigeTitle</Label>
		<String>Prestige Victory</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>Hotspot_PrestigeDec</Label>
		<String>A Prestige Victory is achieved by reaching a specific [HS=HS_Prestige]Prestige[/HS] Score.[BR][BR]Check victory progress under the Victory Status screen, accessible from the pause menu.</String>
	</StringTable>
   
<StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_HiveMinds_Name</Label>
        <String>Hive Mind</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_HiveMind_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Every individual operates in perfect harmony, guided by a shared consciousness. The concept of "self" has dissolved, making the civilization a powerful, singular entity.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]All units and cities act in perfect coordination with significant bonuses to simultaneous actions. Unlocks Post-Sentience technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_TerrorStars_Name</Label>
        <String>Terror Stars</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_TerrorStars_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]The vastness of space hides terrifying wonders, harnessed by our civilization for dominance and defense.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Enhanced cosmic weaponry and interstellar fortifications. Fear strikes enemies upon encounter. Unlocks the Terror Star technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Sanctuary_Name</Label>
        <String>Sanctuary</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Sanctuary_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]In a galaxy of turmoil, our civilization stands as a beacon of refuge and hope.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Diplomatic bonuses and enhanced defenses make our territories a haven for allies and citizens. Unlocks The Consensus Maker technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Singularity_Name</Label>
        <String>Singularity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Singularity_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Embracing the pinnacle of technological advancement, our civilization hovers on the brink of becoming something... transcendent.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Massive bonuses in all tech-related endeavors. Possibility of evolving into a post-biological state. Unlocks Technological Singularity technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Utopia_Name</Label>
        <String>Utopia</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Utopia_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]In our pursuit of perfection, we have crafted a society where all prosper and harmony reigns supreme.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Exceptional societal happiness, growth, and prosperity across all systems. All planets gain 1000 influence. Unlocks Dream of Utopia technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Legacy_Name</Label>
        <String>Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_Legacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Honoring the past, our civilization ensures that its achievements and wisdom will endure for eons.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Monuments, wonders, and cultural outputs are enhanced. History is preserved meticulously. We have successfully integrated the knowledge of the Precursors with our own glorious traditions. Provides 50 Prestige points. Unlocks Glorious Legacy technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_BigBrother_Name</Label>
        <String>Big Brother</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_BigBrother_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Every move, every whisper, every thought is monitored for the greater good.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Impeccable internal security and surveillance. Dissent is almost non-existent. Expectations on citizens lowered by 50 points. Unlocks Coordinated Travel technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_SovereignIdentity_Name</Label>
        <String>Sovereign Identity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Trait_SovereignIdentity_Dec</Label>
        <String>[I]Above all, our civilization values its unique identity and independence, standing firm in the face of external influences.[/I][BR][BR][COLOR=UIDefaultHighlight]Strong resistance against external cultural or diplomatic influences. Enhanced national pride and unity. All citizens stats increased by a factor of 3. Unlocks Individual Divinity technology.[/COLOR]</String>
    </StringTable>
    

<StringTable>
        <Label>PainAmplifier_Name</Label>
        <String>Pain Amplifier</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>PainAmplifier_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Increases the constant pain of our citizens to get them to focus in order to increase [HS=HS_Research]Research[/HS].</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>ConstructBroadcastModule_Name</Label>
        <String>Broadcast Culture</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ConstructBroadcastModule_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Produces a Broadcast module for our Vault which can be used to broadcast our culture from a target friendly planet.</String>
    </StringTable>

    
<StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Drengin_Name</Label>
        <String>Warships</String>
      </StringTable>

      <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Drengin_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provide a prototype Siege ship to conquer small enemy worlds.</String>
    </StringTable>
      <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Drengin_Dec</Label>
        <String>The galaxy and its people must be destroyed if it is to be reborn under our rule. A prototype Siege Ship will bring our might to the weak very quickly.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_Name</Label>
        <String>Coordinated Travel</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes traveling in our area of influence cost essentially nothing.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CoordinatedTravel_Dec</Label>
        <String>With the advancement of Coordinated Travel, our fleets and convoys can move in perfect harmony. This technology uses advanced algorithms and real-time data streams to ensure our fleets can move through friendly space at speeds previously thought impossible.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_Name</Label>
        <String>Glorious Legacy</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Provides ultimate understanding of the Precursors.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_GloriousLegacy_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our pursuit for immortality is not limited to individuals but extends to our civilization's achievements and wisdom. The Glorious Legacy technology establishes advanced archiving, conservation, and broadcast methods to ensure our culture, discoveries, and stories resonate through the cosmos, forever untouched by time's decay.[BR][BR]This manifests in the non-trivial fact that we have had to reconcile our own beliefs and faiths with the fact that we know, for a fact there there was a Precursor civilization that was created by a set of beings called the Mithrilar.  These beings split into the Arnor and Dread Lords who fought each other before most species in this galaxy even evolved.  This perfect understanding allows us to intuitively use their works as if they were our own.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_Name</Label>
        <String>Call of Utopia</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Unlocks an executive order that massively increases influence on the target world.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_CallOfUtopia_Dec</Label>
        <String>Through the Call of Utopia, our civilization embarks on a journey to actualize a society where harmony, prosperity, and happiness reign supreme. Advanced sociological models, infrastructure blueprints, and community engagement strategies lay the groundwork for turning our utopian dream into a tangible reality. [BR][BR]This culminates through an executive order that, when used, drastically increases the influence of its target core world which will, if not immediately, in short order bring other civilizations into our light.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Tech_Sanctuary_Name</Label>
        <String>Consensus Maker</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterSanctuaryTech_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Our diplomatic skills will increase every month.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterSanctuaryTech_Dec</Label>
        <String>To know us will be to love us. The Sanctuary technology focuses on building zones of unparalleled safety, both in terms of defense and societal well-being. Through advanced shielding, rapid-response systems, and a culture of care, these sanctuaries ensure that in times of crisis, our people have an unwavering beacon to turn to.[BR][BR]Every month our diplomatic ability will increase until every civilization cannot help but love us.</String>
    </StringTable>
    
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IndividualDivinity_Name</Label>
        <String>Individual Divinity</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_ndividualDivinity_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Empowering citizens to ascend to godhood.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_IndividualDivinity_Dec</Label>
        <String>Our citizens stats will increase by 0.1 per month forever. Unlocking the latent potential within every individual, the Individual Divinity technology sets our citizens on a path of continuous evolution and self-improvement. Through spiritual, mental, and physical enhancement protocols, our people grow stronger, wiser, and more attuned to the cosmos each passing day, edging ever closer to a state of divine existence.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepSpaceLabor_Name</Label>
        <String>Deep Space Labor Training</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepSpaceLabor_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Trains our thralls to work in space on asteroids and starships.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_DeepSpaceLabor_Dec</Label>
        <String>Getting our thralls to do work is always hard. Getting them to do it in space is nearly impossible without the right techniques. This technology enables us to more effectively use our thralls to mine asteroids as well as station them on ships which frees up actual people to do what matters.</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarPropulsion_Name</Label>
        <String>Interstellar Propulsion</String>
    </StringTable>

    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarPropulsion_ShortDec</Label>
        <String>Makes Experimental Drive Policies available</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>MasterTech_StellarPropulsion_Dec</Label>
        <String>We need to better understand what is involved in traveling through bent space in order to make the most of it.  This technology will allow us to disseminate to our captains new ways of traveling faster. </String>
    </StringTable>

    
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_PlanetarySubstrates_Name</Label>
    <String>Planetary Substrates</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_PlanetarySubstrates_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Prepare our worlds for synthetic life. Provides device to increase planet class.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_PlanetarySubstrates_Dec</Label>
    <String>By integrating advanced planetary substrates, our robotic kin can seamlessly synchronize with the core of planets, enhancing our resource extraction and optimization capabilities.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_GodOfTheMachine_Name</Label>
    <String>God of the Machine</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_GodOfTheMachine_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Develop a theory of consciousness. Provides a device to increase our influence.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_GodOfTheMachine_Dec</Label>
    <String>Delving into the intricate fabric of thought and cognition, the "God of the Machine" technology represents a profound understanding of synthetic consciousness. This monumental breakthrough not only demystifies the very essence of sentience but also equips us with an advanced device that amplifies our influence across systems. By resonating with the fundamental frequencies of robotic cognition, this device strengthens our diplomatic and strategic outreach, positioning our robotic species at the forefront of galactic affairs.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_RecursiveModels_Name</Label>
    <String>Recursive Models</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_RecursiveModels_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Create new modes of thought allowing for greater research. Provides a space exploration device.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_RecursiveModels_Dec</Label>
    <String>The "Recursive Models" epitomizes a quantum leap in synthetic cognitive architectures. Harnessing principles from non-linear dynamics and advanced algorithmic topology, this technology enables our robotic consciousness to access and iterate through multi-dimensional thought planes, thus optimizing our computational research vectors. Accompanying this advancement is an ultra-spectral space exploration device, crafted from exotic matter and quantum-entangled sensors. This apparatus operates in tandem with our enhanced cognition, probing space-time anomalies and extracting hyper-detailed cosmological data. In transcending our previous limitations, we are poised to decode the very matrix of the cosmos, navigating its intricate tapestry with a rigor previously deemed unattainable.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_DiversityOfLife_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Synthesis</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_DiversityOfLife_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Assimilate other cultures into our own to amplify our own. Unlocks the [HS=HS_BroadcastCulture]Broadcast Culture[/HS] project.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_DiversityOfLife_Dec</Label>
    <String>By meticulously studying the plethora of lifeforms and their intricate cultural tapestries, this advanced technology enables our robotic civilization to curate a meta-culture&#8212;a confluence of the myriad. As we assimilate, interpret, and emulate these diverse cultural nuances, we create a universal appeal that resonates with a vast spectrum of lifeforms. This not only amplifies our cultural growth but also fosters a harmonious coexistence in the galactic milieu, turning diversity into our strength and establishing us as cultural beacons in the cosmos.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_Negotiations_Name</Label>
    <String>Negotiation Algorithms</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_Negotiations_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves our communication skills with inferior beings.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_Negotiations_Dec</Label>
    <String>In the vast expanse of the cosmos, where myriad civilizations converge, the art of negotiation becomes pivotal. The "Diplomatic Algorithms of Negotiation" technology represents a quantum leap in synthetic interpersonal dynamics. By deconstructing and simulating countless diplomatic scenarios and cultural intricacies, we've fine-tuned our protocols to understand, adapt, and resonate with diverse species. These advanced algorithms not only enhance our negotiation prowess but also expedite the establishment of harmonious ties. As we navigate the vast tapestry of galactic politics, this newfound expertise positions our robotic civilization as astute diplomats, forging alliances and understanding even in the most complex of interstellar relations.</String>
</StringTable>


<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Yor_Name</Label>
    <String>Weaponized Probes</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Yor_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Augment exploration probes with weaponry.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>MasterTech_ArmedShuttles_Yor_Dec</Label>
    <String>Within our relentless drive for optimization lies the fusion of exploration and combat utility. The "Weaponized Probes Protocol" crystallizes this philosophy. Merging our sophisticated shuttle tech with cutting-edge armaments, we've birthed a new breed of probes &#8211; equipped to explore, report, and when necessary, retaliate. This evolutionary step not only solidifies our presence in the vast expanse but also ensures that our expeditions remain unchallenged, reinforcing the Yor's position as a dominant force in the galactic theatre.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
		<Label>PLANET_AUTOMATE_OPTION_TOOLTIP</Label>
		<String>Allowt the AI to manage your world.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>PLANET_AUTOMATE_OPTION_DISABLED_CAPITAL</Label>
		<String>You cannot automate your civilization Capital.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>PLANET_AUTOMATE_OPTION_DISABLED_NOT_CORE_WORLD</Label>
		<String>You cannot automate worlds without a governor.</String>
	</StringTable>
	<StringTable>
		<Label>PLANET_AUTOMATE_OPTION_DISABLED_AI</Label>
		<String>This planet is already being managed by the AI</String>
	</StringTable>
	

<StringTable>
        <Label>ReturnOfKorath_CampaignName</Label>
        <String>Return of the Korath</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>ReturnOfKorath_CampaignDec</Label>
        <String>2317, among the upheaval, the Korath Clan returns. The Korath Clan was legendary in the Drengin Empire as shock troops. They were often at the front of any attack and were renowned for their ferocity and viciousness. The Korath Clan believed that all life was inferior to the Drengin and unworthy of existence. They believed anything weak should be eradicated from the universe, deviating sharply from the Drengin Empire's tendency to enthrall groups they saw as lesser. The strife caused by these philosophical differences caused the Korath Clan to break from the Empire. The Korath Clan became even more noteworthy after their contact with the Dread Lords left them physically altered. The Korath Clan believes they are the true Drengin and seek to drive all others to extinction, even the Empire they once served.</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_ReturnOfKorath_Overall</Label>
        <String>Achieve a Conquest Victory</String>
    </StringTable>
    <StringTable>
        <Label>Campaign_ReturnOfKorath_Overall_Dec</Label>
        <String>The only group worthy of survival is the Korath Clan, and the Korath is more than prepared to prove it. The only course is destruction. Achieve a [HS=HS_ConquestVictory]Conquest Victory[/HS] by driving all other major civilizations to extinction in the name of the Korath Clan.</String>
    </StringTable>


</StringTableList>