<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<StringTableList xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_HegemonySpawn_Name_5XA</Label>
    <String>Rise of the Hegemony</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_HegemonySpawn_Dec_5XA</Label>
    <String>Word has reached us that a new empire called The Hegemony has arrived in our part of space.[BR][BR]Allegedly they only want total domination of the galaxy.  They do not want peace.  They will not accept surrender. They wish to wipe everyone out.  We must be on guard for them.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_HegemonySpawn_Choice_Name</Label>
    <String>Understood.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_HegemonySpawn_Choice_Dec</Label>
    <String>We will keep an eye out for this new civilization.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SlyneSpawn_Name_5XA</Label>
    <String>Return of the Slyne</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SlyneSpawn_Dec_5XA</Label>
    <String>Word has reached us that the gelatinous species known as the Slyne have returned to our area of space.[BR][BR]Something has changed in them. It was well known that they experimented with cybernetic implants to enhance themselves but now they appear mad.[BR][BR]Reports indicate that they are on a rampage across the galaxy.  They must be stopped!</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SlyneSpawn_Choice_Name</Label>
    <String>Understood.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SlyneSpawn_Choice_Dec</Label>
    <String>We will keep an eye out for them.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnXendar_Name</Label>
    <String>The Xendar Resurgence</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnXendar_Dec</Label>
    <String>Galactic archives tell tales of the Xendar, a mighty civilization whose luminescence was extinguished by humans during the early years of exploration. The stars bore silent witness to their apparent end. But nothing in space remains hidden forever.[BR][BR]A force, pulsing with malice, has emerged from the void. The Xendar have returned, not as the pawns they once were, but as avatars of vengeance.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnXendar_Choice_Name</Label>
    <String>We must get ready!</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnXendar_Choice_Dec</Label>
    <String>We will not go quietly into the night.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnThalan_Name</Label>
    <String>Visitors from a Doomed Tomorrow</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnThalan_Dec</Label>
    <String>Subspace communication indicates have brought us knowledge that confirms our worst fears: Time travel is possible the users of it mean to espunge us from the timeline![BR][BR]The Thalan, a civilization from an alternative, crumbling future have arrived. In their timeline, the actions of our present civilizations lead to a future calamity that engulfs all. Now, they've embarked on a desperate mission: to save their own people, even if it means erasing us from existence.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnThalan_Choice_Name</Label>
    <String>Defend the Present!</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnThalan_Choice_Dec</Label>
    <String>We will not be erased. Probably.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnSnathi_Name_7XT</Label>
    <String>Whispers of the Furry Menace</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnSnathi_Dec_7XT</Label>
    <String>Intergalactic channels are abuzz with disconcerting rumors. Hailing from the hidden reaches of the cosmos, the Snathi, cosmic squirrels with a lust for domination, have made their ominous presence known.[BR][BR]Once thought to be mere space legends, whispered in hushed tones, these squirrels aren't here to hoard nuts. They've harnessed the energy of the stars, equipped their ships with weapons of unparalleled fury, and are now plotting their rapid expansion.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnSnathi_Choice_Name</Label>
    <String>We will stay alert.</String>
</StringTable>
<StringTable>
    <Label>Event_SpawnSnathi_Choice_Dec</Label>
    <String>We must prepare for the squirrelly onslaught.</String>
</StringTable>










<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_Name</Label>
    <String>Sylne Technocracy</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_ShortName</Label>
    <String>Sylne</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_LeaderName</Label>
    <String>Lord Aelron</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Sylne Federation, an ancient and secretive civilization, prides itself on its scientific advancements and the ability to withstand wars against all odds. Originating from the SlyneSystem, they are known for their neutral stance and expansionist motives.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_LeaderDec</Label>
    <String>Lord Aelron, a visionary leader of the Sylne Federation, is known for his strategic brilliance and his unwavering commitment to the progress of his people. He believes in a harmonious universe where science and peace coexist.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_HomeworldName</Label>
    <String>Slyne</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_Callsign</Label>
    <String>S.F.S.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
    <String>The Sylne Federation is a highly advanced civilization with a deep understanding of the universe. Their mastery over science and technology makes them a formidable foe to all who cross their path.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_StartupTitle</Label>
    <String>The Sylne Federation</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SYLNE_StartupDescription</Label>
    <String>The Sylne Federation, an ancient and secretive civilization, prides itself on its scientific advancements and the ability to withstand wars against all odds. Originating from the SlyneSystem, they are known for their neutral stance and expansionist motives.</String>
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_Name</Label>
    <String>Thalan Contingency</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_ShortName</Label>
    <String>Thalan</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_LeaderName</Label>
    <String>High Councillor Thelis</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Thalan Contingency, hailing from the distant ThalisSystem, are a unique blend of ancient knowledge and advanced time manipulation techniques. While their intentions are largely peaceful, their xenophobic tendencies keep them cautious of other civilizations. Their incredible mastery over time and deep understanding of the universe make them a formidable force.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_LeaderDec</Label>
    <String>High Councillor Thelis, a timeless figure of the Thalan Contingency, embodies wisdom and foresight. His leadership focuses on safeguarding Thalan traditions while adapting to the ever-evolving galactic stage. His vast knowledge has steered the Thalan through countless adversities.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_HomeworldName</Label>
    <String>Thalis</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_Callsign</Label>
    <String>T.C.S.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
    <String>The Thalan Contingency is a highly advanced civilization with a deep understanding of the universe. Their mastery over time and space makes them a formidable foe to all who cross their path.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_StartupTitle</Label>
    <String>The Thalan Contingency</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_THALAN_StartupDescription</Label>
    <String>The Thalan Contingency, hailing from the distant ThalisSystem, are a unique blend of ancient knowledge and advanced time manipulation techniques. While their intentions are largely peaceful, their xenophobic tendencies keep them cautious of other civilizations. Their incredible mastery over time and deep understanding of the universe make them a formidable force.</String>      
</StringTable>



<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_Name</Label>
    <String>Snathi Revenge</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_ShortName</Label>
    <String>Snathi</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_LeaderName</Label>
    <String>Overlord Squeek</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unleashed from their prison by the Dread Lords, the Snathi have returned with a burning vendetta. These aggressive space squirrels were once bio-engineered by the Precursors to be caretakers but turned into their most feared adversaries. The Snathi, now with their newfound freedom, will let no one stand in their way as they conquer the stars.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_LeaderDec</Label>
    <String>Overlord Squeek, the most fearsome and cunning of the Snathi, is a master tactician who seeks to bring the universe under his rule. With a sharp mind and an even sharper claw, Squeek will stop at nothing to exact revenge on those who dared to imprison his kind.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_StartupTitle</Label>
    <String>The Rise of the Snathi</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_StartupDescription</Label>
    <String>The universe once trembled at the very mention of the Snathi. With their newfound freedom, they are determined to reclaim their place in the cosmos, leaving devastation in their wake.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
    <String>Scavengers of ancient relics and zealous in their cause, the Snathi excel in expansion and warfare. Their resilience and toughness make them formidable opponents, and their ability to rally their kind under a single banner is unmatched.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_SNATHI_Callsign</Label>
    <String>R.G.S.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_Name</Label>
    <String>Xendar Remnants</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_ShortName</Label>
    <String>Xendar</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_LeaderName</Label>
    <String>Lord Vrexar</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_Faction_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Xendar Remnants are the surviving vestiges of a once-great civilization, obliterated by the Terran Alliance. Now, driven by vengeance and a thirst for power, they aim to retake the galaxy, ensuring that the Xendar name once more reigns supreme. Their past has taught them that only through strength and unity can they prevent future annihilation.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_Faction_LeaderDec</Label>
    <String>Lord Vrexar is a beacon of hope and vengeance for his people. A survivor of the Terran-Xendar war, his leadership is defined by his unwavering commitment to the Xendar's resurgence and his deep-seated resentment towards the Terran Alliance.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_HomeworldName</Label>
    <String>Xenoria</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_Callsign</Label>
    <String>X.S.S.</String>
</StringTable>

<StringTable>
    <Label>FACTION_XENDAR_StartupTraitsDescription</Label>
    <String>While they may be remnants of a bygone era, the Xendar are masterful engineers, expert colonizers, and fierce warriors. Their aggressive and xenophobic tendencies, born from a history of betrayal, make them a formidable foe to all who cross their path.</String>
</StringTable>





</StringTableList>